♪ Far off into the expanse of yellow sand ♪
♪ Comes great longing for a parted person ♪
♪ Moonlight like water, clouds like smoke ♪
♪ When did it once shine down ♪
♪ Afraid of mortal greed abiding ♪
♪ Can’t help answer your thousand words with ten thousand of mine ♪
♪ Back then a farewell, now meeting again ♪
♪ Lingering quietly grows from the fingertips ♪
♪ Even if your ears, nose, brows, eyes can’t be forgotten ♪
♪ Yet still wait for the two of us to have debts never more ♪
♪ Gathering orchids on an empty mountain ♪
♪ Searching for butterflies over the sea ♪
♪ Too much love and hate ultimately precludes fulfillment ♪
♪ Thrilling experiences rush by ♪
♪ Endlessly distant heaven and earth ♪
♪ Drooping eyes are all in the past ♪
♪ Lonely when you go ♪
♪ Yet dreams are indistinct when you return ♪
♪ Perhaps this love may not be as wished ♪
♪ Countless feelings overwhelm ♪
♪ Heart is shaken while still young ♪
♪ Asking who can, by whom, ♪
♪ be exempt ♪
Battle Through The Heavens - Season 3
Recap
Qing Lin?
It was
Yan City’s Mo Clan who did it.
Welcome, Clan Head.
Where’d they go?
No one in the Jia Ma Empire will be able to oppose me!
Misty Cloud Sect Leader’s personal disciple,
Nalan Yanran has come to express congratulations!
Episode 11
“Mo Estate”
Nalan
Yanran
Niece Nalan,
I did not expect that you would personally come today.
My Mo Clan is truly honored by your presence.
Clan Head Mo Cheng is very courteous.
Yanran was only following Teacher’s orders.
Niece Nalan,
Elder Ge Ye.
Please.
The banquet is down here.
Thank you all
for coming to the old me’s birthday banquet.
Now,
I will toast first
to thank everyone for coming.
That should be
the Mo Clan Head
Mo Cheng, nicknamed Executioner Mo, right?
What are you planning to do next?
Crash the party.
Doesn’t the Mo Clan like bullying people?
I’ll use overwhelming strength
to take down Mo Cheng
and make them hand over Qing Lin.
Since Mo Cheng is the Mo Clan Head,
his life, I imagine,
should be worth quite a bit, right?
Everyone, please sit.
Please.
On your invitations,
presumably it was made clear
that at this gathering,
besides the old me’s birthday,
there is an important matter
I want to discuss with everyone.
I am preparing to establish a Mo Alliance,
to have all powers in the Jia Ma Empire’s Northeast Region
assembled as one.
Once you join the Mo Alliance,
you will be my Mo Clan’s ally.
With my Mo Clan,
we will enjoy prosperity together
and face difficulties together.
My Tao Family village
definitely supports the Mo Clan.
We
will be the first to join the Mo Alliance!
Blackwater Ridge is also willing to join!
My Fort Feilun
is also willing to join the Mo Alliance!
Many thanks for your enthusiastic support.
The formation of the Mo Alliance
will allow our Northeast Region to unite as one.
From then on,
within the Jia Ma Empire,
the Mo Alliance will occupy an important—
Apologies,
Clan Head Mo Cheng.
I think
you probably won’t have time to set up the Mo Alliance.
Who is this sir?
Today is my Mo Clan’s joyous day.
If sir could please do a favor;
any matters,
please reserve until after the banquet ends to discuss.
How about it?
Take him down.
Vacuum Palm.
You are actually
a Fight Emperor?
I do not know why sir has come.
I come to Mo Clan
just for one person.
Hand over Qing Lin!
I do not know of any Qing Lin.
Sir,
do you not know
that my Mo Clan and the Misty Cloud Sect are—
Misty Cloud Sect is your Mo Clan’s patron,
right?
Yun Yun is just a sightless fogy
who can’t tell right from wrong.
Even if Yun Yun was here today,
you would not be saved.
Hand over Qing Lin.
Or else today
there’ll be a bloodbath.
I—
I don’t know what you’re talking about.
If not,
then die.
Sir,
although you are a Fight Emperor,
Sect Leader Yun
is not someone you can carelessly insult.
Today,
even if the old me has to stake my life,
for the sake of Sect Leader Yun’s reputation,
I must seek justice!
Young Lady,
you mustn’t be impulsive.
Nalan Yanran?
You’re pretty good at kissing ass.
But like I said before,
even if Yun Yun came,
I will strike all the same.
Young Lady!
This sir,
your words today,
are you trying to provoke
the Misty Cloud Sect and my teacher Yun Yun?
Outside of bringing up the Misty Cloud Sect and Yun Yun,
what else can you do?
Get lost.
Mo Cheng,
if you don’t hand over Qing Lin,
I will make you pay a price today.
Nobody can help you.
You—!
I, Mo Cheng,
have been righteous my whole life,
fighting to protect people from harm,
only killing those who ought to die.
The number of wicked people these hands have been dyed in the blood of,
I can no longer remember.
Those who kill will themselves be killed.
Even if these villains
have strong practitioners like you to avenge them,
I will still have no regrets.
Sir is a Fight Emperor;
on the basis of unwarranted charges,
acting arbitrarily
to insist on killing my Misty Cloud Sect’s External Deacon Mo Cheng.
My Misty Cloud Sect
will definitely not stand idly by!
Unwarranted?
You sure know how to spout drivel.
Mo Cheng.
You sanctimonious rat,
no matter how you continue to make excuses,
you can’t scrub away
those wicked deeds you have done!
False accusations can always be made.
If Fight Emperor wants to kill the old me,
I am not afraid of death;
but I also cannot be wronged for no reason!
Rest assured.
Your character,
we all know well.
The Misty Cloud Sect
definitely won’t let a good person be wronged.
Fight Emperor sir,
with your strength,
everyone here is no match for you.
But justice is within the human heart.
Using strength to bully the weak
will only cause you to be mocked by all!
That’s right.
Right, right.
Although the Mo Clan is a bit overbearing,
they haven’t done anything out of line.
This Fight Emperor is too domineering.
Do you want to die?
That person is a Fight Emperor,
he doesn’t need a reason to kill people!
Wonderful, wonderful.
Misty Cloud Sect’s future successor
really is eloquent.
But that brain of yours
doesn’t work so well.
Mo Cheng is a good person?
All these years,
he’s been transplanting Magical Beast organs
into people’s bodies.
Such a dehumanizing and depraved individual
is somehow considered a good person?
Mo Clan’s patron, the Misty Cloud Sect,
was actually unaware?
You maliciously frame me!
Such dirty deeds,
the Mo Clan Head would never do such a thing!
What is that?
What is this?
Old Hai,
my thanks.
This is one of Mo Clan’s test subjects.
If Young Lady Nalan is still unconvinced,
I can bring you to Mo Clan’s laboratory to take a look.
Qing Lin isn’t in the laboratory.
Where did you hide her?
Mo Cheng,
give me an explanation.
Misty Cloud Sect
will no longer bother with the Mo Clan’s business.
Uncle Ge,
we’re leaving.
Sir, just who are you?
Later,
you will naturally find out.
Where is Qing Lin?
What is he doing?
On the Dou Qi Continent,
strength reigns supreme.
Whether it’s experiments,
or forbidden arts.
In order to become stronger,
where have I, Mo Cheng, gone wrong?
Misty Cloud Sect
is able to dominate the land
because they possess a Fight Emperor!
And you
are able to bully and do as you please here
because you are stronger than me, right?
Power.
As long as I can acquire immense power,
I no longer need to fear any of you!
In order to pursue power,
he turned himself into a half-human, half-beast monstrosity.
Another wretched person who lost their way on the path to power.
Not enough.
Not nearly enough!
Clan— Clan Head!
It— it— it’s me!
You—!
After eating you,
I will become stronger!
This is all you’ve got?
Heavenly Flame?
I need power,
power!
Triple Jade-Green Snake Flower Pupils.
Once I swallow her,
I will obtain true power!
Qing Lin!
Old Hai,
let’s chase.
Up ahead.
Hand over Qing Lin.
In your dreams.
Hmph.
Is that going to help?
What is this?
It can actually resist Heavenly Flame.
Dammit!
Teacher,
do you know what’s wrong?
I have never before encountered such a tough barrier.
This is definitely not a product of the Jia Ma Empire.
This is an Isolation Barrier.
After it is activated,
it can cut off the attacks of Fight Ancestor and below;
and its most magical property
is that it can even cut off Heavenly Flame attacks.
So powerful.
This is the Hall of—
Don’t have a choice;
we can only wait until the isolation device’s energy runs out.
Otherwise, no one can enter.
Shit.
Qing Lin has to be inside.
Fight Emperor.
After swallowing the Triple Jade-Green Snake Flower Pupils,
I can complete the final evolution.
At that point,
who can still be my opponent?
Where—
where’d she go?
Who?
Who’s there?
Dammit,
give her back to me!
Your instincts are quite sharp.
It’s a pity,
this kind of low level forbidden fusion art really is uninteresting.
Lu Man
It really is the Triple Jade-Green Snake Flower Pupils.
Looks like Elder’s feeling wasn’t off.
Just who are you?
So it’s something from the Hall of Souls.
Now that the person is found,
it’s about time for me to return.
Noo!
It’s Qing Lin!
Chase!
Give her back!
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Have you thought about ♪
♪ After crossing this desert ♪
♪ Just what lies ahead ♪
♪ Shall I fall here ♪
♪ Or firmly grasp onto fate’s ♪
♪ pulse ♪
♪ He once ♪
♪ loved ♪
♪ hated ♪
♪ suffered ♪
♪ until seeing that flame in the distance ♪
♪ Perhaps this ♪
♪ is ruinous ♪
♪ is excessive ♪
♪ is wrong ♪
♪ Yet still unafraid ♪
♪ to burn ♪
♪ Disregard that unbounded universe ♪
♪ Engage in a fight ♪
♪ Who can resist the wave splitting flame ♪
♪ Don’t speak of this endless dangerous threshold ♪
♪ Reject the climb ♪
♪ He intends to ride the wind ♪
♪ straight through ♪
♪ the heavens ♪
Preview