♪ Far off into the expanse of yellow sand ♪
♪ Comes great longing for a parted person ♪
♪ Moonlight like water, clouds like smoke ♪
♪ When did it once shine down ♪
♪ Afraid of mortal greed abiding ♪
♪ Can’t help answer your thousand words with ten thousand of mine ♪
♪ Back then a farewell, now meeting again ♪
♪ Lingering quietly grows from the fingertips ♪
♪ Even if your ears, nose, brows, eyes can’t be forgotten ♪
♪ Yet still wait for the two of us to have debts never more ♪
♪ Gathering orchids on an empty mountain ♪
♪ Searching for butterflies over the sea ♪
♪ Too much love and hate ultimately precludes fulfillment ♪
♪ Thrilling experiences rush by ♪
♪ Endlessly distant heaven and earth ♪
♪ Drooping eyes are all in the past ♪
♪ Lonely when you go ♪
♪ Yet dreams are indistinct when you return ♪
♪ Perhaps this love may not be as wished ♪
♪ Countless feelings overwhelm ♪
♪ Heart is shaken while still young ♪
♪ Asking who can, by whom, ♪
♪ be exempt ♪
Battle Through The Heavens - Season 3
Recap
On the Dou Qi Continent,
strength reigns supreme.
Whether it’s experiments,
or forbidden arts.
In order to become stronger,
where have I, Mo Cheng, gone wrong?
After swallowing the Triple Jade-Green Snake Flower Pupils,
I can complete the final evolution.
At that point,
who can still be my opponent?
So it’s something from the Hall of Souls.
Now that the person is found,
it’s about time for me to return.
Give her back!
Episode 12
Although you are very strong,
under our two Fight Emperors’ pincer attack,
trying to leave won’t be an easy task.
As long as you return Qing Lin to me,
that will be the end of it.
Hmph.
Your name is Qing Lin?
Good name.
Qing Lin is extremely important to me.
Handing her to you?
No way.
Two Fight Emperors want to stop me.
You can go ahead and try!
Go.
Careful, Xiao Yan,
avoid hurting Qing Lin!
Don’t worry, Teacher,
I know what I’m doing.
Thanks, Old Hai.
Your Heavenly Flame isn’t bad.
Pity the way you use it is far too crude!
This attack again.
Hmph.
Is that it.
Jia Man Empire’s maniacs
really don’t like being reasoned with.
Luckily,
I also don’t like being reasoned with!
Break!
That’s—
Qing Lin!
Mo Cheng,
as long as you give back Qing Lin,
I promise to spare your life!
Spare my life?
Fuck that!
Because of your so-called justice,
you destroyed my Mo Clan,
ruined my plans!
No,
not quite there yet...
Clearly you yourself went astray!
In this world, strength reigns supreme,
winners become king!
As long as I am stronger than you,
I make the rules;
what then distinguishes right from wrong?
You dare!
You bug,
daring to harm my Sky Serpent Mansion’s Saintess?
Qing Lin.
This—
Teacher,
Qing Lin’s been poisoned.
This isn’t poison.
Fight Emperor sir,
I am Sky Serpent Mansion’s Lu Man.
Just then, if I wasn’t concerned about staying too long here
and attracting Jia Ma Empire’s other strong practitioners,
just the two of you
would not necessarily be my match.
Who’d have guessed
that this filthy thing would launch a sneak attack.
Qing Lin’s soul has been partially sucked away.
I must immediately bring her back to the Sacred Pool for nourishment.
Combined with my Mansion’s Secret Technique,
her soul can be fully restored.
Xiao Yan,
she is right.
Qing Lin’s soul is impaired.
If it isn’t nourished and restored as soon as possible,
it won’t be long
before Qing Lin...
Stop hesitating.
A while ago,
my Mansion’s Great Elder
sensed that a reincarnated Saintess possessing the Triple Jade-Green Snake Flower Pupils had appeared
and specially had me come welcome the Saintess back to the Mansion.
And Qing Lin
is that reincarnated Saintess I was looking for.
The Saintess’s aura is getting weaker and weaker.
Give the Saintess to me;
I promise that Sky Serpent Mansion will save the Saintess!
That monster still hasn’t died.
Damn it,
this monster’s strength is skyrocketing.
Careful.
In the pursuit of power,
he lost his heart.
He is no longer human,
but rather, a beast that has lost all reason.
Power.
I will eat her!
Currently, all that monster can see
is this girl, Qing Lin.
While I was snooping in the Mo Estate,
I saw records for this kind of fusion technique.
It requires swallowing the intact soul of the Triple Jade-Green Snake Flower Pupils
for this monster to complete its evolution.
Its strength
would then be comparable to the peak of Fight Emperor.
Peak of Fight Emperor?
Bring Qing Lin and leave;
fully recover her health.
This monster,
allow us to deal with it.
Sky Serpent Mansion
wishes more than anyone for Qing Lin to be safe.
Thank you both.
Remember,
if a single hair on Qing Lin’s body is harmed,
I will settle things with the Sky Serpent Mansion.
Your enemy
is us.
Dammit,
he’s too fast.
The Heavenly Flame can’t get close.
Old Hai,
freeze him!
Aye.
Green Lotus Core Flame.
Burn it all!
With this Heavenly Flame’s power,
even a Fight Emperor
would be gravely wounded.
Unexpectedly, this kid actually has two kinds of Heavenly Flame.
Shit!
Xiao Yan!
I’m going all out!
He’s catching up.
Old Hai,
I’m counting on you to hold back this monster.
I have a way of dealing with him.
Kid,
whatever attack it is, use it now!
I can’t hold on much longer!
One kind of Heavenly Flame’s power isn’t enough;
then how about two kinds?
Stop, Xiao Yan!
You actually want to merge two kinds of Heavenly Flame?
Stop now!
Your body is simply unable to withstand the Heavenly Flames’ violent energy;
doing this
is like burning yourself from playing with fire!
Teacher,
believe me!
Merging Heavenly Flames?
Insane.
This fellow has gone insane!
Bastard,
if you die, who will refine the Spiritual Recovery Purple Pill for me?!
Shit,
stabilize!
Stinky brat,
if you go on like this,
your body will fall apart!
I need more power;
only this way,
I won’t be slighted by others.
Only this way
can I protect
those I care about!
Since you insist in such a way,
fine.
Xiao Yan,
stabilize your mind.
This is
the seed formed from merging two kinds of Heavenly Flame?
So it’s like this.
Dou Qi,
Heavenly Flame,
Flame Mantra.
All things
lead to the same path.
This terrifying power.
Two kinds of Heavenly Flames combined,
it actually succeeded!
Xiao Yan,
I have to admit
that you are always full of surprises.
Does this have a name?
I will call it
Angry Buddha Fire Lotus.
I’ll let you
test its power.
Go,
Angry Buddha Fire Lotus!
With my current strength,
is this the end..?
Stinky brat, be careful!
Teacher.
Where is this?
Teacher?
Teacher!
So you were here!
Teacher,
did you see it?
My Angry Buddha Fire Lotus succeeded!
The Angry Buddha Fire Lotus’s destructive power,
even I
would be amazed by it.
Even if Teacher can no longer be by your side in the future,
you now possess the capital to overcome strong enemies.
Everything
has been thanks to your nurturing.
Teacher’s strength, paired with my Angry Buddha Fire Lotus
can definitely rule the world in the future!
The Angry Buddha Fire Lotus you invented,
Teacher is quite satisfied with it.
However, with my body’s current condition,
I’m afraid I can no longer maintain my spiritual state.
I must fall into a slumber.
What—
What’s going on?
Xiao Yan,
Teacher is very happy to have you as my disciple.
Ha ha ha.
Teacher,
Teacher!
I can—
I can transfer Dou Qi to you,
I—
Silly child,
in the future,
Teacher won’t be able to continue protecting you.
Everything,
you will have to rely on yourself.
Angry Buddha Fire Lotus.
It has to be because I forcefully used the Angry Buddha Fire Lotus.
It was me...
It was me that harmed Teacher.
In only thinking about pursuing strength
I neglected the person I should’ve cared most for.
I am a fool.
What’s the use
of wanting all this power?
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Have you thought about ♪
♪ After crossing this desert ♪
♪ Just what lies ahead ♪
♪ Shall I fall here ♪
♪ Or firmly grasp onto fate’s ♪
♪ pulse ♪
♪ He once ♪
♪ loved ♪
♪ hated ♪
♪ suffered ♪
♪ until seeing that flame in the distance ♪
♪ Perhaps this ♪
♪ is ruinous ♪
♪ is excessive ♪
♪ is wrong ♪
♪ Yet still unafraid ♪
♪ to burn ♪
♪ Disregard that unbounded universe ♪
♪ Engage in a fight ♪
♪ Who can resist the wave splitting flame ♪
♪ Don’t speak of this endless dangerous threshold ♪
♪ Reject the climb ♪
♪ He intends to ride the wind ♪
♪ straight through ♪
♪ the heavens ♪