♪ Far off into the expanse of yellow sand ♪
♪ Comes great longing for a parted person ♪
♪ Moonlight like water, clouds like smoke ♪
♪ When did it once shine down ♪
♪ Afraid of mortal greed abiding ♪
♪ Can’t help answer your thousand words with ten thousand of mine ♪
♪ Back then a farewell, now meeting again ♪
♪ Lingering quietly grows from the fingertips ♪
♪ Even if your ears, nose, brows, eyes can’t be forgotten ♪
♪ Yet still wait for the two of us to have debts never more ♪
♪ Gathering orchids on an empty mountain ♪
♪ Searching for butterflies over the sea ♪
♪ Too much love and hate ultimately precludes fulfillment ♪
♪ Thrilling experiences rush by ♪
♪ Endlessly distant heaven and earth ♪
♪ Drooping eyes are all in the past ♪
♪ Lonely when you go ♪
♪ Yet dreams are indistinct when you return ♪
♪ Perhaps this love may not be as wished ♪
♪ Countless feelings overwhelm ♪
♪ Heart is shaken while still young ♪
♪ Asking who can, by whom, ♪
♪ be exempt ♪
Battle Through The Heavens - Season 3
Recap
I heard that Your Majesty The Queen
obtained the Green Lotus Core Flame half a year ago.
Sect Leader Yun,
why provoke the Snake People?
The Queen died!
Avenge the Queen!
Kill them!
Peak of Fight King?
This place actually has mechanisms?
Octane Blast!
Heavenly Flame,
I’m coming!
Episode 4
Green Lotus Core Flame.
Ten years to form a spirit,
hundred years to take shape,
thousand years to become a lotus.
It has been a thousand years.
My race has also
endured in the desert for such a long time.
Purple Cloud Wings!
Purple Cloud Wings!!
Did it stop working?
That hurt like hell...
The air has been cast under a flying prohibition.
Didn’t expect there to be such a mysterious space underneath the altar.
I actually didn’t die...
then this time I really am lucky to be alive.
Such a high place, yet still didn’t fall to my death.
Stinky brat,
good thing you have the Sea Core Vest gifted by Yun Zhi,
otherwise...
Yun Zhi.
The most important thing right now
is to find the Heavenly Flame.
Teacher,
the Green Lotus Pedestal
sensed that the Heavenly Flame is just ahead.
That’s right,
the Heavenly Flame’s aura is very noticeable.
Then what are we waiting for?
Let’s go!
Ready...
Shoot!
Careful.
This uncle will meet you again!
Damn it—
Die!
Go to hell!
Shoot!
Go!
Yan Shi, sir,
we’ve come.
Mo Basi
Elder,
leader of the Mo Tribe, Mo Basi has arrived.
Damn you!
Despicable human!
Mo Basi, I will assist you!
Gu He,
where is the Heavenly Flame?
Yan Shi,
Feng Li,
hold them back.
Leave it to us.
Heavenly Flame aura is in four places;
the aura is weakest in the west.
Illusory is real, real is illusory.
It is the most probable location of the Heavenly Flame.
I’ll charge there with you.
En.
Your opponents are us.
Only you two?
Try this attack!
That scared me.
Teacher,
don’t you think
it’s too quiet here?
Makes me feel very nervous.
Teacher,
didn’t you say there’s a flying prohibition;
then how can you be floating around?
Spiritual bodies are not constrained by the prohibition, of course.
Stinky kid,
hurry and keep up.
Spiritual body.
Teacher,
wait for me!
The Heavenly Flame is on the island.
Let’s swim over.
Get back!
Why’d you pull me, teacher!
Th—
This—
This lake’s water has poison!
The lake’s water is highly toxic.
Even a Fight King would be in trouble touching a small amount.
Dammit,
can’t fly and also can’t swim there.
We can only use the most brainless method,
same as when we entered the magma last time.
Envelop you,
cross the water and reach the island.
Teacher,
let’s hurry,
time is precious!
Don’t dilly-dally,
the water’s toxicity is extremely high;
although my Bone Chilling Flame can prevent it from getting into your body,
it causes my Spiritual Strength
to be rapidly exhausted.
I’ll make haste and swim over.
Green Lotus Core Flame?
Queen Medusa places such great importance on the Heavenly Flame,
yet here there are no traces of her.
We’ve been tricked,
this Heavenly Flame is fake!
I’m infuriated!
The remaining three locations also have Heavenly Flame,
we still have an opportunity.
Yes,
there’s still opportunity.
Let’s see where you guys run.
Kill them!
Dream on!
Break for me, all of you!
Old He,
about time you came over.
Recover your strength as quickly as possible.
Brother,
we’ve been saved.
Fight Emperor!
If this Queen were to become a martyr,
you
can remain here.
It’s him.
Your good luck ends here.
There are snakes in the water?
Exploding Steps!
Good thing I reacted quickly.
The Heavenly Flame is just up there.
Won’t be long before you two can reunite.
Be careful,
Queen Medusa is also up there.
Let’s play it by ear.
En.
Teacher,
let’s go.
She discovered me!
He actually hasn’t died?
From the holy pool to here,
this human kid has survived it all.
Perhaps,
this is Heaven’s reminder to me
that no matter what his purpose is,
there will be someone to witness
my devotion to the Snake People race.
Even if swallowing the Heavenly Flame fails
and I sacrifice my body for this,
I will be worthy as the Queen of the Snake People.
Cannot hesitate any longer.
Snake Spirit,
please watch over me!
Teacher,
the Queen discovered me
yet did not show any reaction;
this is a bit too odd...
I reckon she also did not expect
to keep fatefully running into a stinky brat like you.
What?
She’s about to swallow the Heavenly Flame.
Then let’s take action immediately.
Wait a little more;
waiting until she is at her weakest
will present the best opportunity to take action.
Medusa is about to start swallowing the Heavenly Flame.
This is Queen Medusa’s original form?
After a Snake Person is born,
a Secret Technique is used to infuse the spirit of a snake-type Magical Beast into their body.
Once this kind of companion spirit snake-type Magical Beast is merged,
summoning an original form like this
causes their strength to skyrocket.
This is also the Snake People’s greatest trump card.
How powerful.
Then swallowing a Heavenly Flame,
shouldn’t it be very easy?
Medusa, for the sake of leading her people back to their homeland,
is taking the risk of swallowing a Heavenly Flame to advance to Fight Ancestor.
Ai,
there is only a small chance of survival.
For the sake of her people?
A thousand years ago,
the Snake People were exiled to this place.
The desert’s intense heat
is incompatible with their bodies.
Returning to their homeland
is also the long-held wish of every generation’s Queen Medusa.
Medusa will start swallowing the Heavenly Flame!
Xiao Yan,
be careful.
If trouble arises,
flee immediately.
Both the Heavenly Flame and Medusa
are extremely dangerous.
In order to lead your people’s return to their homeland,
you are willing to endure searing pain.
While I, in order to win the Three Year Agreement
and protect the people I care about,
am also willing to endure the pain of Heavenly Flame’s burning.
We
are not so different.
She is as tenacious as you.
Teacher,
is it her weakest moment now?
Keep waiting.
Your Majesty The Queen.
Queen!
Queen Medusa.
You did it for the well-being of your people,
while I am the same as you.
For the sake of the family members I hold dear,
for the sake of lost dignity,
I want to prove to the world
that for my heart’s desires, I am willing
to sacrifice everything.
Even if that means
dying from the Heavenly Flame.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Have you thought about ♪
♪ After crossing this desert ♪
♪ Just what lies ahead ♪
♪ Shall I fall here ♪
♪ Or firmly grasp onto fate’s ♪
♪ pulse ♪
♪ He once ♪
♪ loved ♪
♪ hated ♪
♪ suffered ♪
♪ until seeing that flame in the distance ♪
♪ Perhaps this ♪
♪ is ruinous ♪
♪ is excessive ♪
♪ is wrong ♪
♪ Yet still unafraid ♪
♪ to burn ♪
♪ Disregard that unbounded universe ♪
♪ Engage in a fight ♪
♪ Who can resist the wave splitting flame ♪
♪ Don’t speak of this endless dangerous threshold ♪
♪ Reject the climb ♪
♪ He intends to ride the wind ♪
♪ straight through ♪
♪ the heavens ♪
Preview