♪ Far off into the expanse of yellow sand ♪
♪ Comes great longing for a parted person ♪
♪ Moonlight like water, clouds like smoke ♪
♪ When did it once shine down ♪
♪ Afraid of mortal greed abiding ♪
♪ Can’t help answer your thousand words with ten thousand of mine ♪
♪ Back then a farewell, now meeting again ♪
♪ Lingering quietly grows from the fingertips ♪
♪ Even if your ears, nose, brows, eyes can’t be forgotten ♪
♪ Yet still wait for the two of us to have debts never more ♪
♪ Gathering orchids on an empty mountain ♪
♪ Searching for butterflies over the sea ♪
♪ Too much love and hate ultimately precludes fulfillment ♪
♪ Thrilling experiences rush by ♪
♪ Endlessly distant heaven and earth ♪
♪ Drooping eyes are all in the past ♪
♪ Lonely when you go ♪
♪ Yet dreams are indistinct when you return ♪
♪ Perhaps this love may not be as wished ♪
♪ Countless feelings overwhelm ♪
♪ Heart is shaken while still young ♪
♪ Asking who can, by whom, ♪
♪ be exempt ♪
Battle Through The Heavens - Season 3
Recap
A Fight Emperor’s strength,
could a Fight King shake it?
Five Snake Spirit Gathering!
I would actually fall here...
It was you who hurt her;
then leave your lives behind!
Episode 8
On the Dou Qi Continent,
the gap between Qi Methods
is determined by
the degree to which the Qi vortex within the Qi center can accommodate Dou Qi;
difference in Dou Qi quality;
the rate of absorption of natural energy
and its refinement into Dou Qi during training;
and
the speed and ease of driving Dou Qi during battle.
Qi Methods
are split, from highest to lowest, into Tian, Di, Xuan, and Huang
When cultivation class is equal,
those who practice high class Qi Methods
far surpass those who practice low class Qi Methods.
The higher the class of the Qi Method you practice,
the greater
the benefits it brings.
Xiao Yan.
Xiao Yan!
Wake up!
Use your resilience to conquer the Heavenly Flame.
Do not give up!
My family’s Young Lady
is the Misty Cloud Sect Leader, Yun Yun’s most prized disciple.
How could she have trash for a husband?
Heavenly Flame.
Xiao Yan,
since you don’t want Uncle Xiao’s reputation damaged,
after three years,
come to the Misty Cloud Sect to challenge me.
If I win,
our engagement shall be annulled on the spot.
Can’t
give up.
I...
must succeed.
Beast Flame?
Acceptance Spirit
can open up a special space inside your body
used to store a Heavenly Flame.
Xiao Yan,
find a way to drive the flame seed into the Acceptance Spirit.
Go to
the Acceptance Spirit!
This aura,
how did it suddenly become this much stronger?
Although refining a Heavenly Flame can raise one’s fighting strength,
it shouldn’t have the ability to increase cultivation class.
Refining the Heavenly Flame
seems to have succeeded.
It succeeded.
It succeeded!
I did it!
Teacher,
You seem to have changed quite a lot.
All your wounds are healed too.
I feel great.
I feel like
my whole body is filled with energy.
Use your full strength to hit me.
Let me sense which star you’ve currently reached.
Teacher,
here goes.
You’ve actually reached a Four-star Fight Master’s strength.
What did you do?
Four-star Fight Master?
After entering the empty-mind state,
while in a trance,
I think I saw the flame seed repairing the meridians inside my body.
So that’s what happened.
What a lucky fellow.
Is this not
supposed to be a benefit of refining a Heavenly Flame?
Dream on.
Refining a Heavenly Flame,
only after gradually becoming proficient at controlling it
will it bring you benefit.
Within a short period of time, it shouldn’t cause any increase in strength.
Your situation,
first time I’ve seen something like it.
But it’s a pity;
if you were a Fight Spirit or Fight King
and still soared by several stars,
then you would really have profited big time.
I’m already satisfied with soaring to four stars.
If it was any higher,
my body couldn’t adapt to this level of strength.
After all,
haven’t I relied on training one step at a time to get here.
Good.
Knowing when enough is enough.
Come,
try out your Origin Flame Seed.
Green Lotus Core Flame.
Appear!
I, Xiao Yan, finally possess a Heavenly Flame!
Right, Teacher,
now that I have a Heavenly Flame,
can I immediately start forging the Flame Mantra?
Don’t rush.
Everything is about balance.
Swallowing the Heavenly Flame tonight has already exhausted your energy.
Rest for a day first.
Xiao Li
Sand Mercenary Company has taken things too far.
Kidnapping Qing Lin in the middle of the street,
do they think our Desert Metal no longer has any people?
Big Brother,
I’ll immediately bring our men
Xiao Ding
to go confront Luo Bu!
Halt.
Sand Mercenary Company’s strength has skyrocketed recently.
Apart from that Fight Grandmaster Luo Bu,
another Fight Grandmaster has appeared.
Two of Rock Desert City’s medium-sized mercenary groups
have just been cleaned up by them.
Nothing to be afraid of.
Big Brother,
we at Desert Metal
aren’t cowards!
Second Brother.
Xue Lan
Company Leader,
there’s trouble.
Xue Lan!
Xue Lan.
What happened?
Who hurt you?
Sand Mercenary Company.
They surrounded our compound
and spouted
that in one day’s time,
if we don’t submit,
they would make Desert Metal a bloodbath.
Luo Bu!
The air temperature
has already reached its lowest point.
Right now is the coolest time of day.
Although it’ll provide little help in using the Heavenly Flame to forge the Flame Mantra,
we can’t just give up.
Xiao Yan.
You can begin.
When forging the Flame Mantra,
I am unable to help you.
Everything is up to you.
Don’t worry,
Teacher.
You are the only person who practices the Flame Mantra.
Whether it possesses the qualifications and potential befitting of a Tian Class Qi Method,
all of that, you have to gauge.
Based on what the scroll said,
to evolve this Qi Method,
you must continually swallow Heavenly Flame.
You already narrowly escaped death in swallowing the Green Lotus Core Flame.
If the Flame Mantra is unable to evolve,
abandon this kind of Qi Method.
Teacher,
now isn’t the time to say depressing things.
Even if trying to evolve the Flame Mantra fails this time,
I believe
I still won’t give it up.
You said before,
it is a necessity for me to become a strong practitioner at the peak.
Not to mention,
your new body
can only be refined with the flame produced after evolving the Flame Mantra.
Giving up on practicing the Flame Mantra
would be giving up on your hopes of resurrection.
Disciple is not willing
and won’t give in.
Since you persist,
then,
my good disciple,
train in peace.
I believe that you can succeed.
Even if this Qi Method is unable to evolve,
your Teacher
will do everything possible
to make you
a peak practitioner.
This
is the Flame Mantra’s space?
It is only a Huang Class, Low Level Qi Method,
yet it is already this imposing.
Green Lotus Core Flame,
between heaven and earth,
you are the first Heavenly Flame to forge the Flame Mantra!
Go!
Merge with the Flame Mantra into one!
Trying to run?
Green Lotus Core Flame,
You once surrendered to me.
Follow me in forging the Flame Mantra!
Go!
Still trying to run?
Disobedient, huh.
Then I’ll force you to be obedient!
Xiao Yan.
Hang in there.
This thing,
how is it so powerful?
Something happened.
Xiao Yan,
stinky brat!
Xiao Yan!
Stinky brat,
wake up!
Wake up!
Forget this bullshit Flame Mantra.
Leave.
We are leaving now!
Teacher.
I—
I won’t leave.
Let me
try once more.
Or else
I can’t accept it.
You are getting yourself killed!
Stinky brat,
I was never going to trust anyone again.
Back then, accepting you as a disciple
was only because I wanted to absorb your Dou Qi
and restore my body.
However,
why must you be this stubborn?
You are actually willing
to court death for my sake.
Today,
even if it means losing this old life of mine,
I will rescue you!
Xiao Yan,
as my disciple,
you must hang in there.
Let go, Teacher!
Your foundation will be damaged by the Green Lotus Core Flame!
Let go!
Even if I die,
I will make you merge with the Flame Mantra!
This is Teacher’s only hope for resurrection!
Teacher,
wonderful.
You’ve woken up.
Congratulations, Xiao Yan.
You’ve successfully proven that this Flame Mantra
really can swallow Heavenly Flame.
Its potential
is indeed limitless.
And your potential
is also limitless.
I—
I really did it!
Xuan Class, Middle Level.
Teacher,
the Flame Mantra has increased by an entire class
compared to the previous Huang Class Middle Level.
Not bad.
It is worthy of being the Green Lotus Core Flame,
able to supply such powerful energy for evolving the Qi Method.
But the process
was extremely dangerous.
That kind of agony was truly horrifying.
If the Heavenly Flame’s backlash succeeded back then,
even my spirit, I’m afraid,
would have been incinerated to nothingness.
This Flame Mantra is indeed strange.
Who knows which madman invented it.
At the time, we went through countless hardships
to obtain this thing from that damned place.
Teacher.
How much time remains
until that Three Year Agreement?
Two months.
Nalan Yanran.
These last two months,
you’d better get ready.
As long as the Flame Mantra continues to swallow Heavenly Flames
and reaches Tian Class,
Teacher will be able to be resurrected.
Hai Bodong’s map of the Purifying Lotus Demon Flame,
we must obtain it.
Pity,
at the Snake People Shrine,
I forgot to look for Sand Datura.
Stinky brat,
take a look at this.
You forgot,
but I didn’t forget.
Then what’re we waiting for?
Teacher,
let’s go find Hai Bodong!
This stinky brat.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Have you thought about ♪
♪ After crossing this desert ♪
♪ Just what lies ahead ♪
♪ Shall I fall here ♪
♪ Or firmly grasp onto fate’s ♪
♪ pulse ♪
♪ He once ♪
♪ loved ♪
♪ hated ♪
♪ suffered ♪
♪ until seeing that flame in the distance ♪
♪ Perhaps this ♪
♪ is ruinous ♪
♪ is excessive ♪
♪ is wrong ♪
♪ Yet still unafraid ♪
♪ to burn ♪
♪ Disregard that unbounded universe ♪
♪ Engage in a fight ♪
♪ Who can resist the wave splitting flame ♪
♪ Don’t speak of this endless dangerous threshold ♪
♪ Reject the climb ♪
♪ He intends to ride the wind ♪
♪ straight through ♪
♪ the heavens ♪
Preview