♪ Far off into the expanse of yellow sand ♪
♪ Comes great longing for a parted person ♪
♪ Moonlight like water, clouds like smoke ♪
♪ When did it once shine down ♪
♪ Afraid of mortal greed abiding ♪
♪ Can’t help answer your thousand words with ten thousand of mine ♪
♪ Back then a farewell, now meeting again ♪
♪ Lingering quietly grows from the fingertips ♪
♪ Even if your ears, nose, brows, eyes can’t be forgotten ♪
♪ Yet still wait for the two of us to have debts never more ♪
♪ Gathering orchids on an empty mountain ♪
♪ Searching for butterflies over the sea ♪
♪ Too much love and hate ultimately precludes fulfillment ♪
♪ Thrilling experiences rush by ♪
♪ Endlessly distant heaven and earth ♪
♪ Drooping eyes are all in the past ♪
♪ Lonely when you go ♪
♪ Yet dreams are indistinct when you return ♪
♪ Perhaps this love may not be as wished ♪
♪ Countless feelings overwhelm ♪
♪ Heart is shaken while still young ♪
♪ Asking who can, by whom, ♪
♪ be exempt ♪
Battle Through The Heavens - Season 3
Recap
Queen Medusa has deployed an energy barrier beneath this altar.
The energy barrier can’t hold up for much longer.
Xiao Yan, move now!
Before Queen Medusa regains consciousness,
snatch the Heavenly Flame!
Wait until I recapture the Heavenly Flame;
I will also prove to the world
that for the sake of my heart’s desires
I am willing to endure searing pain.
Teacher,
what is this thing?
Episode 6
Yun Zhi, Gu He and company, who had entered the island to look for the Heavenly Flame,
could not find anything in the end.
While Xiao Yan,
taking advantage of two sides fighting,
seized the opportunity to snatch away the Heavenly Flame.
Unexpectedly,
he accidentally left traces behind.
Jia Ma Empire’s strong practitioners,
while trying to chase down Xiao Yan,
ended up confronting the Snake People’s
four Great Leaders’ interception.
Coming as you please,
leaving as you please!
What kind of place do you take my Snake People’s for?
Then allow me to seek advice from you!
I’ll hold them back.
You go chase after the Heavenly Flame.
If we’re late,
the Heavenly Flame will really be stolen by someone else.
Then I’ll leave this place to Sect Leader Yun.
Yan Shi,
Feng Li,
let’s go.
Come back here!
Watch out!
Your opponent is me.
Hold off this Fight Emperor!
Aye!
Petty tricks.
Prepare to die.
Elder, careful!
Damn it!
Eat this!
Can’t waste any more time.
Wind Return to Earth!
Not good, quickly disperse!
Another four have come.
Looks like it’s time to retreat.
They’ve finally arrived.
Elder,
we have come.
Quick,
shatter the rune!
Aye!
Hua She Wang
Nan She
Hei Du
Kui Xing
Elder!
Elder,
are you alright?
I’m alright.
Chase!
Aye!
Fly straight ahead for one and a half more hours
and then you’ll leave the desert.
Not good,
Gu He’s party is chasing after you!
That fast?
Found him!
These fellows,
aren’t they a bit too persistent?
Sir,
I am Jia Ma Empire’s Gu He.
As long as you hand over the Heavenly Flame,
I, Gu He will definitely not wrong you!
Giving it to you would be foolish.
The other side’s Fight Emperor is catching up.
Go!
I cannot let them take away the Heavenly Flame.
Absolutely not.
Stinky brat, don’t act tough.
The other side has the numbers advantage;
let Teacher take over.
Teacher,
I’m counting on you then.
Rest assured, stinky brat.
Such speed,
could it be that the other party is a Fight Emperor?
Chase.
I’d like to know
just where this Fight Emperor is from.
Sect Leader Yun,
you came at the right time.
Quickly stop that fellow.
I’ll chase him.
You should quickly leave the Tager Desert;
let us reconvene at Rock City.
If I am able to catch up to that person,
I will bring back the Heavenly Flame.
Why should we go separately?
The Snake People’s Eight Great Leaders have already chased us here;
if I keep protecting you all,
I should be able to safely escort you out of the desert.
However,
I’m afraid the Heavenly Flame...
Alright,
I understand.
I leave the Heavenly Flame to Sect Leader Yun.
Let’s go.
The Fight Emperor and Gu He have separated.
The Fight Emperor went this way.
Let’s split up.
Yue Mei,
you lead Mo Basi, Hei Du
to hunt down Gu He’s party of three.
Everyone else, come with me
to chase down the Fight Emperor!
Elder Yin Shi,
with us five joining hands,
the Five Snake Poison Killing Seal
will make this Fight Emperor
pay a price!
Go!
Before the Fight Emperor escapes from the desert,
we must stop them!
Five hundred meters distance and I can attack;
still off by a little.
It’s that Fight Emperor.
Stinky brat,
it looks to me that this Fight Emperor may bear some goodwill towards you.
How about
try seeing if they’ll let you off?
Last time, perhaps they only acted out of compassion.
The allure of the Heavenly Flame
could even make a Fight Emperor go crazy.
Careful!
Cyclone Wall!
Stop!
This move is too vicious!
Hand over the Heavenly Flame.
No matter where you are from,
offending a Tier 6 Alchemist,
Pill-King Gu He,
is not a very wise decision.
I’ll fight them.
Xiao Yan, don’t!
Vacuum Palm!
If I don’t run now, when can I?
Four Sided Wind Wall!
How to get out of this?
Sir,
my patience is limited.
You have already nearly crossed my limit.
Teacher,
I can’t willingly hand over the Heavenly Flame.
Without fighting,
I couldn’t excuse myself.
Your favor of saving my life in the desert,
this little one will never forget.
But the Heavenly Flame is too important to me;
please forgive me.
How is it him?
Didn’t I let you go back?
Yet you’re still screwing around in the desert.
I came to the desert for the very reason of looking for Heavenly Flame.
Why should I leave?
I won’t let go of the Heavenly Flame easily.
Get lost.
Get lost now!
Take the Heavenly Flame and quickly leave.
Just pretend that I wasn’t able to catch up to you today.
Yun Zhi,
is that you?
The tracking snake detected
that a Fight Emperor recently passed through here.
Chase!
I was still recognized by you.
Yun Zhi!
So that masked Fight Emperor turned out to be you.
It was me.
You’ve advanced to Fight Master.
Just got lucky.
Right,
why were you with Gu He?
I once owed him a favor.
He wanted to come to the desert to look for Heavenly Flame
and had me join along.
Heavenly Flame.
Then if you don’t bring back the Heavenly Flame,
wouldn’t he blame you?
Perhaps.
However,
my duty is only to protect his safety.
He’s taken you for a mysterious Fight Emperor practitioner,
so he should understand,
to snatch away the Heavenly Flame from a Fight Emperor’s hands,
just how difficult it is.
This Heavenly Flame is too important to me.
I’ve been following it for more than half a year,
only finally getting a hold of it now.
However,
what are you doing with the Heavenly Flame?
With your current strength,
if you made the slightest contact with this thing,
not even your bones would remain.
That’s probably true.
But I need it.
Have you always been training alone?
Pretty much.
Your training talent is quite good.
However, the path of cultivation is unusually dangerous.
Say,
if you wouldn’t mind,
I can recommend a place;
there,
you can receive the best conditions for training.
What place?
Misty Cloud Sect.
Misty Cloud Sect has extremely great power in the Jia Ma Empire.
I have an old relationship with it;
if you are willing,
I can...
What’s wrong?
Places like Misty Cloud Sect,
a little nobody like me
would only be asking for humiliation.
Misty Cloud Sect isn’t as intolerable as you think;
why are you belittling yourself?
With your training talent,
at Misty Cloud Sect
you’d be able to directly obtain the most suitable Qi Method and Fight Techniques.
Don’t say any more.
I have urgent business.
Farewell.
If there’s a chance in the future, we’ll meet again.
If you don’t want to see me,
then so be it.
Yao Yan,
you bear enmity towards Misty Cloud Sect?
I don’t want to keep talking about some shitty Misty Cloud Sect.
Relying on myself,
I can also become strong.
Fine,
let’s not mention the Misty Cloud Sect.
However,
I remember you said you were an alchemist;
could it be
that you also want to swallow the Heavenly Flame to become stronger?
I—
I...
That’s right.
I want to swallow the Heavenly Flame.
This is the only way for me to increase my strength.
Yao Yan,
we all saw how Queen Medusa met her demise.
Even a peak Fight Emperor like her died because of it.
I control my own fate, not the heavens.
In order to become strong,
why should I fear death?
Yun Zhi,
step aside.
I cannot allow you to get yourself killed.
Give the Heavenly Flame back to me!
You don’t have to take such a big risk.
Yun Zhi,
don’t force me to act against you!
Give up the Heavenly Flame;
leave with me now.
I will definitely let you become strong.
Give the Heavenly Flame to me!
Yao Yan,
promise me!
Don’t risk swallowing the Heavenly Flame!
Only by becoming strong
can I wash away past shame,
can I protect the people I care about.
Swallowing the Heavenly Flame
is my only hope for becoming strong.
That time in the Magical Beast Mountain Range,
I haven’t forgotten a single day.
Your favor of saving my life,
if there’s an opportunity someday,
I will definitely repay it.
Promise me,
please don’t risk swallowing the Heavenly Flame.
If I were to fail,
please forget about me.
Sorry.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Have you thought about ♪
♪ After crossing this desert ♪
♪ Just what lies ahead ♪
♪ Shall I fall here ♪
♪ Or firmly grasp onto fate’s ♪
♪ pulse ♪
♪ He once ♪
♪ loved ♪
♪ hated ♪
♪ suffered ♪
♪ until seeing that flame in the distance ♪
♪ Perhaps this ♪
♪ is ruinous ♪
♪ is excessive ♪
♪ is wrong ♪
♪ Yet still unafraid ♪
♪ to burn ♪
♪ Disregard that unbounded universe ♪
♪ Engage in a fight ♪
♪ Who can resist the wave splitting flame ♪
♪ Don’t speak of this endless dangerous threshold ♪
♪ Reject the climb ♪
♪ He intends to ride the wind ♪
♪ straight through ♪
♪ the heavens ♪
Preview