♪ Far off into the expanse of yellow sand ♪
♪ Comes great longing for a parted person ♪
♪ Moonlight like water, clouds like smoke ♪
♪ When did it once shine down ♪
♪ Afraid of mortal greed abiding ♪
♪ Can’t help answer your thousand words with ten thousand of mine ♪
♪ Back then a farewell, now meeting again ♪
♪ Lingering quietly grows from the fingertips ♪
♪ Even if your ears, nose, brows, eyes can’t be forgotten ♪
♪ Yet still wait for the two of us to have debts never more ♪
♪ Gathering orchids on an empty mountain ♪
♪ Searching for butterflies over the sea ♪
♪ Too much love and hate ultimately precludes fulfillment ♪
♪ Thrilling experiences rush by ♪
♪ Endlessly distant heaven and earth ♪
♪ Drooping eyes are all in the past ♪
♪ Lonely when you go ♪
♪ Yet dreams are indistinct when you return ♪
♪ Perhaps this love may not be as wished ♪
♪ Countless feelings overwhelm ♪
♪ Heart is shaken while still young ♪
♪ Asking who can, by whom, ♪
♪ be exempt ♪
Battle Through The Heavens - Season 3
Recap
Even if I die,
I will make you merge with the Flame Mantra!
This is Teacher’s only hope for resurrection!
Congratulations, Xiao Yan.
You’ve successfully proven that this Flame Mantra
really can swallow Heavenly Flame.
Its potential
is indeed limitless.
And your potential
is also limitless.
I really did it!
Teacher,
let’s go find Hai Bodong!
This stinky brat.
Episode 9
Just what secrets does this map possess?
Hai Bodong
Old Hai.
Little fellow,
you’ve finally returned.
You’ve really made me wait.
Have you brought back..?
This is the Sand Datura.
This thing was far too difficult to look for.
Within the Snake People Shrine,
I was only lucky to find one just now.
I have really troubled you.
Old Hai,
I’ve already brought back the goods for you.
That map fragment,
shouldn’t you give it to me first?
What we agreed upon back then
was that after you refine and give me the seal breaking pill,
I would give you the map fragment.
Moreover, in the future,
I can be considered to owe you a favor.
I hope that Old Hai,
after receiving the pill,
will keep your word.
Personally,
although I’m good-tempered,
what I hate most is being played for a fool.
Let’s go.
This place is underneath the desert,
a secret space I formed using an ice seal.
No matter how great the disturbance inside,
the outer world won’t know a thing.
Pretty sturdy.
Little fellow,
the recipe and ingredients needed to refine the Breaking Adversity Pill
are all here.
Old Hai,
things like refining medicinal pills
always have a chance of failure.
Refining a Tier 6 pill,
although I have some confidence,
I can’t make any guarantees.
If refinement fails in the end,
this liability...
Rest assured.
Alchemists should not be liable,
I understand this principle.
During refinement,
I require absolute quiet;
I cannot allow anyone to disturb me.
That includes you yourself, Old Hai.
I will stand guard outside the door.
There will definitely not be anyone who would dare barge inside.
I leave everything to you.
Teacher,
nothing’s wrong with this place, right?
En.
I checked;
that fellow hasn’t set up any tricks here.
Breaking Adversity Pill.
Tier 6 pill.
It has the unique effect of breaking most kinds of seals.
Really quite a good thing.
Teacher,
time to get started.
I knew you would make these old bones of mine do hard labor.
I’d like to do things myself,
but with what little alchemy ability I have,
trying to refine a Tier 6 medicinal pill
is just delusional.
While Teacher is refining the pill later,
you should diligently observe.
This will be of great benefit to your improvement in alchemy.
Understood, Teacher.
Impressive cauldron.
A medicinal cauldron
is the most important thing an alchemist possesses.
A good cauldron
can greatly increase the success rate of pill refinement.
This cauldron of mine
is known as
“Black Demon.”
Black Demon?
Sure is domineering.
I’m about to begin.
Xiao Yan,
look carefully.
Wafting medicinal fragrance...
the pill is about to form!
Teacher,
what is this?
A special ice body coagulated by the Bone Chilling Flame.
Once mixed into the pill and swallowed by someone,
it will slip into their body.
Normally, it will not have the slightest unusual activity.
However,
if activated by my Heavenly Flame,
these ice bodies will swiftly transform into extremely destructive Bone Chilling Flame.
You should never let down your guard.
This is only a self-defense measure of alchemists.
Old people really are more shrewd.
Pill, arise!
This is a Tier 6 medicinal pill’s power?
Hold up,
it’s like this pill developed a spirit of its own!
The product doesn’t look bad.
Stinky brat,
catch.
Inside this,
there’s actually some mystical force.
This is probably the element that breaks the seal.
Could it have failed?
Looks like I was reckless;
although I unable to fully see through that fellow’s strength,
he is too young, after all.
I’ll go take a look.
Little fellow,
did it succeed?
Just got lucky,
somehow managed to succeed.
This is the Breaking Adversity Pill?
Little fellow really does hide his abilities deeply.
Old Hai,
I’ve already refined the pill for you.
Where is the map fragment?
Little fellow,
after I confirm that this pill is the Breaking Adversity Pill,
I will use both hands to offer the map fragment to you.
Let me remind you,
if you use the pill,
but due to the recipe you provided
the seal still isn’t broken,
would you place the blame on me?
I traveled thousands of miles in the desert,
taking the risk of getting killed by Queen Medusa
in order to help you find Sand Datura,
and even expended all effort to refine a medicinal pill.
All this you’ve ignored.
Old Hai,
I’ve done so much
in exchange for nothing but a map fragment
and a Fight Emperor’s verbal promise.
You tell me,
did I lose,
or did I gain?
Stinky brat,
you’ve gotten better and better at talking.
Teacher,
when dealing with this kind of person,
you have to strike first.
Little fellow,
rest assured.
As long as this Breaking Adversity Pill can produce the smallest effect,
I won’t go back on my word.
Do as you like then.
Let me caution Old Hai,
this is the last time I’m capitulating.
Many thanks for your understanding.
I will now take the Breaking Adversity Pill.
Teacher,
this old fellow won’t go back on us, right?
No need to worry.
As long as he takes the Breaking Adversity Pill,
he won’t be able to pose a threat to you.
Teacher,
he swallowed it.
The seal
is about to break.
This damned seal has finally disappeared.
I am now a Fight Emperor once again!
Old Hai,
this stance of yours,
you’re not going to kill the donkey after it drove the mill, right?
This kid, being able to refine a Tier 6 pill at such a young age.
Such geniuses you can only befriend;
cannot become enemies with them.
Little brother Xiao Yan,
how could I forget the help you provided me?
That kind of ungrateful action,
the old me will not do.
I sincerely apologize,
just then was because I suddenly recovered my strength
and found it difficult to control my Dou Qi for a time.
I’ve startled you.
I originally also wanted to experience
the true strength of Ice Emperor, who once dominated the Jia Ma Empire.
Pity.
Little brother Xiao Yan is joking.
According to the agreement,
this map fragment is yours.
There is tremendous spiritual energy within;
it is indeed that map fragment.
Then I express many thanks to Old Hai.
Little brother Xiao Yan,
you seem to be very interested in the map.
However,
this should only be one of many map fragments.
I wonder if you can tell me
that after gathering the fragments,
what will be revealed.
Honestly,
I only encountered this kind of map fragment at an auction once.
Exactly what they are hiding,
I am also unsure.
Shit,
he’s anticipating all of my attack patterns.
Better decide this quickly.
Triple Lightning
Arc Dance!
Where’d he go?
This guy is too strong.
Second Brother is no match for him.
Mo Ran
Trash is trash.
This pitiful strength
yet trying to be my opponent?
Second Company Leader!
Bastard!
Another one seeking death.
Let me give you brothers a ride
Little Yan!
Your life,
I’m taking it today!
Second Company Leader.
Sorry, Big Brother.
I’ve come late.
You all carefully tend to your wounds.
That guy,
let me handle him.
This guy is called Mo Ran.
A One-star Fight Grandmaster Luo Bu found from who knows where.
His Qi Method is of the Earth affinity
which is well suited to drawn out fights.
One-star Fight Grandmaster.
Teacher,
you don’t need to intervene this time.
I want to take this man’s life myself.
En.
Kid,
no matter who you are,
I’d advise not setting yourself on fire.
Just this Desert Metal Mercenary Company
isn’t anywhere close to being our enemy.
Now,
kneel on the ground and beg for mercy.
I might even forgive you!
Enough with the crap!
This is all you’ve got?
You actually dare to bluff in front of me?
Too weak.
This power is too weak!
Kid,
now you know where meddling gets you, eh?
Obediently leave your life behind.
Little Yan!
Quiet.
Big Brother,
Little Yan, he—
his opponent is a Fight Grandmaster!
Don’t forget,
Little Yan without that strange black ruler
is actually his strongest state.
You
and this Desert Metal Mercenary Company bunch of fools,
I will have all of you disappear today!
After completing the Clan Head’s orders,
I can leave this godforsaken place.
Yan City’s Mo Clan.
You brat,
you actually know of the Mo Clan?
This is—
Kid.
This is the Dou Qi armor that Fight Grandmasters can agglomerate.
Unfortunately it hasn’t been long since I entered Fight Grandmaster;
otherwise Dou Qi armor could cover my entire body.
Even so,
your attack power
cannot possibly break it!
Dou Qi armor?
No wonder.
I don’t believe
that your turtle shell can’t be broken.
Little shit,
getting a taste of Dou Qi armor
and dying in my hands
wouldn’t be bad!
This—
This is—
Not bad,
Xiao Yan.
Relying on yourself,
believing in your own strength.
That is the conviction held by strong practitioners.
The current you
is on the way to becoming a strong practitioner.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Have you thought about ♪
♪ After crossing this desert ♪
♪ Just what lies ahead ♪
♪ Shall I fall here ♪
♪ Or firmly grasp onto fate’s ♪
♪ pulse ♪
♪ He once ♪
♪ loved ♪
♪ hated ♪
♪ suffered ♪
♪ until seeing that flame in the distance ♪
♪ Perhaps this ♪
♪ is ruinous ♪
♪ is excessive ♪
♪ is wrong ♪
♪ Yet still unafraid ♪
♪ to burn ♪
♪ Disregard that unbounded universe ♪
♪ Engage in a fight ♪
♪ Who can resist the wave splitting flame ♪
♪ Don’t speak of this endless dangerous threshold ♪
♪ Reject the climb ♪
♪ He intends to ride the wind ♪
♪ straight through ♪
♪ the heavens ♪
Preview