♪ Far off into the expanse of yellow sand ♪
♪ Comes great longing for a parted person ♪
♪ Moonlight like water, clouds like smoke ♪
♪ When did it once shine down ♪
♪ Afraid of mortal greed abiding ♪
♪ Can’t help answer your thousand words with ten thousand of mine ♪
♪ Back then a farewell, now meeting again ♪
♪ Lingering quietly grows from the fingertips ♪
♪ Even if your ears, nose, brows, eyes can’t be forgotten ♪
♪ Yet still wait for the two of us to have debts never more ♪
♪ Gathering orchids on an empty mountain ♪
♪ Searching for butterflies over the sea ♪
♪ Too much love and hate ultimately precludes fulfillment ♪
♪ Thrilling experiences rush by ♪
♪ Endlessly distant heaven and earth ♪
♪ Drooping eyes are all in the past ♪
♪ Lonely when you go ♪
♪ Yet dreams are indistinct when you return ♪
♪ Perhaps this love may not be as wished ♪
♪ Countless feelings overwhelm ♪
♪ Heart is shaken while still young ♪
♪ Asking who can, by whom, ♪
♪ be exempt ♪
Battle Through The Heavens - Season 3
Recap
Could we have gotten lost?
There’s no mistake.
I finally feel like I’m alive again.
I’m leaving it to you.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Only a fool would stay and wait to die.
Episode 2
Fight Emperor?
Thank you, Your Honor,
for saving my life.
The desert will no longer be peaceful.
You should quickly leave this place.
I also accidentally wound up in the desert.
Then I bid farewell.
Thank heavens,
I’m finally freed from that crazy Snake woman.
Trying to run?
Snake Summoning Technique!
You dare provoke me?
Wait!
Sect Leader Yun,
this is the Snake People’s heartland.
Please focus on the primary mission.
Leave quickly.
Then, many thanks.
Everyone,
we’ll meet again, if it’s fated.
Sect Leader Yun is chivalrous.
Just then was a misunderstanding.
Please do not mind.
I am Gu He;
I would like to request to meet the noble Queen Medusa.
News of this group of human practitioners should be reported
to the Queen as soon as possible.
Trying to meet the Queen, her Majesty.
Our Snake People race and you humans
have long feuded,
dying each other in blood.
What is there to discuss?
If you are tactful,
leave immediately.
Or else, once our Eight Great Leaders gather,
your team of Jia Ma Empire’s strong practitioners
is going to shrink significantly, I’m afraid.
Don’t be arrogant!
Teacher,
you’ve finally come out.
What happened just then,
I’m aware of it all.
Do you know who the man that arrived at the end
is?
Pill-King Gu He.
Didn’t expect him to come as well.
Xiao Yan,
Teacher guesses
that Gu He has also come for the Heavenly Flame.
Fucking hell,
the Queen wants to swallow the Heavenly Flame,
now there’s also a Pill-King trying to steal the Heavenly Flame too,
and he brought so many helpers...
Dummy!
Teacher,
I get it now!
Gu He, and the Queen,
will eventually, because of the Heavenly Flame,
directly clash.
While we’ll take the opportunity to fish in troubled waters
and snatch the Heavenly Flame.
Finally your mind has woken up.
Looking at Hai Bodong’s map,
passing through the sandstorm area up ahead
is the fastest way to reach the Shrine.
Teacher,
let’s go.
Yan Shi
Old He,
how about directly acting to capture her;
let’s stop wasting time.
If we arrive late,
the thing you want might be gone.
And letting her go
would expose our movements.
This mission’s difficulty
would increase greatly.
Since madam is not willing to cooperate,
then don’t blame us for bullying with a numbers advantage.
Feng Li
Yan Shi,
Feng Li,
please.
Jia Ma Empire’s Ten Strong,
Lion King Yan Shi,
Windrunner Feng Li.
You actually recognize me.
I’m taking your life!
Break for me!
Yan Shi,
you talk too much.
My face...
I will kill you all!
Now’s a good time.
Snake Technique:
Split!
She escaped.
We’ll immediately set off
to meet Queen Medusa.
It's so heavily guarded.
Teacher,
we’ve got to figure out a way to sneak in.
I, Hua She, in the name of the Queen
have carefully handpicked, from the Eight Great Tribes,
you all to be the lead dancers.
This is your extremely great fortune, mind you.
Hua She Er
In a while,
you’d better give me a good showing at the Sacrificial Ceremony,
leading all of the Snake People in dancing well
to satisfy Her Majesty The Queen and the Snake Spirit.
But of course,
Marshal Hua.
Rest assured,
our waists
are the most supple.
Looks like the Snake Form Pill I refined
has a pretty good effect.
Turns out Teacher, while in the Magical Beast Mountain Range,
had refined this kind of useful thing.
Teacher,
let’s go.
Now,
it’s about time for me to decide.
Even if it is like a moth drawn to flame,
I am fully committed.
Your Majesty The Queen!
Your Majesty The Queen.
Jia Ma Empire’s Gu He has brought a group of human fighters
to attack my race.
Subordinate used a Secret Technique, burning essence blood,
in order to desperately escape.
Pill-King Gu He.
He certainly knows how to pick a day.
Among Gu He’s contingent,
there is also a human Fight Emperor.
Do you know which Fight Emperor they are?
Subordinate does not know.
The Fight Emperor was always masked.
Perhaps
they do not want people to know their identity.
Your Majesty The Queen.
Yin Shi
Gu He’s group
will likely reach the Shrine very soon.
I am worried they will disturb the ceremony.
Elder,
pass down the order.
Once the sun rises to the highest point,
immediately begin the Sacrificial Ceremony.
Yes,
Queen.
Gu He has come
simply because he wants the Heavenly Flame.
Yue Mei,
have these four flames placed in the Shrine’s four corners.
Let him slowly search.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Queen,
Subordinate has another important matter
to report to you.
The human boy who barged into the holy pool,
although he is merely a little Fight Master,
he actually possesses the ability to instantly rise in strength to a Fight Emperor.
This ability is very rare.
Yue Mei originally planned to capture and study him;
unfortunately, he escaped.
Such an ability exists?
You may go back down.
Yes.
Nice moves,
there are even Snake People fancying you!
Teacher, be more serious!
Where is the Heavenly Flame?
The tallest building in front on the right
contains a Heavenly Flame’s aura inside.
Luckily we got here before the Queen’s evolution.
Teacher,
let’s go.
It’s heavily guarded,
forcefully charging in would alert them.
Gotta think of a way to sneak inside.
The Heavenly Flame’s aura is getting closer.
That crazy Snake woman?
Look at what’s in that Snake woman’s hands.
The Heavenly Flame is in that box.
Heavenly Flame?
Something’s wrong,
this Heavenly Flame is fake.
Shit.
Halt!
Turn around!
Capture that person!
Halt!
Move aside!
Do not forget the Queen’s instructions;
it is only a small insect.
Our own Snake Guards will take care of it.
Yes, Elder.
Halt!
Don’t run!
Move aside!
Out of the way!
Move!
Halt!
You’d better halt!
Quick!
Halt!
Don’t run!
Where?
Capture them!
They ran in that direction!
Chase! Go!
Capture him!
Don’t run!
Halt!
Exploding Steps!
That punch was pretty accurate.
Stop running!
Don’t run!
Halt!
Go look over there.
Yes!
Finally shook them off.
Strange,
besides the fake Heavenly Flame just then,
the Shrine does not have any other traces of a Heavenly Flame.
Let me try using the Green Lotus Pedestal;
it has the same origin as the Green Lotus Heavenly Flame.
Just where is the Heavenly Flame?
The auspicious hour has come!
May the Snake Spirit bless my people!
It found the Heavenly Flame!
Should be underneath that.
But the aura has disappeared again.
Xiao Yan,
let’s find an opportunity to enter.
Teacher,
let’s quickly go.
Stinky little brat,
you’re pretty quick!
Can’t let her discover me.
There’s high security.
The guards also don’t have openings.
It succeeded!
Girls,
begin the dance!
Let us pray,
convey to the Snake Spirit our piety
to give blessings to the Queen.
Teacher,
what now?
Join the prayer.
Look!
What is that?
It’s Gu He’s group.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Have you thought about ♪
♪ After crossing this desert ♪
♪ Just what lies ahead ♪
♪ Shall I fall here ♪
♪ Or firmly grasp onto fate’s ♪
♪ pulse ♪
♪ He once ♪
♪ loved ♪
♪ hated ♪
♪ suffered ♪
♪ until seeing that flame in the distance ♪
♪ Perhaps this ♪
♪ is ruinous ♪
♪ is excessive ♪
♪ is wrong ♪
♪ Yet still unafraid ♪
♪ to burn ♪
♪ Disregard that unbounded universe ♪
♪ Engage in a fight ♪
♪ Who can resist the wave splitting flame ♪
♪ Don’t speak of this endless dangerous threshold ♪
♪ Reject the climb ♪
♪ He intends to ride the wind ♪
♪ straight through ♪
♪ the heavens ♪
Preview