♪ Far off into the expanse of yellow sand ♪
♪ Comes great longing for a parted person ♪
♪ Moonlight like water, clouds like smoke ♪
♪ When did it once shine down ♪
♪ Afraid of mortal greed abiding ♪
♪ Can’t help answer your thousand words with ten thousand of mine ♪
♪ Back then a farewell, now meeting again ♪
♪ Lingering quietly grows from the fingertips ♪
♪ Even if your ears, nose, brows, eyes can’t be forgotten ♪
♪ Yet still wait for the two of us to have debts never more ♪
♪ Gathering orchids on an empty mountain ♪
♪ Searching for butterflies over the sea ♪
♪ Too much love and hate ultimately precludes fulfillment ♪
♪ Thrilling experiences rush by ♪
♪ Endlessly distant heaven and earth ♪
♪ Drooping eyes are all in the past ♪
♪ Lonely when you go ♪
♪ Yet dreams are indistinct when you return ♪
♪ Perhaps this love may not be as wished ♪
♪ Countless feelings overwhelm ♪
♪ Heart is shaken while still young ♪
♪ Asking who can, by whom, ♪
♪ be exempt ♪
Battle Through The Heavens - Season 3
Episode 1
Queen Medusa,
enduring untold hardships,
finally obtained the Green Lotus Core Flame.
In order to become stronger and win the Three Year Agreement,
Xiao Yan swore to seize the Heavenly Flame.
A third force
was also aiming
to obtain the Heavenly Flame at all costs.
The ripples triggered by this dispute
would cause the Tager Desert
to be peaceful no longer.
It’s already been two months since we entered the Tager Desert.
Teacher,
could we have gotten lost?
There’s no mistake.
I hate the desert!
Up ahead
is the Snake People Shrine.
What?
We’ve almost reached the Shrine!
Shrine?
Heavenly Flame,
I’m coming for you!
Teacher, let’s hurry up!
What the hell?
Stinky little rascal,
look at yourself.
Let’s search for an oasis to replenish water.
Then let’s hurry up, Teacher.
I’m nearly dying of thirst.
Teacher,
that’s not another mirage, right?
It’s an oasis.
Stinky brat,
tonight
we’ll rest there.
Teacher,
I’m going to drink my fill of water!
Let’s go!
About time we found an oasis in this forsaken desert,
I finally feel like I’m alive again.
This is
a Snake Person statue?
Xiao Yan,
this oasis
is a little strange.
Teacher,
aren’t you overthinking?
It’s only a few stone statues.
Also,
don’t we have you, Teacher?
What’s there to be afraid of?
You stinky little rascal,
your flattery is nothing but sweet talk.
The water source is just up ahead!
Teacher,
after our thirst is quenched,
let’s immediately go to the Shrine to find the Heavenly Flame!
Someone’s up ahead.
Hide.
A woman?
Medusa
Teacher,
why’d you hit me?
us peeping from here
isn’t very good, huh...
Stinky brat,
this female Snake Person is dancing.
Dancing?
No wonder.
It looks quite nice.
I feel like
I’ve seen this dance somewhere.
This aura...
It’s Queen Medusa!
Good thing I isolated your aura in time;
otherwise, we would’ve been discovered.
That scared me to death.
It really is stumbling upon something hard to find.
Let’s quickly find ways to snatch the Heavenly Flame.
However,
the surroundings do not contain a Heavenly Flame’s aura.
Perhaps she isn’t carrying the Heavenly Flame with her.
Teacher,
don’t worry so much.
Secretly follow this Queen,
and we’ll definitely find the Heavenly Flame.
Actually summoning a Snake Spirit.
This dance...
Dance of Prayer?
According to legend, the Queen of the Snake People
possesses a marvelous evolution art.
Before evolving,
she must call upon the ancestor Snake Spirit’s blessing
through the Dance of Prayer in a holy pool.
This evolution art is very dangerous.
If it succeeds, she will promote to Fight Ancestor.
If it fails, even her soul would be scattered.
Oh boy,
one could even advance to Fight Ancestor in this way.
Do you know what the most important thing is for this evolution?
It’s Heavenly Flame.
Just like you,
she also needs to swallow a Heavenly Flame to evolve.
Teacher,
before the Queen swallows the Heavenly Flame,
we must snatch it.
Keep an eye on her.
She will guide us to the Heavenly Flame.
She discovered me.
Let’s retreat.
Little insect.
Yue Mei
Your Majesty.
Yue Mei.
Subordinate is here.
I’m leaving it to you.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Daring to spy on the Queen?
Then suffer death.
Only a fool would stay and wait to die.
So many snakes,
they’re chasing me, too.
Die, all of you!
Teacher,
can’t you give me a heads up earlier
so I can prepare before getting possessed?
Xiao Yan,
the Queen has disappeared.
She’s really gone.
Teacher,
where did the Queen go?
Her aura has vanished.
Fight Emperor.
Stinky brat,
focus.
This sister,
there are no grudges between us,
must we fight right away?
Trespassing on my people’s holy pool,
Fight Emperor sir,
would you say this is resentment or a grudge?
Move aside!
Got no time to play with you.
Play?
Teacher,
what technique is this?
This is Energy Correspondence Technique.
Snake People Fight Kings
can extract the spirits of Magical Beasts
and preserve their strength
for driving them.
Snake Technique:
Rampage!
Fight Emperor sir,
When we Snake People face enemies,
we never rest until we die!
Teacher,
we can’t waste any more time.
Get rid of her.
Teacher?
Xiao Yan,
there is a Fight Emperor with very strong perception approaching.
I need to withdraw for now.
Suffer death!
I’m just a Two-star Fight Master,
I can’t defeat her!
Retreat!
His strength decreased so drastically.
An interesting ability.
Looks like I should capture him alive,
then properly interrogate him after returning.
Gu He
It won’t be much longer
until we reach the Snake People Shrine.
There is a Fight Emperor’s aura up ahead.
Fight Emperor?
Could it be Queen Medusa?
The aura is intermittent;
I’m unable to determine yet.
This place is the Snake People’s heartland;
it’s very possible that it’s her.
Let’s go.
Haunting me like a ghost.
This won’t do,
I need to quickly get away.
Damn it,
in this sky, there’s no way to hide.
There’s something!
Let’s see where you run.
Still chasing me?
The game is starting.
Don’t let me easily find you~
Your secrets,
tell them to Sister.
Se-
Tell Sister.
Secrets...
Enchantment!
Octane Blast!
Not bad, your power.
Vacuum Palm!
Since I can’t run,
I might as well fight!
I’m going all out.
Is this all you’ve got?
To deal with you,
it’s enough!
Can’t be entangled any longer.
Damn it,
I will kill you!
Stinky little brat,
I’m going to skin you alive!
You are the first person to dare mar my face!
Is this
the difference between classes?
Weren’t you pretty powerful just a moment ago?
Today
am I going to die here?
You—
Who are you?
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Have you thought about ♪
♪ After crossing this desert ♪
♪ Just what lies ahead ♪
♪ Shall I fall here ♪
♪ Or firmly grasp onto fate’s ♪
♪ pulse ♪
♪ He once ♪
♪ loved ♪
♪ hated ♪
♪ suffered ♪
♪ until seeing that flame in the distance ♪
♪ Perhaps this ♪
♪ is ruinous ♪
♪ is excessive ♪
♪ is wrong ♪
♪ Yet still unafraid ♪
♪ to burn ♪
♪ Disregard that unbounded universe ♪
♪ Engage in a fight ♪
♪ Who can resist the wave splitting flame ♪
♪ Don’t speak of this endless dangerous threshold ♪
♪ Reject the climb ♪
♪ He intends to ride the wind ♪
♪ straight through ♪
♪ the heavens ♪
Preview