♪ Far off into the expanse of yellow sand ♪
♪ Comes great longing for a parted person ♪
♪ Moonlight like water, clouds like smoke ♪
♪ When did it once shine down ♪
♪ Afraid of mortal greed abiding ♪
♪ Can’t help answer your thousand words with ten thousand of mine ♪
♪ Back then a farewell, now meeting again ♪
♪ Lingering quietly grows from the fingertips ♪
♪ Even if your ears, nose, brows, eyes can’t be forgotten ♪
♪ Yet still wait for the two of us to have debts never more ♪
♪ Gathering orchids on an empty mountain ♪
♪ Searching for butterflies over the sea ♪
♪ Too much love and hate ultimately precludes fulfillment ♪
♪ Thrilling experiences rush by ♪
♪ Endlessly distant heaven and earth ♪
♪ Drooping eyes are all in the past ♪
♪ Lonely when you go ♪
♪ Yet dreams are indistinct when you return ♪
♪ Perhaps this love may not be as wished ♪
♪ Countless feelings overwhelm ♪
♪ Heart is shaken while still young ♪
♪ Asking who can, by whom, ♪
♪ be exempt ♪
Battle Through The Heavens - Season 3
Recap
Cannot hesitate any longer.
Even if swallowing the Heavenly Flame fails
and I sacrifice my body for this,
I will be worthy as the Queen of the Snake People.
Episode 5
Queen Medusa has deployed an energy barrier beneath this altar.
However,
just now I sensed the Heavenly Flame’s aura.
All previous things have been traps set by this woman.
She is underneath the altar,
offering her body as sacrifice.
In the end,
the evolution failed.
She has fallen.
Queen!
Why must our Snake People experience such great hardship?
A thousand years!
We have paid the price of a thousand years!
Something’s wrong.
Sect Leader Yun.
Natural energy has suddenly begun to erupt.
This natural anomaly...
Could it be..?
Queen Medusa!
Perhaps
she did not actually fail
and is saving her last remaining energy
to undergo nirvanic rebirth.
It’s too dangerous here;
let’s leave.
Withdraw!
The Queen did not fail!
This place is far too treacherous.
They withdrew?
We cannot allow them to disturb the Queen!
Keep a close eye on them.
Go!
Aye.
The energy barrier can’t hold up for much longer.
Gosh, what happened?
Still alive,
not good!
Xiao Yan, move now!
Before Queen Medusa regains consciousness,
snatch the Heavenly Flame!
She’s still alive?
Xiao Yan.
I— I’m fine.
Oh no!
Medusa’s evolution has triggered a natural energy backlash.
The power of natural energy should not be underestimated;
all prohibitions in this space have been shattered by it.
If we keep stalling,
Xiao Yan and I
will die here!
Teacher,
Teacher!
Are you alright?
Don’t move.
It’s too dangerous here.
Teacher,
you don’t need to protect me.
The Heavenly Flame is over there.
Natural energy doesn’t dare approach the Heavenly Flame.
Xiao Yan,
let’s quickly go there.
Use this opportunity to rush over,
collect the Heavenly Flame!
Okay.
Teacher, let’s go!
That was close.
Exploding Steps!
My life was nearly going to be ended here.
An aura has appeared within the snake’s body once again.
Her evolution succeeded?
Should be the case.
These insurgent natural energies
are the last ordeal in her move towards Fight Ancestor.
Teacher,
we have to hurry,
there’s no time left.
After her evolution succeeds,
I’m afraid we would...
The Heavenly Flame has been provoked!
The Heavenly Flame is about to explode;
take out the Green Lotus Pedestal now!
Yes!
I remember it’s inside...
Your Majesty The Queen!
Your Majesty The Queen.
This— what the hell is this?
Green Lotus Core Flame.
You really were inside.
This energy...
No... No!
Queen!
A generation of strong practitioners,
gone like ash and smoke.
This fire
was sparked from the irritated Heavenly Flame.
Spiritual Strength cannot penetrate through it;
I am unable to detect the situation inside.
Sect Leader Yun,
once the flames have weakened,
let us immediately enter.
The current Snake People
are nothing to be afraid of.
If all Eight Great Tribe Leaders were to arrive,
even I
would find it troublesome.
Alright then,
I promise
that before they reach here,
whether we find the Heavenly Flame or not,
we will still leave.
It failed.
Such courage
is enough to prove that she is an opponent worthy of respect.
Rest in peace,
Queen Medusa.
Wait until I recapture the Heavenly Flame;
I will also prove to the world
that for the sake of my heart’s desires
I am willing to endure the Heavenly Flame’s searing pain.
Hurry up.
Use the Green Lotus Pedestal to collect the Heavenly Flame.
What is that?
It—
It’s rushing over!
Teacher,
dodge!
Its speed is too fast...
Teacher,
what is this thing?
Xiao Yan,
are you hurt?
I’m okay, Teacher.
This was Queen Medusa’s companion spirit,
Quiet Purple Flame Serpent,
a Rank 6 Magical Beast.
Didn’t expect that this so-called evolution
would evolve the spirit,
using spiritual power to agglomerate a real body.
With enough chance,
activating the ancient beast bloodline inside the body
allows it to evolve into a beast comparable to a Fight Ancestor,
Seven-Colored Heaven Swallowing Python.
Seven-Colored Heaven Swallowing...
That—
that thing is Queen Medusa?!
Elder!
Damn it,
I’m going to kill them!
Wait.
Elder,
why?
Her Majesty The Queen has died,
I intend to avenge her!
We Snake People will definitely exact this revenge.
Among the Eight Great Leaders, there are only us three.
Even if we rushed up there, we would only die in vain.
After all of us arrive,
even a Fight Emperor would need to pay up their life!
If this thing is Queen Medusa,
why can’t I feel the slightest killing intent?
Perhaps, during the evolution process,
it was struck dumb by the lightning.
I think
she doesn’t seem
to have any killing intent.
How about
withdrawing the Bone Chilling Flame?
Alright.
Be careful.
Come, little fellow.
Compared to that arrogant Queen,
this appearance is much cuter.
Although I don’t know why your memories were lost,
at any rate, you’re alive.
This also gives me confidence in swallowing the Heavenly Flame.
Little fellow,
are you hungry?
You don’t like any of these...
I know what you want!
Try this,
Amethyst Birth Essence.
Seven-Colored Heaven Swallowing Python is a fire-type exotic beast.
It has a natural liking for things like Amethyst Essence that are filled with pure fire energy.
Kid,
are you planning to keep this little thing by your side?
Teacher,
Heaven let Queen Medusa turn into this,
an ancient beast, delivered to my doorstep.
Its potential is limitless!
If I’m able to keep it for my own use,
then it won’t be inferior to controlling a Heavenly Flame.
You are taking a gamble...
This is going to be a superb fighter in the future,
what’s wrong with gambling once?
Not to mention,
don’t I still have you, Teacher?
If she really does recover her memories
and we can’t defeat her, we’ll just run, yea?
Stinky brat,
I hope you won’t burn yourself from playing with fire.
Little fellow,
if you follow me,
there’s meat to eat.
Come over.
Success.
That’s enough, stinky brat.
Time for proper business.
Got it, Teacher.
Green Lotus Pedestal,
it’s all on you.
It succeeded!
The Green Lotus Pedestal can isolate the Heavenly Flame’s aura,
preventing outside people from discovering it.
Quickly leave.
Don’t move!
Heavenly Flame can’t be put into a storage ring.
It will burn up everything inside.
That was close.
The Heavenly Flame’s aura,
why did it disappear?
The energy fluctuations inside have already calmed.
As for that Heavenly Flame...
could it have been destroyed by Queen Medusa?
Impossible.
Although Queen Medusa’s strength is formidable,
but to destroy a Heavenly Flame,
it is still a bit lacking.
Another strong Snake Person practitioner has come.
Elder Yin Shi,
Yan Tribe’s Yan Ci has arrived.
Yan Ci
The fire has gone out.
Let’s go inside.
Let’s follow them.
Who knows if those Snake People
will play some dirty tricks again.
Human scum, hand over your lives!
Halt!
Don’t try to run!
Elder Yin Shi,
don’t let them get away!
Yan Ci,
endure for the time being.
With just the few of us,
we are still no match for a Fight Emperor.
Wait until the Southern Snake leaders arrive;
Five Snake Poison Killing Seal
will be sufficient to have this Fight Emperor remain here!
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Have you thought about ♪
♪ After crossing this desert ♪
♪ Just what lies ahead ♪
♪ Shall I fall here ♪
♪ Or firmly grasp onto fate’s ♪
♪ pulse ♪
♪ He once ♪
♪ loved ♪
♪ hated ♪
♪ suffered ♪
♪ until seeing that flame in the distance ♪
♪ Perhaps this ♪
♪ is ruinous ♪
♪ is excessive ♪
♪ is wrong ♪
♪ Yet still unafraid ♪
♪ to burn ♪
♪ Disregard that unbounded universe ♪
♪ Engage in a fight ♪
♪ Who can resist the wave splitting flame ♪
♪ Don’t speak of this endless dangerous threshold ♪
♪ Reject the climb ♪
♪ He intends to ride the wind ♪
♪ straight through ♪
♪ the heavens ♪
Preview