♪ Far off into the expanse of yellow sand ♪
♪ Comes great longing for a parted person ♪
♪ Moonlight like water, clouds like smoke ♪
♪ When did it once shine down ♪
♪ Afraid of mortal greed abiding ♪
♪ Can’t help answer your thousand words with ten thousand of mine ♪
♪ Back then a farewell, now meeting again ♪
♪ Lingering quietly grows from the fingertips ♪
♪ Even if your ears, nose, brows, eyes can’t be forgotten ♪
♪ Yet still wait for the two of us to have debts never more ♪
♪ Gathering orchids on an empty mountain ♪
♪ Searching for butterflies over the sea ♪
♪ Too much love and hate ultimately precludes fulfillment ♪
♪ Thrilling experiences rush by ♪
♪ Endlessly distant heaven and earth ♪
♪ Drooping eyes are all in the past ♪
♪ Lonely when you go ♪
♪ Yet dreams are indistinct when you return ♪
♪ Perhaps this love may not be as wished ♪
♪ Countless feelings overwhelm ♪
♪ Heart is shaken while still young ♪
♪ Asking who can, by whom, ♪
♪ be exempt ♪
Battle Through The Heavens - Season 3
Recap
Breaking Adversity Pill.
It has the unique effect of breaking most kinds of seals.
Pill, arise!
This damned seal has finally disappeared.
I am now a Fight Emperor once again!
I don’t believe
that your turtle shell can’t be broken.
Episode 10
Luo Bu
Let me go!
Little brother Xiao Yan,
I have brought the person.
Old Hai,
you’ve worked hard.
Please drink some tea.
This terrifying strength...
Little Yan,
this old sir is..?
Old Hai
is my friend.
While his temperament is a bit...
however,
he is a true strong practitioner.
Strong practitioners
will naturally have a strong practitioner’s temperament.
Otherwise, how would they show their personality?
Speak up,
where did you take Qing Lin?
Qing Lin?
Everyone saw.
You were the one who abducted Qing Lin.
Big Brother,
what exactly happened?
Two days ago,
Qing Lin went outside to purchase food
and has not returned since.
Per our investigation,
she was abducted by the Sand Mercenary Company
and the Fight Grandmaster you previously got rid of.
Qing Lin has the Flame Spirit Serpent as a protector.
How could she be abducted so easily?
At the site we investigated,
we did not discover evidence of fighting.
Qing Lin
may have been immediately knocked out and then taken away.
Big Brother,
Little Yan.
No need to guess around.
Directly asking Luo Bu will make things clear.
Speak.
Where did you take her?
I’ll talk,
I’ll talk.
It was
Yan City’s Mo Clan who did it.
That little girl called Qing Lin,
was personally kidnapped
by First Elder Mo Ran.
They
also lent us people
to help us dominate Rock Desert City,
but the condition was
that from now on,
the Desert Metal Mercenary Company
would no longer exist in this world.
What Mo Clan crap.
They’ve certainly got balls, though.
Old Hai.
I remember you previously spoke of Yan City’s Mo Clan.
What are their origins, exactly?
Mo Clan,
one of the four great clans in the northeastern region of Jia Ma Empire.
Its power,
although it cannot be compared to these titans like the Nalan Clan,
it should not be underestimated.
Mo Clan’s strongest practitioner
is the clan head, Mo Cheng.
Nickname, “Executioner Mo.”
It’s the Mo Clan Head’s carriage,
he’s returned!
Mo Clan is our Mo City’s great benefactor.
It’s our lucky day.
All thanks to Lord Mo.
I heard that today is the Mo Clan Head’s sixtieth birthday.
All of the big powers across the entire Northeast Region have come!
When Mo Cheng was young,
he once joined the Misty Cloud Sect.
Although he later returned to the Mo Clan,
he still made huge donations under the title of Misty Cloud Sect’s “External Deacon.”
Misty Cloud Sect can be considered Mo Clan’s biggest backer.
“Mo Estate”
Mo Cheng
Welcome, Clan Head.
Come on!
Careful.
Hurry up, sister!
Brother, wait for me!
The goods have already arrived;
you may look them over.
I will check them immediately.
Yes,
Clan Head.
Right,
Steward.
Tonight’s birthday banquet
will include distinguished guests from the Misty Cloud Sect.
Remember to greet them properly;
not a single thing can be remiss.
Please rest assured, Clan Head.
I have already made the suitable preparations.
Over here.
Left a little.
Up a little!
The Clan Head is here!
Clan Head.
Go ahead and do your work.
Yes.
Where’d they go?
The goods are down there.
Her protector Beast is a bit troublesome;
we could only use an energy wall cover to trap it.
Qing Lin
This...
just what is this place?
Anybody there?
Let me out!
Flame Spirit Serpent!
Flame Spirit Serpent,
your injuries are so grave.
If only Young Master was here.
He would definitely rescue us.
A Spirit Serpent protector,
looks like this half-breed is indeed not ordinary.
Release the Black Demon Serpent.
I’d like to see
whether the Triple Jade-Green Snake Flower Pupils are actually like the legends say,
able to control snake-type beasts.
As you wish,
my esteemed Clan Head.
Don’t come over!
Triple Jade-Green Snake Flower Pupils are indeed the nemesis of snake-form Magical Beasts.
A feeble half-breed
was actually able to force the Black Demon Serpent to sign a contract.
Such a rare ability
was actually found by me.
Congratulations, Clan Head.
In order to avoid future worries,
after tonight’s birthday banquet ends,
I will immediately begin experiments.
All outsiders who know of the half-breed,
including the Sand Mercenary Company,
must be taken care of.
During this time,
Mo Ran should have cleaned everything up.
As long as my experiment succeeds,
no one in the Jia Ma Empire will be able to oppose me!
Among Mo Clan’s ancestors,
there was once an alchemist
who liked to study unusual and eccentric things.
For example,
taking the strange abilities of Magical Beasts or humans
and transplanting them into his own clan members’ bodies,
permitting a great increase in strength for a short time.
What a psycho.
I think
that girl called Qing Lin
should have something unusual about her, yes?
Could it be...
Triple Jade-Green Snake Flower Pupils?
Old Hai,
I must go to the Mo Clan immediately to save her.
If I could request Old Hai
to go with me.
Little Yan,
you must be careful.
That’s right, Little Yan.
How about
we also go with you?
Big Brother, Second Brother,
focus on your recovery.
With Old Hai accompanying,
I will definitely be fine.
Don’t worry.
It doesn’t seem like I agreed to go.
Little Yan,
you’ve already grown to a level we aren’t able to estimate.
This aura...
Little brother Xiao Yan,
the favor I owe you can be considered paid, yes?
This Mo Clan business
has nothing to do with me.
However...
the Dou Qi comparable to a Fight Emperor within your body
is actually
not originating from you, right?
Old Hai,
why do you say this?
Your age.
Although little brother Xiao Yan
is talented and quick-witted,
reaching a Fight Emperor’s strength at only this age
is utterly impossible.
You
should have activated some kind of unknown thing;
that is to say,
that power
does not actually belong to you.
Old Hai,
as expected of a Fight Emperor.
Your sight really is sharp.
Although that power does not belong to me,
I can still control it
and compete toe-to-toe with Fight Emperor practitioners.
Old Hai,
which star Fight Emperor are you presently?
Two-star.
Why do you ask?
Then may I ask,
before being sealed, how many stars was Old Hai?
Five-star.
After four to five years,
I will automatically recover to five stars.
Perhaps not even you yourself believe that.
The higher the class, the more difficult it is to recover strength.
Trying to return to Five-star Fight Emperor,
will take more than a short four to five years.
However,
I might have a method, within one year’s time,
to let you completely recover a Five-star Fight Emperor’s strength.
Moreover, it doesn’t have any major sequelae.
What is this method?
It hurts,
it hurts!
Let go,
let go!
Old Hai,
have you heard of the Spiritual Recovery Purple Pill?
This is a Tier 5 medicinal pill.
Although its tier isn’t very high,
the ingredients it requires
are rather difficult to find.
Its effect
is to have some kinds of strength
that declined due to seals or internal injuries
be completely recovered.
Say it.
What sort of compensation
are you willing to exchange for the Spiritual Recovery Purple Pill?
Erm,
the Spiritual Recovery Purple Pill’s medicinal herbs,
I’ll need to spend a lot of time looking for them.
How about this,
until I find all the ingredients and refine the Spiritual Recovery Purple Pill,
Old Hai
can stick by my side?
You are looking for a long term fighter, yes?
Old Hai,
you should know
that just by relying on your own power,
even ten years’ time
might not be enough to recover your strength.
We should still be on good terms if the transaction fails,
you’d better not turn against me!
No matter how difficult it is to find the ingredients,
I’ll give you one year’s time.
During that year, I will act as your bodyguard
and ensure your safety.
After one year,
you will give me the Spiritual Recovery Purple Pill.
Accept it.
But Teacher,
it’s only one year.
That’s too good for him.
He was once Jia Ma Empire’s famed Ice Emperor, after all,
and has a strong practitioner’s pride.
One year
is probably his limit.
Just take it.
Then
I’ll listen to Teacher.
Then it’s decided.
One year period.
Let’s go;
we can reach Yan City before dark.
“Mo Estate”
You’d all better keep your wits about you,
tonight is the Clan Head’s big birthday!
Not even a single fly
will be allowed to sneak into our Mo Clan!
Yes.
Why do we have to wear this nonsense?
You are Jia Ma Empire’s famous Ice Emperor;
you’d be recognized as soon as you show your face.
While a nameless kid like myself
doesn’t need to worry about being recognized.
But you, old sir,
are going to be by my side for a year.
If you get exposed tonight,
then it’d be worthless.
How are you planning to search?
I once spent some time with Qing Lin
and am very familiar with her aura.
I’ll use Spiritual Strength to scan the Mo Estate
and search for where they’ve imprisoned Qing Lin.
Besides this secret chamber hidden underground
which my Spiritual Strength was unable to penetrate,
I am unable to find Qing Lin
anywhere else in the Mo Estate.
The entrance was blown open with a punch by Dou Qi.
Could it be that besides us,
there are other people
also looking for something in the Mo Clan?
Who knows.
But the more chaotic the situation,
the better for us.
Let’s go down and look.
Hopefully Qing Lin is indeed down there.
En.
Twelfth one.
I wonder which person
is one step ahead of us.
These twelve guards have been killed in a single strike.
They were not even able to sound an alarm right before dying.
The killer
possesses a Fight Emperor’s strength.
Their strength
is not weaker than yours or mine.
Fight Emperor?
How did another Fight Emperor appear?
We will soon reach the bottom.
There isn’t a Fight Emperor’s aura down there.
Looks like this Fight Emperor
has already left.
What’s that smell?
It stinks.
Why stop here?
Mo Cheng
really is sinister.
This secret chamber is filled with innocent humans and beasts used for experimentation.
Little brother Xiao Yan,
check this place
for whether or not it has the girl you’re looking for.
Qing Lin isn’t here.
Old Hai,
let’s make a move.
We’ll capture Mo Cheng
and interrogate him about Qing Lin’s whereabouts.
I want to expose this abominable guy
in front of everyone.
Wait,
bring one of these capsules for storing beasts.
This is the most important piece of evidence.
Old Hai really does think things through.
Let’s go.
Come, come, come.
Drink!
Please.
City Governor, Lord Bo Er,
Ye Clan Head, Sir Ye Cong,
my thanks to both for finding time
to take part in my birthday banquet.
Lord Mo Cheng,
you are our Yan City’s
indispensable pillar!
Oh, not at all.
This banquet sure is lively.
Lord Mo Cheng,
Jia Ma Empire’s Northeast territory
has nearly been completely swallowed by the Mo Clan.
You flatter me.
Old brother Ye Cong’s temperament is still this straightforward.
Good.
Very good!
Misty Cloud Sect Leader’s personal disciple,
Nalan Yanran has come to express congratulations!
Niece Nalan has come.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Have you thought about ♪
♪ After crossing this desert ♪
♪ Just what lies ahead ♪
♪ Shall I fall here ♪
♪ Or firmly grasp onto fate’s ♪
♪ pulse ♪
♪ He once ♪
♪ loved ♪
♪ hated ♪
♪ suffered ♪
♪ until seeing that flame in the distance ♪
♪ Perhaps this ♪
♪ is ruinous ♪
♪ is excessive ♪
♪ is wrong ♪
♪ Yet still unafraid ♪
♪ to burn ♪
♪ Disregard that unbounded universe ♪
♪ Engage in a fight ♪
♪ Who can resist the wave splitting flame ♪
♪ Don’t speak of this endless dangerous threshold ♪
♪ Reject the climb ♪
♪ He intends to ride the wind ♪
♪ straight through ♪
♪ the heavens ♪
Preview