♪ Far off into the expanse of yellow sand ♪
♪ Comes great longing for a parted person ♪
♪ Moonlight like water, clouds like smoke ♪
♪ When did it once shine down ♪
♪ Afraid of mortal greed abiding ♪
♪ Can’t help answer your thousand words with ten thousand of mine ♪
♪ Back then a farewell, now meeting again ♪
♪ Lingering quietly grows from the fingertips ♪
♪ Even if your ears, nose, brows, eyes can’t be forgotten ♪
♪ Yet still wait for the two of us to have debts never more ♪
♪ Gathering orchids on an empty mountain ♪
♪ Searching for butterflies over the sea ♪
♪ Too much love and hate ultimately precludes fulfillment ♪
♪ Thrilling experiences rush by ♪
♪ Endlessly distant heaven and earth ♪
♪ Drooping eyes are all in the past ♪
♪ Lonely when you go ♪
♪ Yet dreams are indistinct when you return ♪
♪ Perhaps this love may not be as wished ♪
♪ Countless feelings overwhelm ♪
♪ Heart is shaken while still young ♪
♪ Asking who can, by whom, ♪
♪ be exempt ♪
Battle Through The Heavens - Season 3
Recap
Promise me,
please don’t risk swallowing the Heavenly Flame.
If I were to fail,
please forget about me.
Episode 7
Attack together!
You bunch of fellows,
do you really think I wouldn’t kill you?
Dare I ask Sect Leader Yun, so brazenly barging into my Snake People tribe,
why you not only lack the slightest apology
but are instead this arrogant?
Is it that you think my clan can be bullied?
Sorry.
This time I was entrusted by Gu He to help exchange for the Heavenly Flame.
I did not intend to harm people.
Unfortunately, you don’t know good intentions from bad.
Before I change my mind,
leave at once!
Don’t speak too soon.
You might be a Fight Emperor,
but trying to face us five Fight Kings
isn’t going to be an easy task!
You can try.
A Fight Emperor’s strength,
could a Fight King shake it?
Hold her back!
Her speed is too quick,
don’t take her on alone!
Prepare the seal!
Five Snake Spirit Gathering!
This is the Snake People’s fusion Fight Technique;
turns out it really is something.
Five Snake Poison Killing Seal!
Yun Zhi, this girl,
I reckon she really does have ways to let you become a strong person.
Looks like you’re mad again.
When I saved her in the Magical Beast Mountain Range,
I knew she was kind hearted.
Before leaving,
she even left behind the Sea Core Vest for me.
Alas,
she doesn’t know
how important the Heavenly Flame is to me.
The girl has a good heart,
but she doesn’t know,
for the sake of revenge, of shame,
just how much you’ve sacrificed during these three years.
Teacher,
find a safe place.
I need to swallow the Heavenly Flame as soon as possible.
This is—
Snake People practitioners have caught up.
That’s the place we just left from;
Yun Zhi, she—
I sense the auras of five Snake People Fight Kings.
This light pillar seems to be the Snake People displaying their fusion Fight Technique.
Fusion Fight Technique?
Yun Zhi, this girl,
I presume even she would find it tricky to deal with.
Teacher,
let’s quickly hide the Heavenly Flame
and then go help Yun Zhi.
A portal.
There’s a powerful and terrifying aura inside.
I am actually unable to perceive this giant snake’s rank.
I cannot let this beast channel out of the void.
Wind’s Peak,
Killer Meteor!
We sacrificed our lifespan
and used the Five Snake Poison Killing Seal to summon the Spirit Snake;
we will be sure to leave your soul in the desert!
Finish her off!
Just you?
Wind’s Peak,
Setting Sun Flare!
How?
The Spirit Snake isn’t a body of flesh and blood;
even a Fight Emperor shouldn’t think of hurting the Spirit Snake.
The disgrace suffered by the Snake People,
only blood can wash it away!
I didn’t expect
that I would actually fall here...
Are you alright?
Another Fight Emperor?
This flame
is actually a Heavenly Flame?
You are gravely injured,
need to heal your wounds immediately.
Just as well...
Thank you Fight Emperor, sir.
May I ask for honorable sir’s name?
The favor of saving my life,
I will definitely repay it.
I was just asked by someone to come help.
Asked by someone?
I do not know who requested that you save me,
could it be
Gu He?
Gu He doesn’t have the qualification to move me.
Quickly heal up.
Fight Emperor, sir,
if you leave now
you would become the Snake People frien—
It was you who hurt her;
then leave your lives behind!
Looking to die!
This Fight Emperor’s Heavenly Flame just so happens to restrain the flame Spirit Snake!
Overreaching beast.
Not good,
this Heavenly Flame...
There was not half a grudge between the Snake People and sir;
sir’s manner today,
we will firmly remember.
Withdraw!
Snake Technique: Split!
I can’t allow the tiger to return to the mountain.
Since we’ve become enemies,
definitely can’t leave behind seeds of trouble.
But Teacher—
Little fellow,
she should be alright now.
Go on.
I—
I don’t know how to face her.
Matters of emotion,
the old me can’t help you with.
The Snake People have already fled.
Since you are alright,
then till we meet again.
Many thanks to sir.
I still do not know
who was it that asked you to come help?
It was a little fellow who requested that I come.
Allow me, on his behalf, to say sorry to you.
He may have gone a bit overboard.
Little fellow...
could it be
Yao Yan?
May I ask the old sir,
he and I...
can we meet again?
Yun Zhi gazed in the direction Yao Yan departed from,
waiting for that man
to once again appear before her.
But the Yao Yan at that time
would also be the Three Year Agreement’s attendee,
Xiao Yan.
Sometimes
an encounter is fated,
but it is also damned.
In this world,
what is predestined
is also inescapable doom.
When these two appear on the same person,
that person,
as your destined one,
they are also
your inescapable
doom.
Her Majesty The Queen may not have died.
Elder,
why do you say this?
Just then, when the Fight Emperor was about to kill us off,
I detected a thread of the Queen’s aura.
Really?
Are you sure it was Her Majesty The Queen?
Then Her Majesty The Queen,
just where is she?
I am unable to tell.
Let us wait.
One day
Her Majesty The Queen will return.
I’m prepared.
Xiao Yan,
first pull over the Heavenly Flame.
Then have your palm reach into the Heavenly Flame;
find the flame seed at its core;
and take it out.
Quick!
No way,
putting my hand into the Heavenly Flame?
Isn’t that looking to die?
Quick!
With the Blood Lotus Pill’s blood film,
there won’t be any problems.
Dammit,
come over!
The Three Year Agreement is almost here;
refining the Heavenly Flame
is imperative!
Found it.
What terrifying destructive power;
after not even an hour, this temperature
could cause a large city
to be burnt to ashes.
Xiao Yan,
focus.
This time,
I must catch and take you out.
Caught you!
So this is the flame seed.
A thousand years of absorbed energy is compressed within the flame seed;
if the flame seed were to completely erupt
even a Fight Ancestor,
when facing such catastrophic power
would have only one ending.
That is
their demise.
What should I do next?
Swallow it.
What?
Now that you’re not giving up,
then hold on to it.
Life or death,
strong or weak.
Your choice begins from this moment.
Teacher,
I’m going to start.
Quickly consume the Ice Spirit Cold Fountain!
Drive it to circulate through the meridians in your body.
After completing the circulation,
use your Dou Qi to enwrap the Heavenly Flame,
direct it along the route of the Flame Mantra Qi Method,
and then swallow it.
Xiao Yan,
Xiao Yan!
stabilize your mind,
you cannot allow the flame seed to come out!
If the flame seed leaves your body,
it would mean swallowing the Heavenly Flame had failed,
and you would also be burnt to ashes by the flame!
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Have you thought about ♪
♪ After crossing this desert ♪
♪ Just what lies ahead ♪
♪ Shall I fall here ♪
♪ Or firmly grasp onto fate’s ♪
♪ pulse ♪
♪ He once ♪
♪ loved ♪
♪ hated ♪
♪ suffered ♪
♪ until seeing that flame in the distance ♪
♪ Perhaps this ♪
♪ is ruinous ♪
♪ is excessive ♪
♪ is wrong ♪
♪ Yet still unafraid ♪
♪ to burn ♪
♪ Disregard that unbounded universe ♪
♪ Engage in a fight ♪
♪ Who can resist the wave splitting flame ♪
♪ Don’t speak of this endless dangerous threshold ♪
♪ Reject the climb ♪
♪ He intends to ride the wind ♪
♪ straight through ♪
♪ the heavens ♪
Preview