♪ Far off into the expanse of yellow sand ♪
♪ Comes great longing for a parted person ♪
♪ Moonlight like water, clouds like smoke ♪
♪ When did it once shine down ♪
♪ Afraid of mortal greed abiding ♪
♪ Can’t help answer your thousand words with ten thousand of mine ♪
♪ Back then a farewell, now meeting again ♪
♪ Lingering quietly grows from the fingertips ♪
♪ Even if your ears, nose, brows, eyes can’t be forgotten ♪
♪ Yet still wait for the two of us to have debts never more ♪
♪ Gathering orchids on an empty mountain ♪
♪ Searching for butterflies over the sea ♪
♪ Too much love and hate ultimately precludes fulfillment ♪
♪ Thrilling experiences rush by ♪
♪ Endlessly distant heaven and earth ♪
♪ Drooping eyes are all in the past ♪
♪ Lonely when you go ♪
♪ Yet dreams are indistinct when you return ♪
♪ Perhaps this love may not be as wished ♪
♪ Countless feelings overwhelm ♪
♪ Heart is shaken while still young ♪
♪ Asking who can, by whom, ♪
♪ be exempt ♪
Battle Through The Heavens - Season 3
Everyone,
Recap
we’ll meet again, if it’s fated.
Teacher,
let’s go.
Yue Mei,
have these four flames
placed in the Shrine’s four corners.
Let him slowly search.
Capture that person!
They ran away!
Chase!
Catch up!
Look!
What is that?
Episode 3
Quick!
Go.
Leave quickly.
Quicker!
I’ll charge in while it’s chaotic.
Halt!
The altar is off-limits,
you are not allowed to enter!
I’ll back off,
I’ll back off!
Now what to do?
We can talk things out, okay?
What now?
Teacher,
is the Heavenly Flame inside?
The Heavenly Flame’s aura is too weak;
only after entering can I sense it.
Reinforcement Snake Guards have arrived!
Wonderful!
We’re saved!
Captain Yue Mei,
humans have invaded.
You all stay behind.
Those that break into the Western Shrine,
kill without mercy!
Yes!
Elder,
This fellow Gu He has arrived.
Shouldn’t we
make the first move?
No need.
Courtesy first, soldiers after
to avoid creating new problems.
The Queen’s evolution is instead the top priority.
Gu He,
bring your people and leave at once.
Or else,
it will be regarded as declaring war against our race!
Now things are heating up.
Gu He has come
only for the reason of meeting Queen Medusa.
The Queen cannot meet you.
If you leave now,
The Queen is merciful and will not give chase.
Otherwise,
because you have hurt Yue Mei and disrupted the ritual,
my people must demand accountability from the Jia Ma Empire!
Without meeting Queen Medusa,
Gu He is not able to leave.
Your wild behavior cannot be tolerated!
You finally came.
Your Majesty The Queen.
The Queen appearing
means that the evolution hasn’t started yet.
Teacher,
the Heavenly Flame is still here.
They are in the spotlight,
we are in the shadows.
There’s an opportunity.
It’s more fun
when there’s muddying of the water.
You are looking for me.
Queen Medusa,
it is a great honor to meet with you.
I am Jia Ma Empire’s Gu He.
I heard that Your Majesty The Queen
obtained the Green Lotus Core Flame half a year ago.
This Heavenly Flame,
how important it is to an Alchemist,
presumably Your Majesty The Queen is clear about this.
The blood of Snake People is cold;
Heavenly Flame does not actually offer much benefit to you.
This humble one
wishes to take out pills of equal value for exchange.
Pill-King really is well-informed
and your abilities are uncommon,
even being able to invite a Fight Emperor.
This Queen is very curious,
just what can you take out
that would be worthy of the Heavenly Flame?
This humble one is willing to use two Tier 6 Fight Spirit Pills
and a Tier 7 Body Transformation Pill
to exchange for the Heavenly Flame.
I do not know if Your Majesty The Queen
would allow this humble one to fulfill his wish.
Body Transformation Pill?
There he is!
Chase!
Who is that?
A human discovered by Captain Yue Mei earlier.
He escaped from my hands.
It seems that he’s part of Gu He’s gang.
Let me handle him.
Yes, Marshal Hua.
Teacher,
What kind of treasure is the Body Transformation Pill?
Tier 7 Body Transformation Pill
can let a Magical Beast completely break away from their beast body.
An incredible pill for retaining a long lifespan
while gaining a human’s training talent.
If the Queen has the Body Transformation Pill,
there’s no need to risk swallowing a Heavenly Flame to evolve.
Evolving to a Fight Ancestor through the Body Transformation Pill
would take an indefinite amount of time.
Evolving by swallowing Heavenly Flame,
although there is only a slim chance of survival,
given the Queen’s character,
she’d definitely take that chance.
Something’s off.
Your conditions are quite tempting.
Unfortunately,
I refuse.
Why?
The preciousness of the Body Transformation Pill,
as the Queen of the Snake People,
you know it better than we do.
You
are challenging me?
While this Queen has not yet been angered,
wherever you came from,
you can return to.
I once happened to learn from an ancient book
that once the Snake People Queen’s strength reaches the peak of Fight Emperor,
with enough luck,
she can undergo a strange evolution.
This evolution not only allows the Queen to freely transform into a human
but moreover allows advancement to Fight Ancestor.
And the thing required for this evolution
is a Heavenly Flame.
Didn’t expect you’d actually know such things.
This Queen really did not foresee this.
Not only that,
I also know that the current you
is only possessing some of the Queen’s thoughts,
an energy body.
This—
An opportunity has come.
The Queen died!
Avenge the Queen!
Kill them!
Damn,
they’ve started to fight.
Feng Li,
let’s go!
Okay.
Not good.
You command the Snake Guards to protect the altar.
I will go set off the Summoning Order
to notify the Eight Great Tribe Leaders to immediately provide reinforcements!
Yes.
Humans are coming to kill us!
Run quickly!
Don’t push!
Continue attacking!
Flying Squad will harass from the sky;
before the Eight Great Leaders get here,
hold them off!
Obey.
Captain Yue Mei,
the civilians are trying to hide in the altar,
we can’t stop them.
This fight
does not require civilian women and children to be on the battlefield.
Let them hide inside.
Yes.
Please give way!
Sect Leader Yun,
why provoke the Snake People?
I am hired to ensure your safety on this trip.
But as a Fight Emperor of the Jia Ma Empire,
I absolutely cannot allow the Snake People to have a Fight Ancestor!
I planned for half a year,
intending to rely on the Heavenly Flame to advance my alchemy.
It’s regrettable that in the end, it was for nothing.
The Queen wants to swallow the Heavenly Flame to evolve;
she definitely won’t leave this place.
Let’s try, before she swallows the Heavenly Flame,
to snatch the Heavenly Flame.
Good idea.
Wait until I sense the Heavenly Flame
and find where the Queen is hiding.
Snake People Summoning Order!
Not good, he’s triggering the Summoning Order!
Stop!
It succeeded.
This is bad,
the Eight Great Leaders got the message.
Gu He,
where is the Heavenly Flame?
Once we obtain it, we’ll leave immediately.
This place is too distant from the Heavenly Flame,
I’m unable to sense it.
Alright then,
we’ll kill our way down.
Please, Your Majesty the Queen, protect us!
Green Lotus Pedestal
sensed that the Heavenly Flame is down there.
There are only civilians here,
this is a godsend opportunity, stinky kid!
Without anyone noticing,
take away the little Heavenly Flame, little Heavenly Flame...
Where are you going?
Careful!
Kid,
your strength isn’t bad!
A human!
Actually daring to disguise as a Snake Person!
Gu He’s accomplice,
probably didn’t expect that I, Hua She Er, had long already discovered you!
Kill him!
Avenge the Queen!
It’s not like I was the one who killed your Queen!
How did I become Gu He’s accomplice, huh?
Run towards your right.
Gu He taking the heat for you,
isn’t this perfect?
You’re right.
Halt!
Not going to give up on chasing me?
Now they can’t catch up.
Destroying my altar, harming my people,
insulting my Queen!
Humans, you have taken things too far!
Snake Technique:
Rampage!
The Snake race’s berserk technique,
raising strength to the peak of Fight King in an instant!
Peak of Fight King?
Exploding Steps!
She’s coming.
I’ve been discovered.
What’s happening?
This place actually has mechanisms?
Stinky brat,
don’t step on the tiles with runes on them!
I sense that the Heavenly Flame is just below.
Just below this?
Watch out!
Let Teacher handle the rest.
Make it quick.
A trivial skill.
Octane Blast!
Avoid all the tiles with runes,
wait for Teacher to find a safe method
before going underground—
Simple and brutal, has the best effect.
Heavenly Flame,
I’m coming!
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Have you thought about ♪
♪ After crossing this desert ♪
♪ Just what lies ahead ♪
♪ Shall I fall here ♪
♪ Or firmly grasp onto fate’s ♪
♪ pulse ♪
♪ He once ♪
♪ loved ♪
♪ hated ♪
♪ suffered ♪
♪ until seeing that flame in the distance ♪
♪ Perhaps this ♪
♪ is ruinous ♪
♪ is excessive ♪
♪ is wrong ♪
♪ Yet still unafraid ♪
♪ to burn ♪
♪ Disregard that unbounded universe ♪
♪ Engage in a fight ♪
♪ Who can resist the wave splitting flame ♪
♪ Don’t speak of this endless dangerous threshold ♪
♪ Reject the climb ♪
♪ He intends to ride the wind ♪
♪ straight through ♪
♪ the heavens ♪
Preview