English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ In an old dream, myriad cherry blossoms fall ♪
♪ Among the galaxies, things gather and disperse time after time ♪
♪ I insist on chasing this beam of light ♪
♪ No matter how terrifying and dark the sky ♪
♪ The eternal oath surrounding you and me never changes ♪
♪ Surging like blazing fire into the air before blooming ♪
♪ That blood which boils ♪
♪ Eyes are steeped, fire actually strewn everywhere ♪
♪ Looking back, falling into the heart's abyssal stream ♪
♪ Against the wind, undergo rebirth midst downfall ♪
♪ On the journey, that person in the distance ♪
♪ will keep firmly believing ♪
♪ On the journey, that person from the past ♪
♪ sustains the original intention ♪
Battle Through The Heavens
Jia Nan Academy
Episode 4
The Black Mark City auction’s grand finale treasure turned out
to be a Tier 7 pill, Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon Pill.
While everybody was vying for this divine pill,
Xiao Yan, knowing that he was cash-strapped,
left after taking his auction earnings.
The final winner of the divine pill, Sky Serpent Mansion’s Elder Qing
was met with the Blood Sect’s ambush.
Xiao Yan, who had been trailing Fan Ling, unexpectedly witnessed this scene.
What is the meaning of this?
I’ve been waiting for you for a while now.
You came for this, right?
Tell me.
What secret does this map hold, exactly?
Sorry,
can’t tell you.
Heh.
Sure enough.
Good,
very good.
Four-star Fight Grandmaster,
daring to walk into a trap with such little strength,
you sure have guts.
Junior Sect Leader,
why must you handle it personally?
Leave this person to me.
You stand by;
in case he plans to run away,
stop him.
What great strength.
But fortunately, this fellow is only at the Fight Grandmaster level.
As expected of a Fight Spirit practitioner.
But why does this fellow’s Dou Qi have a kind of tenuous feeling to it?
No matter who you are,
today, you no longer have half a thread’s chance for regret!
However,
to thank you for bringing me good news
that the map indeed contains a secret,
I won’t have you end up a shriveled corpse.
Bone Disintegrating Evil Blood Palm!
It is unexpected that the Sect Leader passed down
this level of Fight Technique to Junior Sect Leader.
He really does have high expectations for him.
Careful,
with your current strength,
you are still no match for a Fight Spirit.
That may not be the case.
Xiao Yan,
are you thinking of‒?
Sky Fire Three Mysterious Change, First Change:
Green Lotus Change!
Fire.
Damn it,
he actually possesses a Heavenly Flame?
Junior Sect Leader,
our Blood Sect is the most suppressed by Heavenly Flame;
it is best for us to leave immediately.
Delay him a bit longer.
As soon as my father arrives...
It’s a pity,
originally I wanted to leave it for Ling’er.
My father Fan Lao is a Fight Emperor;
don’t mess around, you brat!
Trying to stall until Fan Lao gets here?
Junior Sect Leader,
step back!
Let me hold him off!
Xiao Yan,
you must make this quick.
Xiao Yan, hurry,
don’t let him get away.
Actually‒
fell‒
This Sky Fire Three Mysterious Change,
its power is quite great;
but unfortunately
the toll it takes on the body isn’t small either.
Not bad,
you’ve improved.
Compared to the first time you used Sky Fire Three Mysterious Change,
this time,
you were barely able to hold on.
Little fellow,
leave now.
I’ve detected Fan Lao’s aura.
Ling’er.
Whoever it is,
I will make them suffer the pain of having their
flesh torn apart by ten thousand blades!
Don’t worry,
I can no longer perceive Fan Lao’s aura.
Teacher,
let’s rest overnight before departing.
Little fellow’s luck is pretty good.
In little more than three years, you’ve
obtained three map fragments.
We are again one step closer to the
Purifying Demonic Lotus Flame.
It’s all thanks to Teacher’s insight.
Or else, no matter how lucky I am,
it would be to no avail.
Let me take a look at this treasure.
Consume it.
Leaving it on you isn’t safe.
Ah, what?
I said,
take this Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon Pill.
Here?
This is but a Tier 7 pill.
Stop talking,
consume it now.
Teacher,
this thing isn’t fake, right?
Why isn’t there the slightest reaction?
What kind of reaction do you want?
Something like the pills you took in the past,
having to go through excruciating pain?
This is a Tier 7 pill, after all.
There has got to be some baseline effect, right?
At that auction, didn’t they say
that this pill’s main effect is
“stand after breaking.”
Once the medicinal strength enters the body,
if you are lucky,
you will naturally be able to manifest unimaginable
benefits in a life-and-death situation.
However, this sort of opportunity
can only occur once.
That kind of inhuman torture isn’t something just anyone can bear.
Even Feng Xian with his tenacious temperament
was almost unable to hang on back then.
Pain that even a Fight Ancestor would find difficult to endure.
Teacher is familiar with Venerate Feng?
I suppose.
I will gradually tell you more about myself in the future.
Knowing too much right now will not benefit you.
Then for now,
does this pill not have the slightest use?
Not quite.
This Mysterious Dragon Pill was refined
from Rank 6 Dragon-type Monster Cores.
If by chance you were to absorb some
of the thin dragon aura it contains,
combined with use of a compatible Sonic Fight Technique,
when facing enemies in the future,
it will be a trump card.
You can try circulating your Dou Qi to check.
Hang in there.
My...
inheritance succeeded.
Stinky brat sure has enough luck,
you have indeed inherited that soul-shocking strange dragon aura.
However,
with your current strength,
just relying on the dragon aura to make sonic waves
is far too damaging to your voice.
You must pair it with a Sonic Fight Technique.
It’s just,
those kinds of Fight Techniques are quite rare.
Trying to obtain one
is easier said than done.
Being able to inherit the dragon aura
is already an unexpected gift.
As for a Sonic Fight Technique,
I’ll just look for one in the future.
But, Teacher,
you seem to be very familiar with this
Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon Pill,
actually knowing how to drive out the hidden dragon aura inside it.
Teacher,
are you‒
Teacher.
That Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon Pill’s medicinal formula
was created by me.
The only people on the Continent who can refine it
consist of two individuals.
One is myself,
the other
is my student whom I once regarded as the most perfect inheritor.
When he was still a baby,
I carried him out from icy cold debris
and raised him like my own son.
His talent in alchemy was not any lesser than yours
and he eventually became a most outstanding alchemist.
Only,
in the end,
due to some things,
he chose to betray me.
How I am today
is all thanks to him.
He should die.
Fortunately,
I later met you.
We shouldn’t have left Black Mark City this early.
This pill,
perhaps he personally delivered it.
Even if we were really able to find him at Black Mark City, then what?
Because of constrainment by that Hall of Souls,
I do not dare to appear at will.
Just based on your current strength,
whether in terms of alchemy or Dou Qi cultivation,
you are no match for him by a long shot.
Teacher,
I will surpass him.
And then I will clean up the sect.
Your eyes
will not be blind a second time.
Good, good!
I, Yao Chen, also believe
that these old eyes of mine
will certainly not be blind a second time.
It's time to go to Jia Nan Academy.
The earlier we find the Fallen Heart Flame,
the earlier I can refine a body for you.
Jia Nan Academy’s old fellows aren't pushovers, mind you.
By then, I won’t be able to come out freely;
you will only be able to rely on yourself.
Let’s get a move on.
Teacher shouldn’t underestimate me;
among people around my age,
I won’t need you to help.
Back then, I was‒
Shut up.
Oh.
Up ahead is Jia Nan Academy.
You cannot forcefully fly within one hundred miles of Jia Nan Academy;
otherwise, you will draw attacks.
Xiao Yan,
descend.
We will enter through Peace Town.
Jia Nan Academy really is powerful,
pressuring even Black Corner Region’s people into submissive obedience.
This must be the terrifying Death Spirit Tree.
Everyone,
to enter Peace Town,
you must consume this pill specially refined
by the Academy for sensing killing intent.
As soon as you possess murderous intentions while in the town,
your whole body will suffuse with red light
and you’ll be wanted for arrest.
Before leaving the town,
just go to the antidote distribution site to receive the antidote.
Um,
can Academy students
be exempt from taking the pill?
You claim you are an Academy student;
report your name, age and recruitment instructor.
Xiao Yan,
eighteen.
Instructor Ruo Lin.
Xiao Yan?
You are that Xiao Yan from Jia Ma Empire
who requested two years’ leave of absence in one go?
So it’s actually him.
Looks like he’s just so-so.
Exactly.
Seems like this girl’s reputation in the Academy isn’t small.
Based on verification with the records,
your identity has been confirmed.
The Law Enforcement Unit will send you to the Academy.
Your return is just in time;
tomorrow happens to be the Inner Academy Qualifying Competition.
Last year Ruo Lin registered you,
but, unfortunately, you didn’t come,
infuriating her to no end.
At the time,
I really couldn’t make it for certain reasons.
Well, I am not concerned with matters between you and your instructor.
Alright.
Head on up.
Many thanks.
Nice!
Xiao Xun’er, wins!
Junior Xun’er is amazing!
That’s right!
She actually defeated Mo Wen in such a short time!
That’s right, she’s so awesome!
Senior,
you’ve allowed me to win.
Next round,
Xuan Level Class Three, Xue Beng
versus Huang Level Class Two, Xiao Yan!
Brother Xiao Yan.
Has that Xiao Yan not arrived yet?
I know about Xiao Yan,
he was absent at the last Inner Academy Qualifying Competition.
Yea,
this kind of cowardly, irresponsible man,
how did he enter the eyes of Xun’er?
A timid little rat,
is he worth so much of your concern?
He came.
Huang Level Class Two,
Xiao Yan.
Zhu Xian
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Dust rains down in the deep night ♪
♪ Standing amidst stormy wind, hair blowing ♪
♪ Heavenly Flame falls; were they ever hesitant or weary ♪
♪ A touch of Sky Flame promises to follow ♪
♪ Back then our figures moved together ♪
♪ Won't let you down; in the end, part the fog before returning ♪
♪ I step through clouds and smoke, walking forward ♪
♪ Rejecting all the various pitfalls ♪
♪ Flap your wings and fly, fight without backing down ♪
♪ That Wu Tan youth is the same as before ♪
♪ Don't look back, break through to the stars' end ♪
♪ Whose support that is behind his back ♪
♪ Enough, enough, enough ♪
♪ Despite that bloodshed, that wound, that enmity ♪
♪ Never rest, forever dye the heavens ♪
♪ At the end, hold no regrets to the very end ♪
Next Episode
Preview