English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ In an old dream, myriad cherry blossoms fall ♪
♪ Among the galaxies, things gather and disperse time after time ♪
♪ I insist on chasing this beam of light ♪
♪ No matter how terrifying and dark the sky ♪
♪ The eternal oath surrounding you and me never changes ♪
♪ Surging like blazing fire into the air before blooming ♪
♪ That blood which boils ♪
♪ Eyes are steeped, fire actually strewn everywhere ♪
♪ Looking back, falling into the heart's abyssal stream ♪
♪ Against the wind, undergo rebirth midst downfall ♪
♪ On the journey, that person in the distance ♪
♪ will keep firmly believing ♪
♪ On the journey, that person from the past ♪
♪ sustains the original intention ♪
Battle Through The Heavens
Jia Nan Academy
Episode 12
Facing the well-coordinated team of older student Liu Mu,
Xiao Yan’s team suffered defeat,
having no choice but to retreat.
After the defeat, Xiao Yan spent the night reviewing
and reformed the team’s battle tactics,
ultimately leading the team to easy victory over Liu Mu’s team.
For the sake of entering the Inner Academy earlier and obtaining more Fire Energy,
emerging leader Xiao Yan assembled all new students
in preparation for a big counter-attack.
Those wind noises earlier,
did you, Xiao Yan, make them on purpose?
Clever trick.
It is unexpected
that you would be this daring,
gathering up all the new students
under your command.
You flatter me.
Please hand over your Fire Energy Cards.
The Fire Energy you’ve stolen previously,
it’s about time they return to their original owners.
Today is likely going to be an intense battle.
Looks like we should join forces,
Xiu Yan.
I’ve been waiting to test just how strong the top five of this session’s Qualifying Competition are.
Take down the leader first;
although there are many new students,
their strength is founded upon that brat Xiao Yan.
By defeating him,
the new student team will definitely collapse.
Strong against strong it is,
let’s rip apart their defense!
This will be a tough battle;
leave the three in the middle to us.
Xun’er,
you and Hu Jia go help the new students.
En.
Be careful, Brother Xiao Yan.
That big guy’s strength isn’t bad,
I’ll deal with him.
The knife carrying one,
leave him to me.
In that case,
that white-haired senior,
allow me to give him a lesson.
Who knew
that we’d actually be lined up for picking by our juniors.
Make it quick;
they are very strong.
We mustn’t take them lightly.
You’re pretty strong, huh?
Turns out his speed and his strength both aren’t weak;
as expected of the Inner Academy being the core of Jia Nan Academy.
Really makes me more and more curious.
Shaking Lightning Arc Blast!
Kid,
it’s your turn next!
Are you alright?
Thank you, Senior Xun’er.
Watch out!
You two, come with me to reinforce the others.
En.
Brat, not bad.
An opportunity to test my techniques has arrived.
Lion Tiger Gold Shattering Roar!
Crap.
Senior,
my apologies.
Dou Qi Armor!
Octane Blast!
How— how could it—
Excuse me,
Senior.
Your leader has already lost.
Still want to continue?
Leader has lost?
How is it possible?
This new student is strong to such an extent?
Leader!
Bastard,
actually this ruthless!
Brothers,
fight!
Perfect.
I—
I’ve lost.
Brother Xiao Yan,
we won!
Beautifully done, everyone.
We really won?
Awesome!
It’s all thanks to Senior Xiao Yan,
or we would’ve been finished for sure!
Senior Xiao Yan’s Sonic Fight Technique just then was so strong!
Wonderful!
All the credit is going to Xiao Yan.
He already admitted defeat,
why harm him?
Wounding a defenseless person,
is it honorable?
Let go!
Apologies, Senior.
This medicine
can help you heal up.
Tell that companion of yours,
this spear today,
I will make him pay for it!
Xiao Yan.
You new students have won.
But you
shouldn’t celebrate too soon.
There are stronger older student teams waiting for you.
I know.
There is still the Black Demon Group and White Demon Group.
Looks like you know quite a bit.
A loss is a loss.
Fire Energy Card,
here.
Sure enough, they have some skill.
They really were able to prey on these two older student teams.
Xiao Yan, this young fellow,
is indeed quite strong,
defeating Su Xiao quickly.
Although he took advantage of the strange effect of the Sonic Fight Technique,
his clean attacks as his sharp judgment
are things not even some of the Inner Academy’s older students possess.
En.
Later, have Hu Qian send over Xiao Yan’s information.
With his potential,
after training in the Inner Academy,
he might be able to squeeze into the Strong Ranking’s top ten.
Xun’er.
Distribute wound healing medicine amongst everyone.
En.
This medicine
can allow you to recover Dou Qi as quickly as possible.
The taste could use some work.
Thanks.
Thank you for the Fire Energy.
Oh well.
It’s on us for being inferior.
This year’s new students aren’t too shabby,
able to defeat this older student team.
Not a problem,
all the Fire Energy you’ve obtained,
hand it to us.
Sha Tie?
You guys actually came as well.
Y’all can get lost.
Let us handle this bunch of new students.
However, I’m not going to return
the Fire Energy you guys lost.
Who told you to be incapable of protecting it?
Sha Tie,
what are you getting at?
I hope your Black Demon Group won’t end up slapped in the face;
after all, this session’s new students aren’t comparable to the past.
You are the so-called Black Demon Group?
You guessed correctly.
We are the Black Demon Group.
These past few days, news of new students stealing from older students has spread around the entire Inner Academy.
Now you, Xiao Yan,
have quite the reputation in the Inner Academy.
However,
ai.
Alas, alas.
In this Fire Energy Hunting Competition,
our duty
is to knock down all of you thorny new students.
However,
as long as you obediently hand over your Fire Energy Cards,
I, Sha Tie, promise not to get rough.
How about it?
Are there no other options?
This is the only option.
Su Xiao’s bunch did help out a little,
exhausting the fighting strength of you new students.
Otherwise,
just our Black Demon Group
couldn’t swallow you all.
Looks like there’s nothing more to discuss.
What,
did your past victory cause you all to become delusional about your own strength?
Fine,
I haven’t fought these past couple days;
my bones are getting itchy.
Big Brother Sha Tie,
perchance you still remember me?
Last time, when you and my cousin visited the Outer Academy,
we met once.
Bai Cheng.
You are...
Bai Shan?
That’s right.
You are also one of this session’s new students?
En.
Yes, Big Brother Sha Tie.
Would it be possible, for the sake of my cousin’s face...
For the sake of Bai Cheng’s face,
I shouldn’t hurt you.
Naturally, you are able to leave.
Big Brother Sha Tie, perhaps...
Bai Shan,
you only need to take care of yourself.
Hurry up and get going.
Don’t meddle.
Big Brother Sha Tie is right.
Bai Shan,
are you going to flee like a coward?
Hmph.
What a joke.
Not fighting with you against the same enemy
is considered fleeing like a coward?
Did you really think we were a team?
Tch.
It was nothing more than a transaction to get what we needed.
And the greatest beneficiary of this transaction
is Xiao Yan alone.
We fight tooth and nail for him,
yet all the benefits
have been taken by him.
Traitor!
Without Xiao Yan’s direction,
would we have gotten to where we are now?
Any random older student team you encounter
would be able to defeat you.
That’s enough.
Since he wants to leave,
leave.
Without him,
we won’t necessarily lose.
Bunch of idiots.
Go ahead and follow him,
I’m done.
Like I said already,
that companion of yours isn’t very good.
Ai.
We can only wish you luck.
Sha Tie’s team isn’t one we can match up to.
Moreover, your companion has now left.
Your originally unpromising odds have decreased further.
Ai.
Let’s leave.
Now that I’ve gathered everyone,
naturally, I will bring everyone out with me.
No matter how strong the enemy is,
I, Xiao Yan,
will never shrink back in the slightest.
I’m not going to bully the weak;
might as well give you time to make preparations.
Let’s see what tricks you pull out.
Black Demon Group’s greatest threat
is their leader,
Sha Tie.
Leave him to me.
Xun’er,
Wu Hao,
Hu Jia.
You each block one of the other three.
The rest of the new students, attack the remaining person;
scatter their strength.
We will defeat our opponents as quickly as possible
to free ourselves to assist you.
Everyone was just in a battle.
Although your Dou Qi has not fully recovered,
as long as we new students
stand united,
who wins and who loses is not yet decided.
Yes!
That’s right!
Go all out against them!
Hell yea!
Go all out!
Let’s fight.
Leave that Xiao Yan to me.
As for the rest, do as you see fit.
The fight has started, brat!
Very good,
your perception is quite strong.
Pity you ran into me today.
Gold Dou Qi,
although this kind of Dou Qi lacks in agility,
its offensive and defensive power is extremely overbearing.
Looks like he’s a close combat fighter.
Fire Palm!
What trick is this now?
Octane Blast!
Overestimating yourself!
I underestimated his strength.
Xiao Yan,
show me your real abilities.
Don’t say you didn’t ask for it.
You are an alchemist?
Your overbearing offensive and defensive power
comes with a deficiency in agility,
and this is your weak point!
So what?
In front of absolute strength and defense,
you are no match for me!
That’s all you got, huh.
How can it be?
Again!
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Dust rains down in the deep night ♪
♪ Standing amidst stormy wind, hair blowing ♪
♪ Heavenly Flame falls; were they ever hesitant or weary ♪
♪ A touch of Sky Flame promises to follow ♪
♪ Back then our figures moved together ♪
♪ Won’t let you down; in the end, part the fog before returning ♪
♪ I step through clouds and smoke, walking forward ♪
♪ Rejecting all the various pitfalls ♪
♪ Flap your wings and fly, fight without backing down ♪
♪ That Wu Tan youth is the same as before ♪
♪ Don’t look back, break through to the stars’ end ♪
♪ Whose support that is behind his back ♪
♪ Enough, enough, enough ♪
♪ Despite that bloodshed, that wound, that enmity ♪
♪ Never rest, forever dye the heavens ♪
♪ At the end, hold no regrets to the very end ♪