English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ In an old dream, myriad cherry blossoms fall ♪
♪ Among the galaxies, things gather and disperse time after time ♪
♪ I insist on chasing this beam of light ♪
♪ No matter how terrifying and dark the sky ♪
♪ The eternal oath surrounding you and me never changes ♪
♪ Surging like blazing fire into the air before blooming ♪
♪ That blood which boils ♪
♪ Eyes are steeped, fire actually strewn everywhere ♪
♪ Looking back, falling into the heart's abyssal stream ♪
♪ Against the wind, undergo rebirth midst downfall ♪
♪ On the journey, that person in the distance ♪
♪ will keep firmly believing ♪
♪ On the journey, that person from the past ♪
♪ sustains the original intention ♪
Battle Through The Heavens
Jia Nan Academy
Episode 3
Faced with the unexpected appearance of
the Purifying Demonic Lotus Flame map,
Xiao Yan forcefully suppressed his churning heart.
He did not know whether he could ultimately refine this demonic flame,
but at this moment, the only thing he knew was
that he needed to obtain the map at all costs.
Confronted by cunning opponents at the auction,
Xiao Yan, in order to avoid raising the suspicion of enemies,
could only back down from competing
and search for another opportunity.
The auction’s most mysterious grand
finale treasure is about to debut at last.
What kind of ripples will it create?
Ladies and gentlemen,
what’s about to come on stage
is this auction’s
grand finale treasure.
Looking at the puffs of chilly air emanating from this jade box,
Teacher,
could it be a pill?
If its price surpasses that of a Di Class Fight Technique,
it has to be at least Tier 7, right?
It is very likely.
Refinement of a Tier 7 pill is extremely difficult.
Following successful refinement,
it will trigger strange natural phenomena
as if doomsday had come.
On the Dou Qi Continent, alchemists who can successfully refine one
are as rare as a phoenix hair or unicorn horn.
And these people
are nowadays invariably grandmasters.
Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon Pill?
Teacher,
what’s wrong?
Nothing.
Spectate for now.
Some things,
allow me to tell you in the future.
Everyone,
this is today’s grand finale treasure.
Tier 7 medicinal pill,
Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon Pill.
This is my first time hearing of a pill at such a tier.
Indeed.
I reckon the starting bid won’t be low.
Ai.
Looks like there’s no hope for us.
That’s right.
To refine this pill,
one requires Monster Cores from two Dragon-type
beasts killed less than seven days prior;
moreover,
the Monster Core rank
has to be at least
Rank 6.
The miraculous effect of the Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon Pill
is not direct promotion of the user’s strength,
but rather
the ability to stand after breaking.
Stand after breaking?
The name of Venerate Feng, Feng Xian,
I think everyone must have heard of it.
Venerate Feng?
That’s a Fight Venerate practitioner,
how could you not know of him?
But what does this pill have to do with Venerate Feng?
Back in the day, the Venerate Feng who was still a
Five-star Fight Ancestor fought with an old enemy;
although he obtained victory, he was gravely injured,
teetering on the brink of death.
Even if he survived,
his strength would have sharply declined.
But in fact,
I think you all have guessed it.
That’s right,
Venerate Feng, Feng Xian luckily obtained
a Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon Pill
and had consumed it.
It was not until that moment of serious injury
that this divine pill went into effect,
allowing him to stand after breaking.
It only took him seven years
What a terrifying “stand after breaking.”
before he leapt to become a Fight Venerate practitioner.
Tell Father,
the item has appeared.
Yes,
Junior Sect Leader.
Enough with the nonsense.
Say a price.
Mere gold is already insufficient to measure up
to the Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon Pill’s value.
Therefore,
this medicinal pill’s price is
unconditional completion of two tasks for the owner.
If the divine pill’s owner has us expend all effort to
fight against an unbeatable practitioner or force,
we still have to do it?
That’s right.
Everyone, rest assured.
These two tasks are sure to be within the
capabilities of the auction participants.
However,
the person who was able to take out this kind of divine pill,
their status and power must not be weak.
And the tasks he is requesting
will most likely not be too easy.
Let’s go.
There’s nothing more worth watching at this auction.
With your current strength,
it is still not enough to compete for this Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon Pill.
Sir, please come in.
Steward Hu is waiting for you inside.
I am the supervisor of this place, Steward Hu.
May I ask for sir’s name?
Yao Yan.
Steward Hu
Mister Yao Yan,
After deducting costs of the Flame Core Ganoderma
and the Pervading Fire Cauldron
as well as a ten percent administrative fee,
from your earnings from auctioning three Green Spirit Pills,
you are left with 930,000.
Please check.
What an unscrupulous administrative fee.
Then I’ve troubled Steward Hu.
I won’t bother you any longer.
Farewell.
Mister Yao Yan,
please wait.
My sect’s Leader is quite interested in Sir.
If Sir might have some time,
could you meet with our Leader?
My thanks for the Leader’s recognition.
I have some business
and cannot stay for long.
Have you seen through his identity?
Yuan Yi
Leader.
This person hides too deeply;
for now, we are unable to tell.
Logically,
taking out three Green Spirit Pills at once
means
that he is very likely to be a high tier alchemist.
Send people to follow him,
figure out his background.
If our Eight Gates can recruit such a high tier alchemist,
then we no longer need fear
that Medicine Emperor.
Yes.
Get on it straight away.
I still need to personally conduct the Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon
Pill handover procedure for Sky Serpent Mansion’s people.
That thing is too valuable.
Our Eight Gates is based on the principle of “reputation first”
so we must ensure that auctioned goods
are safely handed over to the buyers.
Eight Gates agents are shadowing you.
They underestimate me too much, huh.
Where is he?
My true appearance,
you haven’t seen it, I’m afraid.
Kid,
Teacher has already locked down Fan Ling’s aura.
Firstly catch up to him,
then wait for an opportunity.
We must obtain that map.
En.
Got it, Teacher.
This return trip is sure to be dangerous.
Everyone must stay on high alert.
Yes.
Go.
Careful,
there’s an ambush in the forest!
Elder Qing is indeed quite skilled.
However,
I’d like to see how many of my Blood Sect’s
disciples you’ll be able to fend off.
The Blood Sect wishes to become enemies
with my Sky Serpent Mansion?
Not quite enemies,
we only wish to ask Elder Qing for
that Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon Pill.
Ha.
Then I’d like to see
what you are capable of.
Hmph.
You are asking for this!
Everyone, be careful!
Protect Elder Qing!
Elder Qing,
have you thought it through?
Will you voluntarily hand over the pill,
or will I personally fetch it after you die?
Just based on this sort of shameless method of your Blood Sect,
stop dreaming!
Kid,
be careful.
I’m sensing several formidable auras ahead.
En.
I’ll act according to the situation.
This aura...
could it be?
Die!
The Blood Sect wants to act as a mantis catching cicadas,
but you are underqualified.
Such big talk.
Is it-?
Fan Lao,
launching a sneak attack,
what skill do you have?
Hand over the Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon Pill
Fan Lao
and I’ll leave your corpse intact.
Fight Emperor.
Don’t worry,
with my aura isolating you,
he won’t discover you.
I’ve always been curious about Elder Qing’s looks.
Can Father leave her for Child to deal with?
If you dare approach,
I will have this Yin-Yang Mysterious Dragon Pill
turned to powder on the spot!
If my Sky Serpent Mansion cannot have it,
you can also forget about getting it!
Then I will destroy your Dou Qi,
let you have a life worse than death.
Hmph.
Ling’er,
take it and leave first.
Yes, Father.
You all will escort the Junior Sect Leader back to Tomb City.
There must be no mishaps.
Yes.
Let’s go.
Old scum Fan!
I’m going to fight to the death with you today!
Hmph.
Striking rock with an egg.
Looks like we can only follow him for now;
wait for a suitable opportunity.
Ai.
We aren’t able to help her.
In the Black Corner Region, you can only rely on yourself.
Junior Sect Leader.
There are movements of the Black Skull Tomb ahead.
Black Skull Tomb?
Have they come to intercept us?
Looking at their appearance, it doesn’t seem to be an ambush.
Instead, it looks like they are searching for a
secluded path to return to Black Skull Tomb.
Taking a small path?
Heh.
It suits their surreptitious style.
How many people do they have?
A total of six people.
Among them are two Fight Spirits,
a Fight Grandmaster,
and the rest are all at the Fight Master level.
Originally I didn’t plan to lay my hands on them,
but they just had to walk this mountain path.
Then don’t blame this young master for being black-hearted.
Hurry up.
Catch up to the Black Skull Tomb’s people.
Junior Sect Leader.
Sect Leader previously explained
that our top priority is to send the Yin-Yang
Mysterious Dragon Pill back to the sect.
If we get into an accident,
What is there to fear?
If something happens, this young master will take care of it.
Blood Sect disciples, order!
End the fight quickly,
leave no one alive!
This Fan Ling
really is insatiable.
But this is a good opportunity for us.
By taking advantage of them fighting each other,
our chance of success will naturally increase.
En.
Teacher is right.
Junior Sect Leader, be careful!
Boss, go!
Bone Explosion!
Dammit,
don’t let him run away!
Aye.
If you kill me,
you can just wait for the Black Skull Tomb’s ceaseless revenge!
Aiyo,
I’m so scared.
But after killing you,
who will know that it’s us who did it?
Alright,
I’ll stop playing with you.
Heh.
Three Thousand Lightning Movement
has finally fallen into my hands.
After I learn it,
even a Fight King,
what can they do against me?
After watching for so long,
it’s your turn now.
So you discovered me long ago.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Dust rains down in the deep night ♪
♪ Standing amidst stormy wind, hair blowing ♪
♪ Heavenly Flame falls; were they ever hesitant or weary ♪
♪ A touch of Sky Flame promises to follow ♪
♪ Back then our figures moved together ♪
♪ Won't let you down; in the end, part the fog before returning ♪
♪ I step through clouds and smoke, walking forward ♪
♪ Rejecting all the various pitfalls ♪
♪ Flap your wings and fly, fight without backing down ♪
♪ That Wu Tan youth is the same as before ♪
♪ Don't look back, break through to the stars' end ♪
♪ Whose support that is behind his back ♪
♪ Enough, enough, enough ♪
♪ Despite that bloodshed, that wound, that enmity ♪
♪ Never rest, forever dye the heavens ♪
♪ At the end, hold no regrets to the very end ♪