English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
Quick,
hasten the sealing!
Or else if that beast charges out, no one can stop it!
Xiao Yan,
leave this place immediately.
The sealing formation isn't completed yet.
I'll distract it for a bit longer.
Careful, behind you!
Xiao Yan,
come out at once!
Shook it off.
Awesome!
What?
Unexpectedly,
the hunter became the hunted.
But I just wasn't able to get that Han Feng killed.
Teacher,
I'm sorry.
This time I've also implicated you.
♪ In an old dream, myriad cherry blossoms fall ♪
♪ Among the galaxies, things gather and disperse time after time ♪
♪ I insist on chasing this beam of light ♪
♪ No matter how terrifying and dark the sky ♪
♪ The eternal oath surrounding you and me never changes ♪
♪ Surging like blazing fire into the air before blooming ♪
♪ That blood which boils ♪
♪ Eyes are steeped, fire actually strewn everywhere ♪
♪ Looking back, falling into the heart's abyssal stream ♪
♪ Against the wind, undergo rebirth midst downfall ♪
♪ On the journey, that person in the distance ♪
♪ will keep firmly believing ♪
♪ On the journey, that person from the past ♪
♪ sustains the original intention ♪
Battle Through The Heavens
Jia Nan Academy
Episode 1
Xiao Yan completed the Three Year Agreement.
However, he formed an irreconcilable
enmity with the Misty Cloud Sect
and was forced to leave the Jia Ma Empire.
This caused him to truly recognize
that only by constantly growing stronger
could he protect the people he cares about.
The next destination, Jia Nan Academy.
What kinds of challenges and dilemmas will Xiao Yan face?
A new adventure
is about to begin.
And then I stopped following him,
returning to fulfill my orders.
The Misty Cloud Sect has been resting on
its laurels, holding on to the Jia Ma Empire.
Ever since Yun Potian from back then,
there has never again been an outstanding talent.
But,
Brother Xiao Yan's not bad at all.
A strong practitioner like Medusa was actually willing to help him.
Young lady's sight is indeed quite good.
That young fellow,
with time,
perhaps even the clan head would not dare underestimate him.
However,
that is on the precondition that he is given enough time.
Currently, those people in the clan
only look at what's in front of them.
No matter how long it takes,
I am willing to wait.
To wait until he becomes a true strong practitioner at the peak.
Ai.
Xiao Yan,
even if Young Lady is willing to wait,
if you are not able to become stronger as quickly as possible,
with Young Lady's talent and beauty
as well as the power behind her,
do you know how many hardships
you and Young Lady will have to face?
Old Ling,
do you know where Brother Xiao Yan is now?
It may not be long before Young Master
Xiao Yan comes to Jia Nan Academy.
For this period of time,
Old Ling should find a place outside the Academy to get some rest.
If there are no urgent matters,
there's no need to sneak into the Academy.
Although those old men try to curry favor with my clan,
when it comes to the Academy rules,
they are actually very strict.
Alright.
If there's anything, Young Lady should use the bell to call me.
I will hurry over immediately.
Brother Xiao Yan.
I'm waiting for you.
Junior Xun'er,
what a coincidence.
You have also just come down
from the mountain after training?
En.
Senior Bai Shan,
Bai Shan
Xun'er still has something to do.
I will leave first.
Instructor Ruo Lin!
Ruo Lin
Xun'er!
I was just looking for you.
What is it, Instructor Ruo Lin?
In half a month's time will be the
Academy's Qualifying Competition.
You should know
that the top twenty will be eligible to
enter the Inner Academy to train.
Originally, you could've participated last year,
but you actually gave it up.
Last year Xun'er was just a newcomer,
how could I dare to compete with my seniors?
Oh, please.
Would I not know what you're really thinking?
Aren't you just waiting for that fellow to participate together?
Xiao Yan, that stinky brat,
actually made a fool out of me.
That one year leave of his,
I had to bear heaps of pressure in order to settle it.
Yet to this day I haven't even seen him!
I'm infuriated.
If it wasn't for you pestering me all day,
I would've long ago had his name crossed out.
Instructor Ruo Lin,
please don't worry.
This year, Brother Xiao Yan will definitely come.
He's already missed two years of Academy training.
Even if he comes, I think it'd be for nothing.
This time, to obtain a qualifying spot,
even a Fight Grandmaster's strength may not be enough.
Instructor Ruo Lin,
you shouldn't underestimate Brother Xiao Yan.
Back then, relying on just a Fight Practitioner's strength,
he was able to endure twenty exchanges with you.
If it wasn't for this,
would I let him take a year off
and even let him stand me up?
Xiao Yan
is that freshman who took a full two years' leave, huh.
I'd like to see
on what basis you've let Junior Xun'er care this much about you.
Xiao Yan,
Coming up next is the gateway to the Black Corner Region,
the Black Region's Great Plains.
Quickly retract your Purple Cloud Wings.
Why?
Black Corner Region is a famed chaotic region on the Continent.
Flying Fight Techniques like the Purple Cloud Wings are rare goods;
if it gets seen by some strong practitioner,
you'd be asking to be killed.
Looks like this damned place
really is boundlessly chaotic.
I am just passing by this place
and only wish to replenish supplies.
Sir, what is the meaning of this?
Don't tell me you're a novice who's entering
the Black Corner Region for the first time?
Not even knowing the rule that, before entering the tribal camp,
you first have to hand over a road fee from one hundred meters away?
Road fee?
Five hundred gold coins.
Hurry up!
Don't waste my time.
It can't be that you're not even able to afford the road fee?
What a strange rule.
Open the gate.
Come on in,
novice fellow.
Come have a look, have a look
We have good stuff, come
Ah,
it's pretty lively.
I should firstly buy a new map.
The map Old Hai gave doesn't have precise
routes in the Black Region's Great Plains.
Superior goods,
superior goods!
After running around for most of the day,
it turns out not a single shop sells maps?
Let's see if I'll get lucky over there.
Brothers, what is going on?
We're all on the same side,
let's talk it out!
Less of this “brothers” nonsense,
hand over everything,
or else all of you will die!
How am I going more and more astray?
I'm almost out of the camp at this point.
I- Didn't I already pay the road fees?
That paltry amount of money,
do you take me for a beggar?
Let's go.
Don't meddle.
Sorry,
I didn't see anything.
Big Brother,
En.
Kid,
where are you going?
It's your unlucky day,
hand over everything you have!
This grandfather will spare your life.
What if I'm not willing?
Are you tired of living?
Go, together!
Sir,
please wait, Sir!
Just then Sir really helped me out.
Otherwise, the outcome would have been unimaginable.
I was only protecting myself.
Duo Ma
Please wait, Sir.
Seeing as Sir is young and talented, I'd like to invite Sir to a drink.
Sorry,
I need to be on my way.
No time.
Sir is trying to hurry to Black Mark City, right?
How do you know?
Recently, Black Mark City has been preparing to hold an auction.
Most of the passersby here are heading there to hunt for some treasure.
How about it?
I didn't guess incorrectly, right?
Perhaps Sir does not know,
this Black Region's Great Plains often has Black Storms.
If you were to encounter one, you will most likely lose your way.
How about
I hire Sir as a guard for my merchant group
and you can travel with us?
This will save you a great deal of trouble from detours.
Go with him,
he is most likely just a normal merchant.
This way, we can also save some energy.
Then,
alright.
Heh,
I look forward to working together.
My name is Duo Ma.
Yao Yan.
Apologies, Mr. Yao Yan,
I was a little busy.
I should briefly explain to Mr. Yao Yan
the situation in the Black Corner Region.
All of this is the Black Corner Region.
It is occupied by many strong powers.
This is our merchant group's destination,
Black Mark City.
It is next to the famous Jia Nan Academy.
It's controlled by a long-standing power called the Eight Gates.
The strength of their leader, Yuan Yi,
ranks amongst the top ten of the Black Ranking.
Black Ranking?
That is a ranking of strong practitioners in the Black Corner Region,
but the competition for it is extremely intense.
Getting onto the ranking isn't easy.
Oh.
Then the current Black Ranking,
who are the top rankers?
As for this,
the first and second are very mysterious.
I only know that the third rank is
an impressive strong practitioner.
It is said that his strength was at the
peak of Fight Emperor long ago,
and he is also adept at alchemy.
People call him “Medicine Emperor.”
Medicine Emperor.
This nickname sounds quite hefty.
What is his real name?
Let me think,
his name should be...
should be Han Feng.
Teacher,
what is it?
Brother Yao Yan,
are you alright?
Nothing.
That auction you mentioned before,
Oh no!
A Black Storm is coming!
Quick, quickly stop the carriages!
Quick, quickly find cover to hide behind!
Go there!
There!
Quick!
Here, here!
Rock!
Quick, quick!
Hammer,
hammer!
Hurry up!
Quick!
Quickly surround it!
Secure the carriages,
tie up the horses!
The goods are tied down!
It's coming!
Quickly hide!
Quickly hide.
Hold on!
That thing is coming.
Little fellow,
quickly conceal yourself.
Teacher,
what's coming?
Don't-
Don't come over!
A spiritual body like Teacher?
But it should only be at the level of Fight Spirit.
You- just who are you?
There are no grudges between us,
why are you hunting me down?
I'll fight.
Let me go.
Regardless of how accomplished and tyrannical you were while alive,
once you become a spiritual body,
you become the prey of my Hall of Souls.
Not spiritual bodies.
Teacher,
Teacher?
Just who is he?
This fellow,
looks like he's going to be knocked out all the way till Black Mark City.
But what was that thing yesterday?
After it appeared, why is it
that Teacher has never spoken again?
Unexpectedly, the reach of those fellows
has already extended to the vicinity of Jia Ma Empire.
Teacher, you're finally talking?
Those fellows,
who are they?
Little fellow,
some things I was planning to tell you only after you became stronger.
But unexpectedly, my whereabouts have now been discovered by them.
My original plan has also been broken.
Because the underlying force involved is too great,
far surpassing the Misty Cloud Sect.
Even I am unable to do anything.
Are you sure
you still want to know?
Teacher,
please tell me.
Although I don't know
just how strong that force is,
I just want to say,
I
am your disciple.
My abilities have been given to me by you.
Good.
I, Yao Chen, have not been blind a second time.
Yao Chen,
was this Teacher's name in the past?
Little fellow,
I remember I once told you,
on the vast Dou Qi Continent, strong practitioners
are as numerous as the clouds
and they have produced many strange forces.
The Hall of Souls is one of them.
They are extremely strong and mysterious
and expressly sense and hunt down living souls like me
who have lost their physical body but
whose spirits are unusually strong.
Back then, I was lucky to escape their encirclement;
by hiding myself in this black ring refined
from temperate Acceptance Spirit.
I am lucky to still be alive today.
I have been intent on reviving as soon as possible
because I fear them finding me.
Of course, I also have some matters and grievances to resolve.
Teacher, rest assured.
I will obtain the Fallen Heart Flame as quickly as possible
to refine a body for you.
Everything is up to you.
If I appear again,
once they lock down your position,
both of our lives will be in danger.
Strength.
I need strength.
“Black Mark City”
Move aside,
move aside!
Move aside.
Move aside!
The Blood Sect's people are here.
How long did I sleep for?
Ah,
we've arrived at Black Mark City?
Let's go,
enter the city.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Dust rains down in the deep night ♪
♪ Standing amidst stormy wind, hair blowing ♪
♪ Heavenly Flame falls; were they ever hesitant or weary ♪
♪ A touch of Sky Flame promises to follow ♪
♪ Back then our figures moved together ♪
♪ Won't let you down; in the end, part the fog before returning ♪
♪ I step through clouds and smoke, walking forward ♪
♪ Rejecting all the various pitfalls ♪
♪ Flap your wings and fly, fight without backing down ♪
♪ That Wu Tan youth is the same as before ♪
♪ Don't look back, break through to the stars' end ♪
♪ Whose support that is behind his back ♪
♪ Enough, enough, enough ♪
♪ Despite that bloodshed, that wound, that enmity ♪
♪ Never rest, forever dye the heavens ♪
♪ At the end, hold no regrets to the very end ♪