English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ In an old dream, myriad cherry blossoms fall ♪
♪ Among the galaxies, things gather and disperse time after time ♪
♪ I insist on chasing this beam of light ♪
♪ No matter how terrifying and dark the sky ♪
♪ The eternal oath surrounding you and me never changes ♪
♪ Surging like blazing fire into the air before blooming ♪
♪ That blood which boils ♪
♪ Eyes are steeped, fire actually strewn everywhere ♪
♪ Looking back, falling into the heart's abyssal stream ♪
♪ Against the wind, undergo rebirth midst downfall ♪
♪ On the journey, that person in the distance ♪
♪ will keep firmly believing ♪
♪ On the journey, that person from the past ♪
♪ sustains the original intention ♪
Battle Through The Heavens
Jia Nan Academy
Episode 13
Xiao Yan, having assembled all the new students, succeeded in
defeating the older student teams led by Su Xiao and Xiu Yan.
While everyone was cheering and celebrating,
the mysterious Black Demon Group stealthily appeared.
At a critical juncture,
Bai Shan defected last minute,
making matters worse for the new student team,
who were already weakened after a big battle.
As leader, Xiao Yan understood
that he himself must fearlessly face it all
in order to rekindle the new student team’s fighting spirit.
Looks like Brother Xiao Yan is sufficient to deal with this Sha Tie.
Not good.
Definitely can’t lose.
Actually using a Secret Technique to forcefully increase strength,
let’s see how long you last!
Give up, kid!
Leave him to me.
Your Dou Qi is nearly depleted.
Take a rest.
No need.
He was already injured by my punch earlier.
Let’s join hands
and defeat him as quickly as possible.
If we cooperate
and defeat the remaining two Black Demon Group members,
there will be a chance of victory.
This is all preconditioned on
Brother Xiao Yan being able to
hold back Sha Tie during this time.
En.
Then what’re we waiting for?
Let’s go help the new students first.
Hu Jia seems like
she can hold up a bit longer.
Got time to spectate?
Better take care of yourself!
This goddamn flame,
it burns!
Good thing I have Dou Qi Armor;
or else, just flesh
couldn’t last long, I’m afraid.
Bunch of disappointments.
You win.
We won!
Brother Xiao Yan,
are you hurt?
Nothing serious.
Xun’er.
Today
was thanks to you.
It was everyone’s joint effort.
Don’t get cocky just yet,
White Demon Group’s leader Luo Hou
has already stepped into the Fight Spirit class.
Tomorrow is the last day of the Fire Energy Hunting Competition.
You guys
won’t be able to make it past them.
It’s the last day of the Fire Energy Hunting Competition.
This Luo Hou is finally going to take some action.
Woah,
how is this group of new students so strong?
Not even the Black Demon Group was a match for them.
Right?
Let’s go.
Once,
we were not strong enough,
suffering defeat after defeat.
Once,
someone amongst us fled from battle.
But we never gave up
and will never compromise.
Fighting alongside one another,
we crushed the arrogant older student teams one by one underneath our feet.
Today,
we will face the Hunting Competition’s strongest enemies.
I believe,
as long as we unite as one,
we will be able to use victory
to build the new students’ momentum,
to proclaim the new students’ strength!
White Demon Group leader,
Luo Hou.
New student team leader,
Xiao Yan.
Looks like a fight today is unavoidable.
Hmph.
If you know what’s good for you,
then obediently hand over the Fire Energy.
Or else, soon you’ll only be able to crawl back to the Inner Academy.
This is going to be a good show.
Since there’s no room for negotiation,
we have no choice but to wrong you.
Hmph.
Presumptuous new students.
I’ll block Xiao Yan’s group of four.
You all intercept the rest of the new students.
During battle, remember not to split up.
Although the new students have numbers,
they don’t know how to cooperate.
With the advantage of integrating your same-affinity Dou Qi,
your odds are quite good.
Yes.
Atai,
the other four older students,
I’ll leave them to you guys.
Rest assured,
Senior Xiao Yan.
Brothers,
let’s make them witness
the strength of us new students!
Will you attack one by one
or as a group?
It’s the last fight,
no holding back.
Make it quick.
Go!
Understood!
Allow me to meet you.
Not too shabby.
Don’t forget Senior Xiao Yan’s plan,
we mustn’t fall into disarray.
Everyone,
surround them!
Hmph.
In over your head.
Make the formation!
Now!
Flame Splitting Tsunami!
Blood Splitting Chop!
Golden Light Palm!
Quiet Woods Poisonous Snake Vine!
Circular Cold Spinning Rod!
I was careless,
actually embarrassed to this extent by you four.
Senior Luo Hou,
although you are a Fight Spirit practitioner,
us four Fight Grandmasters joining hands
won’t be easy to deal with.
Is that so.
These new students
won’t be able to hold on for much longer, I’m afraid.
Once these four members of the White Demon Group are freed up,
Xiao Yan’s group will no longer have any chance of turning things around.
On solid ground,
I may not be able to withstand your combined attack.
But here,
heh.
Brother Xiao Yan,
looks like he destroyed the bridge on purpose.
Ice affinity Dou Qi
has a huge advantage on water.
We have to be careful.
Mr. Luo,
don’t get too confident.
The winner isn’t decided yet.
Arrogant new students,
today,
I will make you suffer an undeniable defeat!
Watch out!
Brother Xiao Yan,
we can’t continue like this.
Flame Splitting Tsunami!
Good.
You still have the strength to fight back.
Pity,
the show isn’t over yet.
Die!
Not good.
Everyone, watch out!
Xun’er!
Xun’er,
are you alright?
I’m okay.
I will make him pay.
You guys, step back.
It’s time
for this fight to end.
What kind of flame is this,
actually able to disturb my internal Dou Qi circulation?
He—
he is actually trying to merge the Heavenly Flame with another flame?
This crazy kid,
should we intervene to stop him?
He seems to be confident.
How?
Even a Fight Emperor would not dare do such a thing!
You and I both know that once a Heavenly Flame goes out of control,
its destructive power is unimaginable!
Wait and see.
Go,
Angry Buddha Fire Lotus!
Come.
I’d like to see,
Xiao Yan,
just how strong you are!
I’m definitely not going to lose to a new student!
Time to end things.
Not good.
This—
is it that fellow Xiao Yan making a commotion again?
Looks like he went easy on us.
Brother Xiao Yan.
Little fellow,
congratulations.
I announce,
for this year’s Fire Energy Hunting Competition,
the new students win!
Elder,
I haven’t lost yet!
Silence.
Have you not been shamed enough?
Wonderful,
we won!
We new students won!
We won!
Brother Xiao Yan,
what’s wrong?
I’m okay.
Not bad, Xiao Yan.
Xun’er’s sight is indeed good.
However,
I will train hard to catch up to you.
Don’t give all the credit to me;
without your help,
I wouldn’t be able to make it here, no matter how strong I am.
Lone heroes
cannot make it far here
and are not suited to this place.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Dust rains down in the deep night ♪
♪ Standing amidst stormy wind, hair blowing ♪
♪ Heavenly Flame falls; were they ever hesitant or weary ♪
♪ A touch of Sky Flame promises to follow ♪
♪ Back then our figures moved together ♪
♪ Won’t let you down; in the end, part the fog before returning ♪
♪ I step through clouds and smoke, walking forward ♪
♪ Rejecting all the various pitfalls ♪
♪ Flap your wings and fly, fight without backing down ♪
♪ That Wu Tan youth is the same as before ♪
♪ Don’t look back, break through to the stars’ end ♪
♪ Whose support that is behind his back ♪
♪ Enough, enough, enough ♪
♪ Despite that bloodshed, that wound, that enmity ♪
♪ Never rest, forever dye the heavens ♪
♪ At the end, hold no regrets to the very end ♪