English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ In an old dream, myriad cherry blossoms fall ♪
♪ Among the galaxies, things gather and disperse time after time ♪
♪ I insist on chasing this beam of light ♪
♪ No matter how terrifying and dark the sky ♪
♪ The eternal oath surrounding you and me never changes ♪
♪ Surging like blazing fire into the air before blooming ♪
♪ That blood which boils ♪
♪ Eyes are steeped, fire actually strewn everywhere ♪
♪ Looking back, falling into the heart's abyssal stream ♪
♪ Against the wind, undergo rebirth midst downfall ♪
♪ On the journey, that person in the distance ♪
♪ will keep firmly believing ♪
♪ On the journey, that person from the past ♪
♪ sustains the original intention ♪
Battle Through The Heavens
Jia Nan Academy
Episode 7
Through his outstanding ability to control fire,
Xiao Yan achieved victory over fellow alchemist Lu Mu,
becoming famous in a single battle.
The current Xiao Yan
finally used his strength to repay Xun’er’s faith
and swore to Xun’er that he would never leave her,
no matter how enormous the power behind her was.
The fighting is far from over.
Stronger opponents had already been eyeing Xiao Yan.
This Wu Hao has just hurried back
from the Black Corner Region, right.
What a dense bloody aura.
I forgot to tell you,
this Wu Hao was once one of Xun’er’s suitors.
However, due to your appearance, he failed.
I will prove
that Xun’er did not make the wrong choice.
Not going to concede?
Just fight.
I’d like to see
just how strong the Blood Asura actually is!
I—
I surrender!
Wu Hao wins!
You are Xiao Yan?
Do you dare come down to fight with me?
This is going to be interesting;
just who is stronger, this Xiao Yan or the Blood Asura?
Look at that Xiao Yan,
only knowing how to hide behind women.
What a pussy.
Go on, fight.
Hopefully both get injured,
allowing me to save some energy.
Both of you,
settle down.
It is now the Qualifying Competition,
not a place for private challenges.
Tomorrow is the Qualifying Competition’s final day;
at that time, there will naturally be an opportunity for you to fight each other.
Don’t disappoint me tomorrow.
I hope that the person Xun’er waited so long for
isn’t trash.
The competition will continue!
For real?
Of course.
Xiao Mei
Brother Xiao Yan,
if you want to know my current strength,
just wait until tomorrow’s competition.
You girl,
if you had shown your full power,
that opponent today, I’m afraid,
wouldn’t have been able to endure a single exchange.
Cousin Xiao Yan,
long time no see.
Long time no see, indeed.
There’s still the competition tomorrow,
we will go back to get some rest.
Then please get some rest.
Actually,
Xiao Mei isn’t a bad person.
En.
I know.
Those are all things of the past;
I’ve already let go of them.
At this rate of training progress,
it’ll probably take another ten days before
I can reach Six-star Fight Grandmaster.
Father,
I will find you.
No matter who it was that abducted you,
in the future,
they must pay the price.
This jade piece
can actually resist my Green Lotus Core Flame?
Exactly what special properties does it have?
Teacher.
What is it, Teacher?
I am unable to sense
the aura of the Fallen Heart Flame in Jia Nan Academy.
Could it be
that it has already been snatched by others?
That should not be the case.
Although I am unable to sense its aura for certain,
by relying on the unique attraction between Heavenly Flames,
the Bone Chilling Flame has vaguely detected
that within a thousand miles of the Academy
there remain faint traces of the Fallen Heart Flame.
Within a thousand miles?
Just how long would we have to search for?
Those old fellows at Jia Nan Academy,
there’s no way they haven’t become aware
of the Fallen Heart Flame’s existence.
I’ve always felt that the Inner Academy and
Fallen Heart Flame have some relation.
If you are able enter the Inner Academy,
we can probably better ascertain the aura’s location.
Inner Academy.
I hope it won’t disappoint me.
Why do I feel like
there are far more spectators today
compared to the last two days?
But of course.
Today is the final elimination competition to pick five out of twenty.
Naturally, nobody wants to miss the most exciting showdown.
Look, look, he’s here!
Really? Where is he?
Let me see!
So handsome!
Bai Shan! I believe you will definitely be the champion this year!
Kid,
I want your reputation to be destroyed today.
Brother Xiao Yan,
this Bai Shan has high achievements in terms of training talent.
He is quite strong.
You must be careful when you meet him.
Don’t worry, girl.
I know.
Xun’er!
Xun’er.
Xun’er,
today, we all have to do our best
to enter the top five.
As for stinky men, forget about them.
See how I take care of you later.
Did I offend her somewhere?
This is the Outer Academy Deputy
Headmaster’s granddaughter, Hu Jia.
She possesses extremely strong talent that is not inferior to yours.
However, she has an odd personality
and is very stubborn.
People call her “Little Witch.”
This Little Witch sure is macho.
Her reputation truly is well-deserved.
Everyone knows
that in previous years, the Inner Academy Qualifying
Competition consisted entirely of one on one battles.
Whoever ranks higher,
the training resources they obtain from
now on will naturally be greater.
But for the competition this time,
we have decided to change the rules.
They changed the rules?
It’s not clear.
Just what are the Elders thinking?
Now
can the top twenty students please enter the arena.
All twenty people at once?
Go, Bai Shan!
Go, Hu Jia!
Hu Jia! My goddess!
Let’s go.
Do your best.
This year
we will no longer have single elimination rounds
but rather, a battle royale filled with hot blood and excitement.
Whoever can last longer in the competition
will have a higher ranking.
The other way is also true.
How do we fight?
Exactly.
This change to the rules is way too sudden!
Right?
Why did they change the rules?
How are we going to fight!
Whether you fight alone or join hands to attack,
it is all allowed.
We can join hands?
Girl,
then wouldn’t we be able to fight side by side?
But this kind of mode
isn’t necessarily advantageous for us.
The Academy’s most outstanding, like Bai Shan, Hu Jia and Wu Hao,
are able to find allies more easily.
It looks like your prestige in the Academy is quite high.
Couldn’t you also gather up some people?
If it was in the past
there would indeed be people who come to guard the flower.
But now, the flower has an owner.
Why would they come?
No worries.
Just me is enough.
No matter the surging waves ahead,
we will push through together.
Good.
Then I will announce,
the final elimination round
starts now!
Brother Xiao Yan,
how will we fight?
Wait first.
You, follow me in attacking.
The rest of you, defend against sneak attackers.
Yes.
Junior Hu Jia,
how about I protect you?
Very good.
Just like that.
Don’t attack carelessly.
Deputy Headmaster’s idea is not bad.
It may not be completely fair,
but it can develop a person’s cautious
mentality and ability to cooperate.
I just got bored of past one on one battles.
Just wanted to try changing things up.
However, for students who are not good at communicating,
in this kind of situation where you are
surrounded by enemies on all sides,
they will have a harder time, I’m afraid.
Some people have already fallen in such a short time?
Brother Xiao Yan,
who will be our next opponent?
It’s your turn at last.
Everyone else,
hold back Junior Xun’er.
Let me deal with that Xiao Yan.
Yes.
Girl,
be careful.
They are the ones who should be careful.
Xun’er!
Don’t think that just because you defeated Lu Mu, you are able to run wild.
There are many people stronger than him in Jia Nan Academy.
I want to have you, Xiao Yan,
be defeated by me in front of everyone.
I want you to know
that you
are not worthy of Xun’er!
Can’t delay any longer.
Using it so soon..?
Shaking Lightning Arc Blast!
Brother Xiao Yan!
This flame.
The green colored flame on that Xiao Yan’s body
should be
a Heavenly Flame, right?
With a temperature that can cause us to feel heart palpitations,
it is indeed a Heavenly Flame.
This Xiao Yan,
my Alchemy Department wants him.
As long as he does not delay his training at the Inner Academy,
I earnestly wish for the Academy to have another outstanding alchemist.
Did that feel good?
Next,
it’s my turn.
Shit!
Crazy fellow,
actually pushing Bai Shan to this point.
That Xiao Yan’s punches are so rapid
because
he ditched the heavy ruler, right?
Should be.
Presumably, he normally always carries
the heavy ruler in order to train.
How is this guy so fast?
This is...
Damn it.
Why does it have to be now, of all times.
He’s about to advance.
If there is interference during advancement,
at best he will be injured, at worst he may die.
Looks like this little fellow will have to withdraw.
What a pity.
Xiao Yan,
see?
Even the heavens are helping me.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Dust rains down in the deep night ♪
♪ Standing amidst stormy wind, hair blowing ♪
♪ Heavenly Flame falls; were they ever hesitant or weary ♪
♪ A touch of Sky Flame promises to follow ♪
♪ Back then our figures moved together ♪
♪ Won’t let you down; in the end, part the fog before returning ♪
♪ I step through clouds and smoke, walking forward ♪
♪ Rejecting all the various pitfalls ♪
♪ Flap your wings and fly, fight without backing down ♪
♪ That Wu Tan youth is the same as before ♪
♪ Don’t look back, break through to the stars’ end ♪
♪ Whose support that is behind his back ♪
♪ Enough, enough, enough ♪
♪ Despite that bloodshed, that wound, that enmity ♪
♪ Never rest, forever dye the heavens ♪
♪ At the end, hold no regrets to the very end ♪