English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ In an old dream, myriad cherry blossoms fall ♪
♪ Among the galaxies, things gather and disperse time after time ♪
♪ I insist on chasing this beam of light ♪
♪ No matter how terrifying and dark the sky ♪
♪ The eternal oath surrounding you and me never changes ♪
♪ Surging like blazing fire into the air before blooming ♪
♪ That blood which boils ♪
♪ Eyes are steeped, fire actually strewn everywhere ♪
♪ Looking back, falling into the heart's abyssal stream ♪
♪ Against the wind, undergo rebirth midst downfall ♪
♪ On the journey, that person in the distance ♪
♪ will keep firmly believing ♪
♪ On the journey, that person from the past ♪
♪ sustains the original intention ♪
Battle Through The Heavens
Jia Nan Academy
Episode 2
Black Corner Region.
A lawless place that had formed outside of Jia Nan Academy.
Here, it is chaotic and turbulent
with no morality to speak of.
Various powers, for the sake of personal gain,
are constantly competing,
killing,
fighting only for themselves.
Countless rare Fight Techniques
and precious treasures
flow through various channels into this place,
attracting hordes of practitioners to contest for them.
Xiao Yan and Duo Ma finally arrived at Black Mark City.
This is a place where prosperity and disorder
intermingle within the Black Corner Region.
While parting ways,
Xiao Yan was told that the biggest medicine house
in the city has various rare pills and herbs.
But its high prices caused the visiting Xiao Yan to be deterred.
Under Yao Lao's suggestion,
the cash-strapped Xiao Yan could only refine
Green Spirit Pills to exchange for gold.
In order to refine these Green Spirit Pills,
I even got my cauldron broken.
Ugh.
Hopefully they'll auction for a good price.
The ingredients for Spiritual Recovery Purple Pill
should no longer be much of a problem.
But, I previously forgot to tell you,
since you've set your sights on the Fallen Heart Flame,
then, similar to swallowing the Green Lotus Core Flame back then,
you'll have to prepare a kind of Tier 6 pill,
Ground Spirit Pill.
Good thing Teacher brought this up.
Then what
ingredients do we need to prepare?
As for ingredients, there aren't many,
only four of them.
Flame Core ‎Ganoderma,
Asparagus Ice Fire Fruit,
Green Wood Celestial Vine,
and
a Rank 6 Water-type Monster Core.
Rank 6 Monster Core?
That's from a Rank 6 super beast that can rival a Fight Emperor.
Even if you're courting death—not like this, right?
I can only take it one step at a time.
Also,
Black Mark City's auction this time is
reportedly hosted by the Eight Gates.
They are the people in power here.
Auction House
After entering,
make sure to be extremely vigilant.
En.
To think, the Eight Gates actually have
Fight Masters acting as Black Mark City guards.
Sure enough, their power is formidable.
Move aside.
Move aside!
Out of the way!
Move aside, move aside!
Get lost.
It's him.
Fan Ling
Strength of a Fight Spirit,
yet this young.
Looks like this Black Corner Region
really is filled with hidden dragons and crouching tigers.
It's those abnormal fellows.
That person in the middle
is the Blood Sect's Junior Sect Leader, Fan Ling, right?
Isn't there enmity between Blood Sect and the Eight Gates?
Why have they still come to Black Mark City?
Is there anything he's afraid of?
His father is a strong practitioner ranked fifth on the Black Ranking;
moreover, the Blood Sect's power exceeds that of the Eight Gates.
Who would dare lay a hand on him here?
Move aside.
Ah!
Junior Sect Leader,
I- I didn't mean to!
Please spare me,
please spare me!
Careful.
Go.
What are you doing?
Don't!
Junior Sect Leader!
Ahh!
This Blood Sect
really is vicious.
This size
far surpasses the Miteer Family's auction.
It should be here.
I have goods
I'd like to have the auction house auction off.
Don't waste my time taking out anything valued at less than 100,000 gold.
Take a look first.
Appraiser
Move it forward.
This medicinal fragrance
is pleasant and mellow,
delightful and heavenly.
It is simply refreshing to the core.
Two-Lined Green Spirit Pill
is worth some money,
but it is not particularly rare.
Fortunately, there are two of them.
Then just have them sold as a set.
Take a look at that bottle as well.
Three-Lined Green Spirit Pill?!
Excellent stuff;
once it is consumed
not only can it break through the cultivation barrier,
but it can also cause one's strength to skyrocket by three stars.
Compared to the Two-Lined Green Spirit Pill,
its side effects can also be disregarded.
Now
is it worth wasting your time?
This young man,
the old me was oblivious;
I've been remiss.
Come, come, come,
have a seat.
Please have some tea.
An alchemist who can refine a Three-Lined Green Spirit Pill
is not often seen in the Black Corner Region.
Leader would probably be interested in this kind of person.
How about this, young man.
The pair of Two-Lined Green Spirit Pills,
the starting price will be set at 300,000 gold.
And for this Three-Lined Green Spirit Pill,
its starting price can perhaps be set at 700,000.
After undergoing competing bids...
Elder Qing
Mo Er Han
Junior Sect Leader Fan,
please.
Looks like
the Blood Sect has also come for that treasure.
Guest,
please.
Junior Sect Leader,
is something wrong?
That fellow on the other side,
I've encountered him previously.
Every time I meet him,
I have a kind of strange
feeling of fear.
Junior Sect Leader may be imagining things.
Our Blood Sect's Qi method is exceptionally dark and cold;
the only things that can instill fear in us are some extreme flames.
But flames of that level,
even in the entire Black Corner Region,
not many people possess them.
This black-robed person
is clearly not among them.
Huh.
Maybe.
Did that intel turn out to be true?
If it is,
Father said
that no matter the cost,
we have to obtain it.
Rest assured, Junior Sect Leader,
Blood Sect
Elder
the Sect Leader has already secretly made preparations.
Even if that thing falls into the hands of other people,
they won't be able to step beyond a
ten mile radius of Black Mark City.
Ladies and gentlemen, you've been waiting!
Auctioneer
This auction, organized by our Eight Gates,
will definitely not disappoint you all.
Without further delay,
the Black Mark City auction
begins now!
The first treasure
is two tablets of something that can help with
breaking through a cultivation barrier,
the Two-Lined Green Spirit Pill.
Each pill's starting price:
300,000.
330,000!
350,000.
370,000.
390,000!
400,000!
Looks like I'll have the money to buy
Spiritual Recovery Purple Pill ingredients.
550,000.
He's also interested in the Green Spirit Pill?
600,000.
Sorry,
when my Black Skull Tomb finds something good,
we won't be polite.
650,000!
1 million.
The Black Skull Tomb really does have deep pockets.
Not at all.
Offering 1 million for a single Two-Lined Green Spirit Pill,
I'm afraid only Black Skull Tomb idiots would do such a thing.
1.5 million!
1.5 million?!
This much?
Junior Sect Leader,
what- what's wrong?
Hey,
given that Junior Sect Leader wants it so badly,
I'll just let you have it.
1.5 million, sold!
A pair of Two-Lined Green Spirit Pills,
the total is 3 million!
That goddamned Mo Er Han,
just you wait!
How exciting.
This fool
looks a lot more pleasing to the eye now.
Congratulations to this sir for winning the Two-Lined Green Spirit Pill.
Let's take a look at the next treasure,
Three-Lined Green Spirit Pill!
Its starting price is 700,000.
900,000.
1 million.
Congratulations to the Sky Serpent Mansion on winning
the Three-Lined Green Spirit Pill for 1.5 million.
Sky Serpent Mansion.
Little fellow,
you once exchanged blows with the Sky Serpent Mansion,
have you forgotten?
Exchanged blows.
It was that mysterious woman.
En.
They are part of the Sky Serpent Mansion.
Qing Lin
is in their hands...
No need to worry too much about that little girl.
Her extraordinary pupils
will compel the Sky Serpent Mansion to spend
the utmost effort to treat and raise her.
I hope so.
If there's an opportunity in the future,
I am still going to look for her.
This woman is also trying to snatch
the Green Spirit Pill from me?
But, no matter.
Those who snatch from me,
I will have all of them spit it out later.
The next thing to be auctioned is a bit odd
as even we haven't ascertained just what use this thing has.
Purifying Demonic Lotus Flame?
Isn't this just a tattered rag?
However,
based on the markings on it, we can confidently say
this is a cloth piece containing a secret.
It should be a fragment of an ancient map.
Perhaps
it can help us find some kind of ancient treasure.
Little fellow,
your luck is quite good.
You've run into another fragment of the map marking
the position of the Purifying Demonic Lotus Flame.
En.
Those who want to test their luck, take a shot!
Starting price,
100,000 gold.
Aiya.
110,000.
Is he sick in the head?
Right?
Has money to burn.
Yo, yo, yo.
Give it a shot,
your donkey cart might become a horse-drawn carriage!
Is there anyone else who'd like to post a price?
130,000.
I've suddenly taken a little interest in this thing.
Junior Sect Leader,
is a tattered piece of cloth worth this price?
Shut up.
150,000.
200,000.
Don't compete anymore.
Or else, I'm afraid, the map fragment's true value will be exposed.
At that point, it's possible that other powers will also join in.
Then what?
Are we just going to let this map slip away before our very eyes?
Since he wants it, then let's give it to him for now.
After all, there's no way he'll be able to discover its secret.
Once the auction ends, let's think of something.
Congratulations to Junior Sect Leader Fan,
winning a mysterious treasure with limitless potential!
Congratulations to the mister in Balcony #4
for winning the Flame Core ‎Ganoderma.
Finally gained a little something tonight.
This auction,
coming here was the right choice.
With the Flame Core Ganoderma,
we've taken another step towards refining the Ground Spirit Pill.
Everyone,
next to be auctioned is
a Low Di Agility Fight Technique,
Three Thousand Lightning Movement.
By learning this technique,
your movements will be as quick as lightning.
It is so fast that even when fighting across classes,
you can still remain invincible.
Di Class Agility Technique
perfectly remedies the flaws in my Black Skull Tomb's Qi method.
This treasure,
I'm going to take it!
Di Class?
Someone would actually take out this
level of Fight Technique for auction?
Wonder who this spendthrift is.
Goods auctioned in the Black Corner Region
are mostly criminal goods obtained through shady means.
Not daring to practice it themselves
and fearing being discovered by others,
they can only take it out for auction.
Although I am very interested in this
Three Thousand Lightning Movement,
it's clear
that I won't get the chance to compete.
This item will not have a set starting price;
the highest bidder wins!
I bid 5 million gold.
5 million right away?!
Do they have a gold mine at home?
I'm afraid this Fight Technique is going to fall into
the hands of a wealthy and powerful person again!
It's uncommon for everyone to be this excited.
Let me join in on the fun too.
5.1 million.
En.
What a sweet fragrance.
Now that a beauty has intentions,
I can't be lazy.
5.2 million.
Hmph.
8 million.
8 million?
That's equivalent to several years of the Miteer Family's total income.
This bit of wealth can't be considered unusual in the Black Corner Region.
8.1 million.
I'm just curious,
this Di Class Fight Technique is only the second to last item for auction;
then the last item,
what kind of earth-shattering treasure will it be?
10 million!
The Black Skull Tomb really is filthy rich.
10 million gold,
I give up.
Spending so much money on a technique,
let's see what you'll take out to contest with me for the final treasure.
Haven't announced the result yet?
Di Class Fight Technique, Three Thousand Lightning Movement,
Black Skull Tomb's Mo Er Han is the ultimate winner!
Congratulations,
congratulations!
Now this is a real fight.
10 million gold.
So mysterious?
Ever since the protective barrier went up,
I've sensed the appearance of a few concealed auras in the auction house.
One of the auras is not any weaker than Hai Bodong;
it must be the Leader of the Eight Gates.
Just what is this rare treasure,
actually compelling the Eight Gates' Leader to personally sit in.
Wait and see,
I believe it won't disappoint.
Ladies and gentlemen,
what's about to come on stage
is this auction's
grand finale treasure.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Dust rains down in the deep night ♪
♪ Standing amidst stormy wind, hair blowing ♪
♪ Heavenly Flame falls; were they ever hesitant or weary ♪
♪ A touch of Sky Flame promises to follow ♪
♪ Back then our figures moved together ♪
♪ Won't let you down; in the end, part the fog before returning ♪
♪ I step through clouds and smoke, walking forward ♪
♪ Rejecting all the various pitfalls ♪
♪ Flap your wings and fly, fight without backing down ♪
♪ That Wu Tan youth is the same as before ♪
♪ Don't look back, break through to the stars' end ♪
♪ Whose support that is behind his back ♪
♪ Enough, enough, enough ♪
♪ Despite that bloodshed, that wound, that enmity ♪
♪ Never rest, forever dye the heavens ♪
♪ At the end, hold no regrets to the very end ♪