English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ In an old dream, myriad cherry blossoms fall ♪
♪ Among the galaxies, things gather and disperse time after time ♪
♪ I insist on chasing this beam of light ♪
♪ No matter how terrifying and dark the sky ♪
♪ The eternal oath surrounding you and me never changes ♪
♪ Surging like blazing fire into the air before blooming ♪
♪ That blood which boils ♪
♪ Eyes are steeped, fire actually strewn everywhere ♪
♪ Looking back, falling into the heart's abyssal stream ♪
♪ Against the wind, undergo rebirth midst downfall ♪
♪ On the journey, that person in the distance ♪
♪ will keep firmly believing ♪
♪ On the journey, that person from the past ♪
♪ sustains the original intention ♪
Battle Through The Heavens
Jia Nan Academy
Episode 10
After saying his farewells to Instructor Ruo Lin, Xiao Yu and others,
Xiao Yan and the rest of the new students, with Deputy
Headmaster Hu Qian and the Elders escorting,
successfully arrived at the outskirts of the Inner Academy.
Harboring many doubts and curiosities,
the new students finally ushered in the last
hurdle before entering the Inner Academy:
the Fire Energy Hunting Competition.
Didn’t they say these new students were pretty strong?
But that was it.
It’s their unlucky day if they meet our Black Demon Group.
This group of old students is at a numbers disadvantage
yet they are actually able to defeat them in one strike.
Sha Tie
Boss.
Huh.
The rule that new students’ Fire Energy cannot go below two,
it’s about time they change it.
Leave.
Those guys left,
let’s stop dawdling here.
Didn’t the rules say
that those who arrive earlier obtain richer rewards?
Wait.
What’s wrong?
That team of older students just then,
its leader was half a step into Fight Spirit.
The team’s coordination isn’t weak either.
If we were to fight individually,
none of us would be a match for them.
Your point, then?
I think
we should choose a team leader to direct combat.
Otherwise, if we are uncoordinated like loose sand,
it’ll be difficult to escape those old students’ encirclement
and successfully leave the forest, I’m afraid.
Then this team leader,
who’ll it be?
I—
I vote for Brother Xiao Yan.
Fine.
On account of Xun’er,
I’ll believe you once.
Your strength,
I’m convinced.
Listening to your command for now
is fine by me.
Bai Shan, what do you think?
Fine, fine, you’ll be the team leader.
But I’ll be upfront,
don’t treat us like your pawns.
Now that I’ve become the leader,
if we run into danger, naturally I will not let you face it alone.
However,
I hope that everyone
can temporarily put aside divisions and work together.
Or else, it’ll be hard for us to rival the older students.
Brother Xiao Yan,
perhaps we should think of ways to gain
intel on the forest and these older students.
This way, we’ll be able to know the enemy
and win many battles.
En.
I was thinking the same.
Here,
only the older students are clear about
the circumstances of the competition.
Are we going to obtain intel from them?
We still don’t know what the other older student teams are like.
If they are on par with that Black Demon Group,
it’ll be troublesome.
Everyone, come with me.
I’ll use my Spiritual Perception to assess older student teams’ strength.
After finding a relatively weak older student team,
we’ll subdue them
and interrogate them.
When are we going to be able to fight?
No point in being anxious,
we can only wait for now.
There’s an opportunity.
Let’s go.
Lin Ge
Hand it over.
Leng Bai was right,
there are more new students hiding in the northern part of the forest.
Let’s go,
time to look for our next target.
No need to look.
We’re here.
Ho,
you bunch of new students sure have guts,
actually delivering yourself to us.
Boss,
these two girls are pretty nice-looking.
Better go easy on them;
otherwise, if we leave a bad impression,
we won’t have a chance in the future.
Their strength is barely around Two-star Fight Grandmaster.
Don’t drag things out,
make it quick.
Remember,
not a single one can escape!
See how I take care of them.
Overextending blokes.
Hell,
how are these new students—?
Junior, please be merciful!
You— what are you trying to do?
I ask,
you answer.
How big is this forest?
Very— very big.
Take one person each and question them on the side.
If someone’s answer differs from the rest,
don’t blame us for being ruthless.
Perfect, I didn’t get enough of it.
Be gentle, be gentle, brother!
I won’t trouble Junior Sister, I’ll walk myself!
Next question.
How many older students are participating in the Hunting Competition?
How many teams are there?
Thirty five people.
Five people a team,
seven teams total.
What is their strength like?
Are they similar to you guys?
There are four teams similar to us in strength.
The other two teams are the Black Demon Group and White Demon Group;
they are the strongest.
I think...
I think they are about the same as you.
Black Demon Group members wear black uniforms;
their leader is called Sha Tie.
Whereas the White Demon Group wears white uniforms
and their leader is Luo Hou.
In recent years,
it seems like no new student team has ever been able to get past them.
This so-called Fire Energy,
what exactly is its use in the Inner Academy?
Why are you guys so crazy about it?
I’ll talk, I’ll talk!
The Inner Academy has a Blazing Sky Qi Refining Tower;
by training inside, you can obtain the miraculous
effect of gaining with half the effort.
Fire Energy
is the fee for training there.
Very good.
I’m scared of snakes!
I won’t speak.
I’ll talk, I’ll talk!
At the start of each month,
the Inner Academy distributes seven days’ worth of
Fire Energy to each person as living expenses...
There are many ways to obtain Fire Energy in the Inner Academy;
for example, sweeping the tower, copying scrolls, hunting
Magical Beasts, challenging people, et cetera...
Junior Sister, what else would you like to know?
Feel free to ask—
How dare you call her Junior Sister?
Continue.
But the most straightforward way of earning Fire Energy
is by getting on the Inner Academy’s Strong Ranking.
That way you don’t need to worry about running out of Fire Energy.
Thank you, Seniors.
Next,
how about handing over your Fire Energy Card.
Ai,
what a pity.
We can’t actually take all of their Fire Energy;
have to leave a minimum of seven days’ Fire Energy.
Looks like the Blazing Sky Qi Refining Tower is the reason
why Inner Academy students train so quickly;
it is really quite astonishing.
Compared to Fire Energy,
I am more interested in the Strong Ranking.
After entering the Inner Academy,
I’ll look for opportunities to challenge them.
You all know the Fire Energy’s importance in the Inner Academy now.
Don’t you want to gain some more?
Who doesn’t want more?
I also wish I could get enough Fire Energy to train
in the Blazing Sky Qi Refining Tower for a year.
Then would you be willing, for the sake of Fire Energy,
to continue adventuring?
Don’t tell me you have intentions towards the other older students?
Since they can steal from us,
why can’t we steal from them?
You already heard,
besides the Black Demon Group and White Demon Group,
the other older students,
as long as they don’t launch a joint attack,
won’t be able to contend with us individually.
This is our opportunity.
How about it?
Dare to give it a try?
Brother Xiao Yan,
I’ll go with you.
No risk, no reward.
As long as you dare,
I won’t shrink back in the slightest.
Ai,
crazy fellows.
Fine.
Who made me covet Fire Energy so badly?
Let’s go.
Good.
Then it’s decided.
Let’s go;
the hunted are about to begin seeking out the hunters.
This little fellow is called Xiao Yan, right?
Actually exploiting the Fire Energy Hunting Competition’s rules.
He’s got guts.
Elder Lu
In previous years, the Qualifying Competition’s
top five students have been quite haughty
with no one willing to listen to others.
In the end, they were split up and defeated
by the Inner Academy’s older students.
This year,
the team led by Xiao Yan
might be able to give us a surprise.
Xiao Yan.
Lin Ge’s bunch really made the older students lose face.
Not only did they have their Fire Energy stolen by new students,
they also lost in such an embarrassing way.
Liu Mu
These new students are so arrogant.
It’s about time to teach them the real rules of the Inner Academy.
What happened?
Where’d they go?
They’ve already detected us.
I’ll go after them.
I’ll go with you!
Wait!
Leave him to me.
Something’s off.
Xun’er, let’s catch up.
Hmph.
Wu Hao!
Take this!
Dammit,
we fell for their trap!
Bunch of rookies.
These bastards,
actually playing dirty!
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Dust rains down in the deep night ♪
♪ Standing amidst stormy wind, hair blowing ♪
♪ Heavenly Flame falls; were they ever hesitant or weary ♪
♪ A touch of Sky Flame promises to follow ♪
♪ Back then our figures moved together ♪
♪ Won’t let you down; in the end, part the fog before returning ♪
♪ I step through clouds and smoke, walking forward ♪
♪ Rejecting all the various pitfalls ♪
♪ Flap your wings and fly, fight without backing down ♪
♪ That Wu Tan youth is the same as before ♪
♪ Don’t look back, break through to the stars’ end ♪
♪ Whose support that is behind his back ♪
♪ Enough, enough, enough ♪
♪ Despite that bloodshed, that wound, that enmity ♪
♪ Never rest, forever dye the heavens ♪
♪ At the end, hold no regrets to the very end ♪