English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ In an old dream, myriad cherry blossoms fall ♪
♪ Among the galaxies, things gather and disperse time after time ♪
♪ I insist on chasing this beam of light ♪
♪ No matter how terrifying and dark the sky ♪
♪ The eternal oath surrounding you and me never changes ♪
♪ Surging like blazing fire into the air before blooming ♪
♪ That blood which boils ♪
♪ Eyes are steeped, fire actually strewn everywhere ♪
♪ Looking back, falling into the heart's abyssal stream ♪
♪ Against the wind, undergo rebirth midst downfall ♪
♪ On the journey, that person in the distance ♪
♪ will keep firmly believing ♪
♪ On the journey, that person from the past ♪
♪ sustains the original intention ♪
Battle Through The Heavens
Jia Nan Academy
Episode 8
The terrifying performance of Wu Hao and others
made Xiao Yan adopt a more cautious
attitude toward the rest of the competition.
The last elimination competition, which was changed
ad hoc to a battle royale, has finally begun.
Xiao Yan, cloaked in Heavenly Flame, relied on
fast attacks after ditching the Heavy Xuan Ruler
to overwhelm a strong opponent, Bai Shan.
While victory was within sight,
Xiao Yan suddenly encountered a crisis of untimely advancement.
Xiao Yan,
see?
Even the heavens are helping me.
Brother Xiao Yan,
go ahead and advance.
I will hold them back.
I’ll be quick.
If you want to try,
be my guest.
I will no longer hold anything back.
Junior Xun’er,
you—
Wu Hao!
Hu Jia!
Xiao Yan is currently undergoing a breakthrough.
Once he successfully promotes,
his strength will increase greatly.
At that point, when we fight each other,
we will definitely be no match for him and Xun’er.
Don’t tell me you want to see Xiao Yan
come out stronger, win the top five
and also enter the Book Collection Hall to obtain rewards?
Now, we are already no match for him.
If he becomes even stronger,
we will never again have the opportunity to catch up.
Don’t forget,
Xiao Yan is our common enemy.
While Xiao Yan is currently defenseless,
let us work together
to kick him out.
Okay.
Hmph.
Let’s go.
You are mine.
What,
trying to join forces?
Xun’er, don’t worry.
I’m not going to hurt you.
It’s just
that I want to toss out that fellow behind you.
That’s right.
If Junior Xun’er could please
give way temporarily.
You can go ahead and try.
Xun’er,
step aside.
Don’t protect that guy!
Three versus one?
Despicable.
They technically aren’t violating the rules.
Hopefully Xun’er can stick it out.
As long as Xiao Yan successfully advances,
all will be well.
Hu Qian,
this new mode of yours has too many loopholes.
Even a situation of three versus one has appeared.
Rules are rules;
as long as they don’t break them,
we have no right to intervene.
It’ll depend on Xiao Yan’s own good fortune.
Hopefully.
Let’s move.
Can’t delay any longer;
or else, Xiao Yan will soon successfully advance.
Junior Xun’er,
apologies.
Today, this guy must be ousted!
Go!
Golden Light Palm!
Junior Xun’er is finally fighting for real!
She’s too strong!
Xun’er, move aside!
Guardian Trigram Palm!
Junior Xun’er,
my apologies.
Today this guy must be ousted!
Xun’er!
Bai Shan,
you dare injure her?!
I only wanted to deal with Xiao Yan.
It’s because Junior Xun’er herself wanted
to protect him that she got hurt;
how can I be blamed?
No need to keep being hypocritical,
Bai Shan.
If you are able to leave the arena unscathed today,
I, Xiao Xun’er will then leave Jia Nan Academy!
Xun’er, this—
Xun’er.
The rest,
leave it to me.
Brother Xiao Yan.
They are all Five- or Six-star Fight Grandmasters.
Don’t worry.
If you are able to leave the arena unharmed today,
I, Xiao Yan,
will never again take half a step into Jia Nan Academy!
You sure talk big.
Even if you’ve now promoted to Six-star Fight Grandmaster,
trying to fight one against three,
you are seeking your own humiliation!
Xun’er getting hurt was not my original intention.
After defeating you,
I will make Bai Shan pay a price.
Count me in.
Don’t bother.
After we defeat Junior Xiao Yan,
I will voluntarily withdraw
and apologize to Junior Xun’er.
Saying these now
is too late.
Sky Fire Three Mysterious Change, First Change:
Green Lotus Change!
Fight Spirit?
That Xiao Yan
must have used some kind of Secret Technique
that can temporarily raise one’s strength.
The current Xiao Yan
already possesses a Fight Spirit’s strength, I’m afraid.
However,
the Fight Techniques displayed by Bai Shan’s group
are clearly not ordinary either.
This competition
may have come to a stalemate.
Not necessarily.
Xun’er’s injury,
I will make you doubly repay.
Good Lord,
just what kind of terrifying technique is this Xiao Yan displaying?
It is actually powerful to such an extent!
Wu Hao,
Hu Jia!
Give this arrogant brat a lesson.
Ravaging Thunder!
Blood Splitting Chop!
Quiet Woods Poisonous Snake Vine!
Watch out, Brother Xiao Yan!
Go,
Angry Buddha Fire Lotus!
This fellow
really is abnormal.
Brother Xiao Yan!
Logically speaking,
the power produced from stacking two kinds of flames
should be much greater than this.
Could it be—
Correct.
If it weren’t for Xiao Yan controlling the terrifying fire lotus’s power just now,
those three, I’m afraid...
Xiao Yan?
Looks like he’s already buried under debris from the energy explosion.
Fighting one versus three
was indeed wildly arrogant.
But you won’t meet a good ending.
Damn it,
I shouldn’t have listened to your instigation.
This Xiao Yan,
we can’t afford to mess with him!
He’s very strong,
stronger than all of us.
So what if he’s strong?
Under the combined attack of us three,
even if he was able to survive,
he should have at least broken his arms and legs.
This is payback on behalf of Xun’er.
If you can’t accept it,
I’m ready anytime.
Accept.
Are you hurt?
Xun’er isn’t that weak;
it can’t even be considered a superficial wound.
Is this competition
over now?
If not,
I can continue.
Yes.
Of course.
I announce:
this session’s Inner Academy Qualifying Competition
has now concluded.
The top five
are
Hu Jia,
Bai Shan,
Wu Hao,
Xiao Xun’er,
Xiao Yan.
Who knew
that Xiao Yan was actually this strong?
Instructor Ruo Lin,
they won!
They won!
Today’s shame,
I, Bai Shan, will definitely repay it a hundred times over!
Xiao Yan,
just you wait.
This bastard,
so ruthless.
He really isn’t a man.
Xiao Yan,
you are very strong.
But I believe,
I will definitely surpass you.
I wonder
just what kinds of treasures
are in that Book Collection Hall.
Hopefully we can obtain suitable ones.
I heard that after the Qualifying Competition’s battle royale,
Bai Shan, Hu Jia and Wu Hao, those three
were beaten by him to the point they’re still lying in bed!
Right, right!
Senior Xiao Yan’s final Fight Technique was just too strong!
So cool!
Woah,
Xiao Mei,
isn’t that your cousin?
Yea, that’s him.
He’s coming!
Cousin Xiao Yan,
Xun’er.
Oh right, Xiao Mei,
can you walk a bit with me?
There are some things
I need to tell you.
Me?
I couldn’t have imagined
that so many things happened in the clan.
En.
After I return to Jia Ma Empire,
I will properly settle things with the Misty Cloud Sect.
During this time,
try not to return.
I believe that the current Cousin Xiao Yan can do it.
Back then, I—
What happened back then
has already passed.
We aren’t children anymore, after all.
There’s no use in always thinking about it.
Regardless,
you will always be my cousin.
If there’s anything in the future,
come find me.
This place is pretty mysterious.
Old man,
you meanie.
You never brought me to play here before.
Deputy Headmaster,
does this Book Collection Hall
have any Sonic Fight Techniques?
Sonic Fight Techniques?
Of course it does.
However,
whether you can encounter one
will depend on fate.
Book Collection Hall
This session’s Inner Academy Qualifying Competition’s
top five have been established.
They have come
to obtain their reward.
Strange,
why did Teacher suddenly break off his connection with me?
Could it be
because he fears those two people?
Then they must be far too terrifying.
What is this little fellow’s name?
I am Xiao Yan.
Greetings to two Elders.
A greenish flame,
shaped like a lotus,
fiery like a volcano.
If the old me’s prediction is not off,
the Heavenly Flame this little fellow controls
should be
the Green Lotus Core Flame, nineteenth on the Heavenly Flame Ranking.
Being able to control a Heavenly Flame at such an age,
he really is a gifted genius.
This session’s top five
is much better than last session’s.
If two Elders could please open the Space Lock.
This Space Lock
is an extremely strong enchantment laid by a Fight Venerate in the Academy
several hundred years ago.
Without the two Elders using a special method to open it,
even a Fight Ancestor could not break in.
We have troubled two Elders.
Now,
you may freely enter the Book Collection Hall on your own.
Remember,
once inside,
be sure to obey the Hall Guardian Elders’ instructions.
Let’s go,
Brother Xiao Yan.
En.
Young people,
I wish you luck.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Dust rains down in the deep night ♪
♪ Standing amidst stormy wind, hair blowing ♪
♪ Heavenly Flame falls; were they ever hesitant or weary ♪
♪ A touch of Sky Flame promises to follow ♪
♪ Back then our figures moved together ♪
♪ Won’t let you down; in the end, part the fog before returning ♪
♪ I step through clouds and smoke, walking forward ♪
♪ Rejecting all the various pitfalls ♪
♪ Flap your wings and fly, fight without backing down ♪
♪ That Wu Tan youth is the same as before ♪
♪ Don’t look back, break through to the stars’ end ♪
♪ Whose support that is behind his back ♪
♪ Enough, enough, enough ♪
♪ Despite that bloodshed, that wound, that enmity ♪
♪ Never rest, forever dye the heavens ♪
♪ At the end, hold no regrets to the very end ♪