English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ In an old dream, myriad cherry blossoms fall ♪
♪ Among the galaxies, things gather and disperse time after time ♪
♪ I insist on chasing this beam of light ♪
♪ No matter how terrifying and dark the sky ♪
♪ The eternal oath surrounding you and me never changes ♪
♪ Surging like blazing fire into the air before blooming ♪
♪ That blood which boils ♪
♪ Eyes are steeped, fire actually strewn everywhere ♪
♪ Looking back, falling into the heart's abyssal stream ♪
♪ Against the wind, undergo rebirth midst downfall ♪
♪ On the journey, that person in the distance ♪
♪ will keep firmly believing ♪
♪ On the journey, that person from the past ♪
♪ sustains the original intention ♪
Battle Through The Heavens
Jia Nan Academy
Episode 9
In order to protect Xiao Yan, who was in the middle of a breakthrough,
Xun’er, fighting outnumbered,
was unfortunately injured by Bai Shan.
Xiao Yan, seeing Xun’er get hurt while protecting him,
was unable to hold back and used the Angry Buddha Fire Lotus
to trounce his opponents after he successfully advanced,
obtaining the number one rank in a show of absolute superiority.
The Inner Academy Qualifying Competition’s top five have the opportunity
to enter the Book Collection Hall to hunt for treasures.
What sorts of lucky encounters will Xiao Yan
have in the mysterious Book Collection Hall?
Brother Xiao Yan!
Welcome, students, to the Book Collection Hall.
You can freely choose from any of the rewards here.
However, only that which you can take from the energy layer will be yours;
you cannot forcefully obtain things.
Remember,
each person can only bring out a single reward.
Your time is limited.
When the outer rune circle’s flames go out,
it signals the end.
Therefore, make haste.
Hm?
Strange.
I haven’t seen any rewards.
There seems to be something over there.
Careful!
High Xuan Qi Method,
Purple Lightning Burst.
Turns out
the rewards shoot out from the energy barriers.
This Qi Method is not bad,
but it isn’t what I need.
Di Class Fight Technique.
Looks like the more valuable things
have more noticeable energy ripples.
But where they appear
doesn’t follow a regular pattern.
Girl,
looks like we should hurry
and split up.
En.
Alright, Brother Xiao Yan.
Be careful.
My Spiritual Perception,
I wonder if it can sense their energy fluctuations.
What strong energy fluctuations.
Something good?
Sorry,
I found it first.
Xiao Yan.
Brother Xiao Yan.
Girl, look at this.
Nine Layer Phoenix Flame Skill,
Di Class Middle Level.
Junior Xiao Yan certainly does have extraordinary agility.
Looks like Junior Xiao Yan
is about to miss out on this Qi Method.
I’m afraid I’m about to disappoint you.
Girl, this is for you.
Thank you, Brother Xiao Yan.
It is exactly the transitional Qi Method I need.
But I wonder, the Sonic Fight Technique that Brother Xiao Yan wants,
just where could it be.
No worries.
I’ll continue using my Spiritual Perception.
I will also help Brother Xiao Yan search.
A Rank 6 Magical Beast’s Monster Core is valuable stuff that’s hard to come by.
Regrettably,
it’s not what Brother Xiao Yan needs.
Time is almost up.
Brother Xiao Yan.
Junior Xiao Yan,
looks like the unluckiest one is actually you.
Time’s almost up,
what is he doing?
Girl,
it’s sonic-type energy.
I don’t believe I can’t catch you!
Go,
Brother Xiao Yan!
You’re not going anywhere!
Quickly see if you can take out the thing inside!
Dammit,
I can’t?
Brother Xiao Yan,
hurry!
Let me try.
I—
I succeeded?
This Lion Tiger Gold Shattering Roar
is so strong!
This kid.
It is unexpected that with the power of your meditative condition,
you were able to integrate the tiger’s roar for your own use.
Don’t get too excited yet;
right now, you merely have an initial grasp
and can only display thirty to forty percent of
the Lion Tiger Gold Shattering Roar’s power.
To reach complete mastery,
you must continue spending time honing it.
There aren’t any shortcuts.
En.
Your little girlfriend has come.
Brother Xiao Yan.
Just then I heard a majestic roar.
Was it that you successfully learned the Sonic Fight Technique?
It’s just an initial milestone.
All thanks to you
helping me take out this Lion Tiger Gold Shattering
Roar just in time at the Book Collection Hall.
Brother Xiao Yan, no need to be courteous with me.
Right,
today we’ll be entering the Inner Academy.
Are you ready?
En.
Of course.
The Inner Academy
is what all Jia Nan Academy students aspire to.
As long as you are willing to work hard,
you will be able to realize your full potential
and obtain even greater strength.
Therefore,
no matter how harsh training is,
you should persevere.
I know
that there was some disagreement among you at the Qualifying Competition.
However, young people
should be open-minded.
Who knows, you may have to fight side by side in the future.
In particular, after entering the Inner Academy,
having more friends
is always better than having more enemies.
I hope
that you soon let go of divisions
and instead unite.
Yes.
No wonder they need to escort us the whole way.
Who could’ve imagined
that the mountains behind the Academy would be this dangerous.
If we had to travel through the forests by ourselves,
not many of us would be able to exit alive, I’m afraid.
Old man,
are we at the Inner Academy yet?
Why did it stop?
The Inner Academy
isn’t so easy to get to.
Let’s enter.
Elder Zhao
Old man Hu,
having you escort the new students lets us be at ease,
always right on time.
To think,
this year it is you on duty, old fellow.
This is the Inner Academy’s Elder Zhao and Elder Lu.
If there’s any problem at the Inner Academy in the future,
you can look for them.
You five, come forward.
These five little fellows
are the top five of this year’s Qualifying Competition.
Their strength is quite good.
En.
The potential of this year’s new students
is indeed better than that of the last session’s.
What’s this?
I’ll cut to the chase.
Although you passed the Qualifying Competition
and obtained the qualification to enter the Inner Academy to train,
in truth,
the real test has only just begun.
Right now, you only need to know one thing.
That is, to treat the chips in your hands
as something to protect like your own life.
Next,
you will, as the groups you were in while entering the Inner Academy,
go into the forest behind me.
Within the forest,
a few groups of older students are waiting for you.
Only by defeating the older students, or by avoiding them,
and then successfully reaching the end of the forest,
can you truly enter the Inner Academy.
Meanwhile, the older students will do whatever it takes
to obtain the “Fire Energy” on your chips.
Fire Energy?
What is Fire Energy?
May I ask, Elder Zhao,
this Fire Energy,
just what is its use?
Once you reach the Inner Academy,
you will naturally find out.
I announce
that this session’s Fire Energy Hunting Competition
begins now!
Hurry, hurry.
Wait for me!
What are we waiting for?
Let’s go.
En.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Dust rains down in the deep night ♪
♪ Standing amidst stormy wind, hair blowing ♪
♪ Heavenly Flame falls; were they ever hesitant or weary ♪
♪ A touch of Sky Flame promises to follow ♪
♪ Back then our figures moved together ♪
♪ Won’t let you down; in the end, part the fog before returning ♪
♪ I step through clouds and smoke, walking forward ♪
♪ Rejecting all the various pitfalls ♪
♪ Flap your wings and fly, fight without backing down ♪
♪ That Wu Tan youth is the same as before ♪
♪ Don’t look back, break through to the stars’ end ♪
♪ Whose support that is behind his back ♪
♪ Enough, enough, enough ♪
♪ Despite that bloodshed, that wound, that enmity ♪
♪ Never rest, forever dye the heavens ♪
♪ At the end, hold no regrets to the very end ♪