English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ In an old dream, myriad cherry blossoms fall ♪
♪ Among the galaxies, things gather and disperse time after time ♪
♪ I insist on chasing this beam of light ♪
♪ No matter how terrifying and dark the sky ♪
♪ The eternal oath surrounding you and me never changes ♪
♪ Surging like blazing fire into the air before blooming ♪
♪ That blood which boils ♪
♪ Eyes are steeped, fire actually strewn everywhere ♪
♪ Looking back, falling into the heart's abyssal stream ♪
♪ Against the wind, undergo rebirth midst downfall ♪
♪ On the journey, that person in the distance ♪
♪ will keep firmly believing ♪
♪ On the journey, that person from the past ♪
♪ sustains the original intention ♪
Battle Through The Heavens
Jia Nan Academy
Episode 6
In order to settle everyone’s doubts,
to deter those so-called rivals,
and most importantly, to not disappoint Xun’er
who had bitterly waited two years for him,
Xiao Yan took decisive action, achieving victory in one strike.
Reuniting after a long time, the two chatted
all night, confiding in one another.
Xiao Yan learned that the power behind Xun’er
was not directly related to his father’s disappearance.
All he can do for now
is to raise his strength as quickly as possible
and to continue searching for the whereabouts of his father.
Hey,
isn’t that Xiao Yan?
I heard he’s going to compete today.
There’s going to be a good show this time.
His opponent today
is even stronger than Xue Beng.
Damn it,
how did Goddess Xun’er fall for this guy?
I mean, he just looks like that.
Exactly!
Xiao Yu,
you’d better hurry up!
Instructor Ruo Lin,
wait for me!
Xiao Yan has come.
Such a strange Dou Qi,
blazing hot and volatile as if it were a flame.
This kind of Dou Qi,
not using it for medicinal pill refinement
would really be a huge waste.
Old Huo,
this Xiao Yan
once obtained the championship title of
Jia Ma Empire’s Alchemist Grand Meeting.
If he were to join that Alchemy Department of yours,
his achievements in the future, I’m afraid,
would be incalculable!
His potential is indeed extraordinary.
However, he should already have his own teacher.
Otherwise, by just relying on talent,
it is definitely impossible to achieve such things at this age.
Of course,
if he’s interested in coming to the Alchemy Department,
I wouldn’t mind having another outstanding student.
There’s quite a lot of people.
These Elders’ auras
are overbearing to the point of making one stifled.
Brother Xiao Yan.
I’m fine.
The three on the left side of that platform
are the Outer Academy’s Deputy Headmaster
as well as two rather prestigious Elders.
The Deputy Headmaster’s strength
lies at the peak of Fight Emperor.
The rightmost one
is the Department Head of the Alchemy Department.
The Alchemy Department is independent
from the Outer and Inner Academy.
No one can interfere with their business.
Even the Deputy Headmaster can’t.
Alchemy Department.
The distribution of powers in the Outer Academy is quite chaotic.
Although your hidden strength is very great,
you still need to be cautious of two forces.
One of them is this Alchemy Department
because of the extremely privileged
position of alchemists on the Continent.
While the other force
is the Academy’s Law Enforcement Unit.
In the Law Enforcement Unit, strong practitioners
are as numerous as the clouds.
Due to their special responsibilities, they
have the authority to arrest people at will.
Back then, that bloody fight between
Jia Nan Academy and the Black Corner Region
was all thanks to them.
Many thanks to Instructor Ruo Lin for the warning.
En.
From now on,
focus entirely on the Inner Academy Qualifying Competition.
Entering the top twenty won’t pose any difficulty to you;
with your true strength,
I think
you might be able to aim for the top five.
Is there any difference?
After you enter the top five,
you will naturally find out.
Yu’er!
Yu’er, Yu’er!
Here, here!
Lu Mu
I’m over here!
Yu’er!
That is your opponent today, Lu Mu,
a top student in the Alchemy Department.
Not only are his alchemy skills remarkable,
he also isn’t weak in terms of Dou Qi cultivation.
Yu’er!
What is the level of his strength?
Around a Three-star Fight Grandmaster.
However,
that fellow is a complete medicine addict;
his Dou Qi is thin,
nothing to be afraid of.
That fellow
is Yu’er’s number one suitor.
Instructor Ruo Lin!
Stop bringing up that sticky parasite I can’t get rid of.
Didn’t expect
that Cousin Xiao Yu’s charm also isn’t small.
You think everyone’s like you?
I have too many suitors.
Students,
after going through yesterday’s
preliminary round of eliminations,
today shall decide the twenty spots
qualified to enter the Inner Academy.
The first match is
Xuan Level Class Three
Luo Fu!
Xuan Level Class Five
Ge Li!
I’m taking a spot in the Inner Academy for sure!
Luo Fu, you dummy,
fight back!
Ge Li, beat him up!
Knock him to the ground!
Looks like this Luo Fu is going to lose.
Not necessarily.
Although Ge Li’s attacks are fierce
But after a while, his Dou Qi will eventually
become unable to support them.
Luo Fu may look like he’s losing,
but he is minimizing the damage dealt by
all of his opponent’s rapid attacks.
I wonder, over these two years,
what kind of level this girl has trained up to.
I imagine
it must not be any weaker than me.
Shit.
This guy’s defense really is tight.
Fuck it!
Now’s the time!
Luo Fu’s going to win.
Luo Fu wins!
Unyielding as a mountain,
moving like thunder.
As expected of Jia Nan Academy.
If it weren’t for Teacher’s guidance,
just based on my own fumbling around,
it’d be hard to catch up to the training
progress of these geniuses, I’m afraid.
Really don’t know how Jia Nan Academy
carries out its training.
Every year, the Academy has some students
enter the Black Corner Region to gain experience.
Although it is very dangerous
and has even led to the loss of several exceptional talents,
those students that successfully return despite
going through life and death situations,
whether in terms of strength or disposition,
have all transformed into strong practitioners.
Didn’t expect that Jia Nan Academy’s top students
would actually be this daring.
That Bai Shan, Lu Mu, and others
have previously entered the Black Corner Region alone for experience.
Therefore,
don’t underestimate them.
Next match,
Alchemy Department, Lu Mu
versus Huang Level Class Two, Xiao Yan!
Xiao Yan’s doomed this time,
it’s Senior Lu Mu, after all!
This is going to be a good show,
Senior Lu Mu can definitely defeat him!
Many people are waiting for you to embarrass yourself;
as Lu Mu is considered part of the Outer Academy’s top ten,
he is much more overbearing than yesterday’s Xue Beng.
Be careful.
To put a complete end to those troubles like with Bai Shan,
this match,
you must win;
you cannot lose.
Brat,
don’t humiliate yourself.
If you lose to that annoying fellow,
I’ll look down on you.
Brother Xiao Yan,
you can do it!
Don’t worry.
I’d like to see
just what ability Xiao Yan possesses to be able to be with Xun’er.
Go on and fight,
hopefully both of them get themselves crippled.
Then Xun’er won’t be wasted on that Xiao Yan anymore.
It’s Senior Lu Mu!
Go, Senior!
Show that kid what you’ve got!
Thank you all,
thank you all for the support!
Yu’er!
I will do my best!
Wait for my good news!
This idiot.
Yu’er!
This is Brother Xiao Yan, right?
Don’t worry,
we’re all fellow peers.
I’ll hold back; I definitely won’t let you get hurt.
Or else, if Yu’er becomes angry,
the ill-fated one is going to be me!
Then many thanks to Senior Lu Mu.
However,
my goal is the top five.
Is Senior Lu Mu still willing to go easy on me?
Brother Xiao Yan,
in all things it is better to be grounded;
do not pursue what is beyond your grasp.
That top five, even I don’t have much confidence.
The match
starts now!
Senior Lu Mu!
Defeat Xiao Yan!
Give him a taste of Jia Nan Academy’s might!
Go, Xiao Yan!
Xiao Yan, this fellow, really attracts favor from the girls.
It’s only been a day since he came
and there are already people cheering for him.
Xiao Yan,
beat that medicine addict!
That top five,
I am quite interested in it as well.
I’m afraid I can’t give in then.
Senior Lu Mu.
Please.
This fellow,
what an impenetrable defense.
Even with my sword speed,
I’m unable to touch his body.
Ai,
I’ve really underestimated you.
Looks like not getting serious won’t do.
You should be aware of my other identity, right?
What I specialize in isn’t Dou Qi
but rather, playing with fire.
Beast Flame.
Brother Xiao Yan,
watch out.
My Blue Crystal Flame
once injured a Fight Spirit practitioner.
The power of an alchemist’s flame is extremely great;
this time, Xiao Yan is done for!
Sorry,
what I am best at
also isn’t Dou Qi,
but rather,
playing with fire.
Xiao Yan can also summon an essence flame?
Isn’t that something only alchemists
or practitioners Fight King or above can do?
Could it be
that he is also an alchemist?
Go, Xiao Yan!
Xiao Yan, you’re so cool!
This brat,
why does he also possess a flame?
Right,
I remember when he left back then,
Xiao Yan, this fellow, allegedly had a mysterious alchemist teacher.
Looks like
he’s also become an alchemist now.
No wonder he can summon a flame.
Even if Xiao Yan is an alchemist, so what?
Didn’t Lu Mu also fall at the hands of Big Brother Bai Shan back then?
Besides,
the way I see it, he’s no match for Lu Mu.
Xiao Yan,
I hope you can defeat Lu Mu.
This way, I can have you completely crushed in front of Xun’er.
With Xun’er’s seemingly indifferent but actually prideful character,
how could she choose a loser?
Since we’re all alchemists,
then let me see
what level the “playing with fire” you specialize in
has reached.
Pill Flame Skill!
Oh dear, oh dear,
he can’t have burnt to nothing, right?
How am I going to account to Yu’er this time?
Don’t move.
Or else the fire chains will immediately explode.
When that happens,
you won’t be able to keep your arms and legs.
This fellow
actually,
could actually control the flame to such a refined level.
Having the flame split into two,
one acted as a defense that diverted Lu Mu’s attention
while the second was lurking in the ground,
laying a trap that Lu Mu fell for.
This kind of multitasking approach
requires a substantial amount of Spiritual Strength in order to be carried out.
This Xiao Yan
is worthy of someone who became the champion
of Jia Ma Empire’s Alchemist Grand Meeting.
I lost.
Senior Lu Mu’s Pill Flame Skill is very powerful.
If I hadn’t used Dou Qi to condense some Dou Qi armor in front of my chest,
just by using the Purple Flame curtain,
there was no way of blocking Senior’s Spiraling Flame Cone.
Brother Xiao Yan,
no need to console me.
Winning and losing is normal.
Losing to one of your own
can’t be considered shameful.
This match:
Huang Level Class Two,
Xiao Yan wins!
A showdown between alchemists is just too exciting!
I want to become an alchemist too!
Xiao Yan! Xiao Yan! We love you!
Xiao Yan, this...
getting famous in a single battle, huh.
Those years,
I became trash in others’ eyes.
It was only with your unfaltering companionship,
encouragement
that now
I finally have the qualifications and strength
to stand by your side.
Brother Xiao Yan.
No matter how huge and terrifying the power behind you is,
I definitely won’t give up.
Xun’er.
Ah, young people.
I know you and Xun’er are in an intimate relationship,
but in a big public place,
you have to exercise some self-restraint.
Um,
I wonder
who will be in the next matches?
Next match,
Xuan Level Class One
Yan Cheng;
Law Enforcement Unit
Wu Hao!
What’s happened?
This match’s Wu Hao is from the Outer Academy’s Law Enforcement Unit.
Nickname, Blood Sura.
He is a strong competitor for the Law Enforcement Unit’s Chief.
These two years,
the number of Black Corner Region people who have died to his hands
Wu Hao
is at least one hundred, I’m afraid.
His strength
must not be underestimated.
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Dust rains down in the deep night ♪
♪ Standing amidst stormy wind, hair blowing ♪
♪ Heavenly Flame falls; were they ever hesitant or weary ♪
♪ A touch of Sky Flame promises to follow ♪
♪ Back then our figures moved together ♪
♪ Won’t let you down; in the end, part the fog before returning ♪
♪ I step through clouds and smoke, walking forward ♪
♪ Rejecting all the various pitfalls ♪
♪ Flap your wings and fly, fight without backing down ♪
♪ That Wu Tan youth is the same as before ♪
♪ Don’t look back, break through to the stars’ end ♪
♪ Whose support that is behind his back ♪
♪ Enough, enough, enough ♪
♪ Despite that bloodshed, that wound, that enmity ♪
♪ Never rest, forever dye the heavens ♪
♪ At the end, hold no regrets to the very end ♪