English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ In an old dream, myriad cherry blossoms fall ♪
♪ Among the galaxies, things gather and disperse time after time ♪
♪ I insist on chasing this beam of light ♪
♪ No matter how terrifying and dark the sky ♪
♪ The eternal oath surrounding you and me never changes ♪
♪ Surging like blazing fire into the air before blooming ♪
♪ That blood which boils ♪
♪ Eyes are steeped, fire actually strewn everywhere ♪
♪ Looking back, falling into the heart's abyssal stream ♪
♪ Against the wind, undergo rebirth midst downfall ♪
♪ On the journey, that person in the distance ♪
♪ will keep firmly believing ♪
♪ On the journey, that person from the past ♪
♪ sustains the original intention ♪
Battle Through The Heavens
Jia Nan Academy
Episode 11
After entering the forest, Xiao Yan’s group witnessed the
mighty strength of a mysterious older student team
and so decided to unite as one to start taking down weaker teams.
Xiao Yan, who had become team leader, led his group
to easy victory over older student Lin Ge’s team.
Learning that Fire Energy is essential for entering
the Blazing Sky Qi Refining Tower to train,
Xiao Yan decided to flip the relationship between hunter and hunted,
snatching Fire Energy from the older students.
Unexpectedly,
while facing the cunning older student Liu Mu’s team,
Xiao Yan’s team had to pay a price for taking them lightly.
Xiao Yan!
You are Xiao Yan?
Are you okay?
En.
We underestimated them.
A few battered losers,
let’s see what else you’ve got.
Everyone is injured.
Things are looking bad.
Heh.
Don’t naively think
that every older student team is as idiotic as Lin Ge’s group.
Our team leader Liu Mu practices Wood affinity Dou Qi;
he has keener perception in the forest.
How could we allow you to launch a sneak attack?
Xun’er,
you first leave with the others.
I’ll stay behind.
No matter what,
we can’t let them take our Fire Energy.
We’re fine,
we can still fight!
Brother Xiao Yan is right,
now isn’t the time to act tough.
Brother Xiao Yan,
please be careful.
Don’t worry,
I’ll go find you all.
Wu Hao, Bai Shan,
let’s withdraw.
En.
Don’t let them get away!
You four, stop them!
Don’t even think about it.
Vacuum Palm!
Everyone, at once!
Give this cocky brat a taste of our might!
Fire Palm!
Damn it.
Brother Xiao Yan.
Thanks.
Hey,
we clearly could’ve won if we fought just then.
Why withdraw?
Here.
This wound healing medicine
can help you all recover.
Take it.
Wu Hao.
Bai Shan.
That older student team has strong tacit coordination,
plus
you three were injured.
If we weren’t able to take them down quickly,
it’d definitely attract the attention of other older student teams.
At that point,
nobody could escape.
Don’t forget,
we’re not going into fights unprepared.
En.
I suppose that makes sense.
That’s right.
Our goal
is to obtain more Fire Energy.
Brother Xiao Yan,
do you have some sort of plan?
En.
Come, everyone.
This older student team today,
none of their individual strengths exceed ours.
We just took them too lightly
and were thus led away
and caught off guard.
Tomorrow,
Hu Jia and Wu Hao,
you two cooperate
to pin them down.
What a tough nut.
Bah!
Don’t think that older students can run rampant.
Atai
Heh.
Our new students’ Senior Xiao Yan
has already disposed of two older student teams.
You will soon
be the next one!
Hmph.
Xiao Yan, who cares?
Exactly!
Senior,
are you talking about me?
Senior Xiao Yan!
We meet again.
The losers still dare to come.
Can’t let them run away this time.
You all, leave now!
If you’ve got any tricks,
go ahead and use them.
If you want Fire Energy Cards,
come take them yourself!
Hmph.
Trying to run?
Hu Jia,
be careful!
Bunch of fools.
Let’s see where you run.
What is it,
has Senior gotten face cramps?
Bastard, attack!
Useless thing,
aim properly before shooting!
What happened?
Don’t get complacent too early,
once my other two brothers arrive—
You talking about these two?
You—
how did you guys find out?
Sorry,
during yesterday’s fight,
I’d already locked down each one of your energy auras.
By following your auras,
I was naturally able to find every one of you.
Based on individual strength,
you are no match for us.
How?
How could I have lost?
They are just new students.
How could it be?
I cannot lose!
I cannot lose,
Leave it to me.
Flame Splitting Tsunami!
Did you hear?
There’s a new student team
who has started hunting those Inner Academy older students in the forest.
Oh?
No way!
Who’s so strong
that they can even defeat those fellows?
Xiao Yan’s team has already hunted three older student teams’ Fire Energy.
Three?
Woah.
So strong.
According to the rules,
if older student teams have their Fire Energy go below ten,
they lose the qualification to participate in
the Fire Energy Hunting Competition.
Right.
Brother Xiao Yan,
up until now,
we’ve dispatched three teams already.
Except for the Black Demon Group and White Demon Group,
we still have two teams to deal with.
These remaining teams will definitely be more cautious.
If they surround us at the same time,
we’ll be disadvantaged.
Although our coordination is a lot better than before,
we can only deal with one team.
Two
is probably our limit.
We new students
don’t have the kind of restriction of losing
eligibility once Fire Energy goes below ten.
So the number of new students currently wandering the forest
shouldn’t be small.
What are you trying to do?
Gather all the new students
and then put out rumors
to lure over the other two older student teams
and finish all of them off.
What do you think?
That’s two older student teams,
if the new students can’t resist,
wouldn’t we be throwing ourselves into the lions’ den?
Don’t underestimate the other new students.
They were able to enter the top twenty of the Qualifying Competition;
they won’t be weak.
Moreover,
if we clean up the older students sooner rather than later,
wouldn’t we be able to go to the Inner Academy earlier
to check out the Blazing Sky Qi Refining Tower?
En.
We’ve already wasted three to four days in the forest.
Delaying things indefinitely won’t do.
I don’t mind.
At worst, we’ll just have to return the Fire Energy we obtained.
You’re the team leader now;
you can make the decision for these kinds of things,
quit being fussy.
Who’s there?
Wait.
It’s us.
Senior Xiao Yan,
just then,
thanks to Senior Xiao Yan for saving us.
Otherwise
we likely would’ve taken another fat beating.
No need to thank.
Senior Xiao Yan,
could we possibly leave the forest together with you?
We are all new students,
naturally, we should support each other.
You all
can team up with us.
Awesome!
Wonderful.
Senior Xiao Yan,
you really are a good person!
Yea!
Here,
this wound healing medicine is for your injuries.
Thank you.
Thank you, Senior Xiao Yan.
Come, come.
Here. Here.
Everyone,
do you want to
give those older students a lesson?
They’ve bullied us this much,
of course we want to beat them up!
We definitely want to beat them up!
Beat them up!
That’s right!
En.
Since that’s the case,
help me out with something.
Everyone,
do you want to return the grievances
you’ve suffered these past couple days
to those conceited older students?
Yea!
Take back our Fire Energy!
Beat them up!
That’s right!
Senior Xiao Yan.
According to your directions,
I’ve already revealed our location to the two older student teams.
They are heading over right now.
Good.
Everyone,
hide yourselves.
Today,
let’s give these arrogant older students a good beating
and take back the Fire Energy we lost!
Alright!
Prepare for battle.
Things are getting lively.
En.
Xiao Yan.
Hmph.
Luo Hou
Interesting.
They’re here.
Su Xiao
Turns out you are somewhat capable.
No wonder you’re this cocky.
Hmph.
They’re nothing much.
Very good.
We’re all here at last.
Junior,
don’t let some temporary victories muddle your brain.
As long as you have strength,
the positions of the hunter and the hunted
can switch at any time.
And now
you are our prey.
Then don’t blame us for bullying with a numbers advantage.
Xiu Yan
Sorry,
we also did not intend to fight fairly.
Leng Bai
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Dust rains down in the deep night ♪
♪ Standing amidst stormy wind, hair blowing ♪
♪ Heavenly Flame falls; were they ever hesitant or weary ♪
♪ A touch of Sky Flame promises to follow ♪
♪ Back then our figures moved together ♪
♪ Won’t let you down; in the end, part the fog before returning ♪
♪ I step through clouds and smoke, walking forward ♪
♪ Rejecting all the various pitfalls ♪
♪ Flap your wings and fly, fight without backing down ♪
♪ That Wu Tan youth is the same as before ♪
♪ Don’t look back, break through to the stars’ end ♪
♪ Whose support that is behind his back ♪
♪ Enough, enough, enough ♪
♪ Despite that bloodshed, that wound, that enmity ♪
♪ Never rest, forever dye the heavens ♪
♪ At the end, hold no regrets to the very end ♪