English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ In an old dream, myriad cherry blossoms fall ♪
♪ Among the galaxies, things gather and disperse time after time ♪
♪ I insist on chasing this beam of light ♪
♪ No matter how terrifying and dark the sky ♪
♪ The eternal oath surrounding you and me never changes ♪
♪ Surging like blazing fire into the air before blooming ♪
♪ That blood which boils ♪
♪ Eyes are steeped, fire actually strewn everywhere ♪
♪ Looking back, falling into the heart's abyssal stream ♪
♪ Against the wind, undergo rebirth midst downfall ♪
♪ On the journey, that person in the distance ♪
♪ will keep firmly believing ♪
♪ On the journey, that person from the past ♪
♪ sustains the original intention ♪
Battle Through The Heavens
Jia Nan Academy
Episode 5
Xiao Yan, after killing the treasure-robbing Blood Sect members,
ended up as the greatest beneficiary of the Black Mark City auction.
However, because of this, he made new enemies.
At this time, Jia Nan Academy is holding its fierce Qualifying Competition.
The top twenty students will obtain the qualification to enter the Academy’s true core, the Inner Academy, for training.
Xiao Yan, who had been absent for two years, has finally appeared.
Brother Xiao Yan.
Xiao Yu
This guy.
Always has to make such a big commotion;
he really loves to show off.
Senior Xiao Yu,
is that the “Brother Xiao Yan” Xun’er is always talking about?
Who would’ve thought that he was actually
able to make it at the last second.
Yea.
This is that brat who is always making Xun’er worry.
His looks,
are you disappointed?
What’s the use of just being good-looking?
At Jia Nan Academy, strength is what matters.
If he wants to prove that our Xun’er didn’t wait for him in vain,
he’d better show some real skill.
This Xue Beng is a Nine-star Fight Master
and the “Overlapping Waves” Spear Fight Technique
he practices is Xuan Class Middle Level.
It has defeated quite a few opponents!
Who knows if Xun’er’s Brother Xiao Yan will be able to handle it.
That brat should be up to the task, right.
I don’t believe that, with his personality,
he’d have achieved nothing during these two years.
Enough, enough.
Stop guessing.
No matter what happens,
he is still a member of our Huang Level Class Two.
Let’s all properly cheer for him.
This Xun’er’s Brother Xiao Yan doesn’t seem like all that.
Yea.
Not sure how many exchanges that small
body of his can last against Xue Beng.
Xun’er’s sight really is...
Exactly.
He is that Xiao Yan?
His strength is only this much.
You are Xiao Yan?
Correct.
You aren’t worthy of her.
Perhaps.
That Brother Xiao Yan Xun’er speaks of is finally willing to appear.
It seems he isn’t particularly handsome.
Hu Jia
I can’t fathom why she thinks about him so much.
Hu Qian
An interesting little fellow.
Hopefully he doesn’t lose to Xue Beng as soon as the fight starts.
Otherwise,
Xun’er will have really lost all face.
At Jia Nan Academy,
countless people have been waiting for you to show your face.
Starting from today,
your troubles will be endless.
However,
today I will have you defeated in front of Xun’er.
This way, you won’t need to worry about those troubles.
To be honest,
I also quite dislike those troubles you speak of.
As such,
I’m sorry that I have no choice but to wrong you.
Oh?
Trying to use me as an example to warn the others?
Not afraid of hurting your tongue from talking so big?
Can we start?
The match starts now!
Arrogant kid.
Shit!
Octane...
Overlapping Waves-
Blast!
What?
So- so strong.
This fellow,
isn’t his improvement too quick?
No wonder he is able to let an outstanding
girl like Xun’er constantly bear him in mind.
This fellow
really does have this ability.
Interesting.
Just wait,
she will definitely be mine.
What destructiveness, determining all with one punch;
not bad, not bad.
This little fellow isn’t an ordinary person.
Girl,
I reckon that even if you or Bai Shan were to face him,
who wins and who loses would be up in the air.
Then I’d like to have a match with him.
If I win,
make him get out of Jia Nan Academy.
Nonsense.
Huang Level Class Two,
Xiao Yan wins!
Xue Beng lost just like that?
He is a Nine-star Fight Master!
Looks like
this Xiao Yan is at least a Fight Grandmaster.
Such a young Fight Grandmaster,
even at Jia Nan Academy he’d be ranked among the top.
That’s right, he’s too strong!
Sorry,
I came late.
I knew Brother Xiao Yan would definitely come.
This Xiao Xun’er,
how’d she become this bold?
Is it just because of that man?
So romantic!
Instructor Ruo Lin.
You still remember that I’m your instructor?
Don’t think that you can get away by not saying anything.
Skipping a year of classes,
you’re really capable, huh?
For the past year, do you know just how much
I wore my lips out with the Academy because of you?
Instructor Ruo Lin,
regarding this matter, this brat Xiao Yan
has indeed carried things too far.
However,
as long as he and Xun’er
are able to persist and enter the top twenty,
you can be promoted to a Xuan Class Instructor;
you won’t lose face.
Instructor Ruo Lin,
I will definitely try my best.
If you still feel like you haven’t been able to vent your anger,
waiting until after the Qualifying Competition
to punish him wouldn’t be too late, right?
At any rate, he’s already come to the Academy;
you can’t be afraid that he’ll run away?
Fine.
Once the Qualifying Competition is over,
I’ll settle things with you.
Alright,
return with me for now.
The next two days will have even more intense fights.
Trying to enter the top twenty for the opportunity to train at the Inner Academy
Xun'er, let's go.
isn’t some easy task.
Many thanks to Cousin Xiao Yu.
Xiao Yan.
Coming, Instructor Ruo Lin.
During this time,
both you and Xun’er can stay at my place.
Then I’ll trouble Instructor Ruo Lin.
Everyone has seen the information;
sure enough, this Xiao Yan is not simple.
Single-handedly,
he contended with Jia Ma Empire’s Misty Cloud Sect
and was even able to kill a Fight King head-on.
What is most shocking
is actually being able to escape successfully from a Fight Ancestor.
This kind of record, even the Inner Academy’s very best
would find it difficult to achieve, I’m afraid.
His potential is indeed very great.
With proper grooming, he may become another peak practitioner.
As for the Misty Cloud Sect,
it only has a single Fight Ancestor;
they would not dare do anything to my Jia Nan Academy.
Misty Cloud Sect is indeed nothing much,
but behind them...
First secretly investigate.
If there really is value in grooming him,
we can give it a try.
Leave her.
What, you?
Weaklings
don’t have the right to possess her.
Lightning attribute Dou Qi.
Bai Shan,
what are you doing?
Nothing.
I only wanted to spar a little with Junior Xiao Yan.
Why must Xun’er be so worried?
With Junior Xiao Yan’s ability,
if he can’t even block one of my random attacks,
how can he participate in the Inner Academy Qualifying Competition?
Senior Bai Shan,
on account of your being my Senior,
I was polite to you just now.
But if you continue being this unreasonable,
then do not blame me for being unforgiving.
If you are a man,
don’t hide behind a woman.
Bai Shan,
you better not cross the line!
Girl,
these matters,
it’s fine for us men to settle them.
You really want to fight?
If you’d like to,
I have no objections.
I have objections!
Student Bai Shan,
messing around like this
is not in accordance with Academy rules.
If you want to challenge him,
you can just settle it at the Qualifying Competition.
Coming late at night,
not only is it improper behavior,
but you’ve also left a bad name for yourself.
Xiao Yan,
I hope you won’t get eliminated in the
middle of the Qualifying Competition.
At that time,
I also hope that you will no longer keep hiding behind women.
A man that Xun’er has recognized
wouldn’t be a coward, right?
Bai Shan, is it?
The so-called man of the hour is only so-so.
You do seem to be an expert when it comes
to jealous and spiteful words, however.
We’ll meet again at the Qualifying Competition.
If you lose,
leave Xun’er.
Are you sure your name is Bai Shan
and not Bai-itch?
You-!
Go back.
Unexpectedly,
because of her,
I’ve actually allowed myself to be this out of sorts.
Therefore,
she must be mine.
Xiao Yan,
just you wait.
It’s been a long time since I went moon gazing with Brother Xiao Yan.
Girl,
these two years,
have you been doing alright?
Do you want to know
what I’ve been through these two years?
Back then, I left Wu Tan City
and entered the Magical Beast Mountain Range to train.
I didn’t think that Misty Cloud Sect’s Yun Shan would still be alive.
It is really beyond my expectations.
Afterwards, I had no choice
but to hide in the depths of the Magical Beast Mountain Range
and to try escaping from Jia Ma Empire.
It was unexpected that Misty Cloud Sect
would spare no effort pursuing me.
Fortunately Yun Yun, based on our past friendship,
removed the seal inside my body and let me go.
Brother Xiao Yan,
when you return once again to Jia Ma Empire,
I believe
that the Misty Cloud Sect will no longer be able to hinder you.
Surprisingly, this fellow went through so much over these two years.
No wonder he has grown so quickly.
Xun’er,
come with me.
I have something I’d like to ask you about.
Xun’er,
this matter is extremely important.
I need you to speak with me truthfully.
Matters Brother Xiao Yan wants to know about,
Xun’er naturally will not hold anything back.
Earlier I mentioned
that following my first departure from the Misty Cloud Sect,
Misty Cloud Sect’s First Elder
brought people to exact personal revenge on the Xiao Clan.
Before I made it back,
the Xiao Clan had already suffered heavy losses.
There were countless deaths and injuries.
Isn’t this Misty Cloud Sect too bold?
Father, for the sake of protecting clan members,
drew away the enemy by himself.
While he was being chased into the mountain forests,
he suddenly mysteriously disappeared.
To this day, his fate is unknown.
Fate is unknown?
Uncle Xiao did not fall into the hands of the Misty Cloud Sect?
Based on the information I currently have,
Father was not captured by the Misty Cloud Sect.
Moreover, now
his life is no longer in danger for the time being.
Therefore, I infer
that Father’s situation
may have other mysterious practitioners involved.
Mysterious practitioners...
What is it that Brother Xiao Yan wants to ask Xun’er?
Xun’er.
I know that you are not from the Xiao Family
and that your background is extremely strong.
I know that the power behind you
has some kind of relation to the Xiao Family.
So what I want to ask you is
whether Father’s disappearance
has to do with the power behind you.
Perhaps you weren’t aware of this matter,
but could you help me inquire about it?
I must obtain confirmation about Father’s safety.
Otherwise,
I won’t be able to sleep or eat well.
There’s no way.
I’m sure that it wasn’t them.
They and the Xiao Family have an agreement
so they definitely won’t forcefully intervene in Uncle Xiao’s matters.
This kind of agreement’s binding power
isn’t as simple as ordinary people think.
Even if some people among them wanted to do it,
they would inevitably face intense opposition.
Furthermore,
being able to take away Uncle Xiao in front of three Fight Kings
must mean their strength is at least at the Fight Emperor level.
But during this time,
I haven’t heard any news related to this.
Fight Emperor.
Besides me, no one in the Xiao Family
has ever gotten in contact with a Fight Emperor practitioner.
Other practitioners mysteriously taking away my father,
what is their purpose?
Brother Xiao Yan.
The power behind me indeed has ties with the Xiao Family.
As for the details, however,
it won’t be good for you if I tell you now.
It seems like
my father’s disappearance still has something
to do with the Misty Cloud Sect, I’m afraid.
This sect
is seemingly not as simple as I thought.
I will have people help investigate this matter.
If there are any clues,
I will tell you immediately.
I still need to raise my strength as quickly as possible.
Or else, even if I learn of Father’s traces in the future,
I may not have the power to rescue him.
Brother Xiao Yan,
you won’t blame Xun’er for not being willing
to tell you about the power behind me
and its relationship to the Xiao Family, right?
Would you do harm to me?
It’s very late,
go back and rest.
The Qualifying Competition resumes tomorrow.
Send people to collect information
about whether there have been recent traces of
other mysterious practitioners in Jia Ma Empire.
Also,
I require all available intel about the Misty Cloud Sect.
Yes,
Young Lady.
Just who was it
that would actually have intentions towards Uncle Xiao?
English subtitles by: Falling Star Pavilion
discord.gg/hkW5GNk
♪ Dust rains down in the deep night ♪
♪ Standing amidst stormy wind, hair blowing ♪
♪ Heavenly Flame falls; were they ever hesitant or weary ♪
♪ A touch of Sky Flame promises to follow ♪
♪ Back then our figures moved together ♪
♪ Won't let you down; in the end, part the fog before returning ♪
♪ I step through clouds and smoke, walking forward ♪
♪ Rejecting all the various pitfalls ♪
♪ Flap your wings and fly, fight without backing down ♪
♪ That Wu Tan youth is the same as before ♪
♪ Don't look back, break through to the stars' end ♪
♪ Whose support that is behind his back ♪
♪ Enough, enough, enough ♪
♪ Despite that bloodshed, that wound, that enmity ♪
♪ Never rest, forever dye the heavens ♪
♪ At the end, hold no regrets to the very end ♪